HAPTER 19
Showdown"
Episode 110
Written by.
SUZUKI Satoshi
JVIusic By.
YAMASHITA Kosuke
That hurts!
Did you hit s ething?
Are vou ay£
I might have twisted ^
my ankle
Don't fail me now, ankle
It s morning.
It s perfectly okay
Hitomi? What's wrong?
Alios ui,|
Did wake you7
\ have rehearsal, so
II be leaving now.
Jt'££lmostfime,
Isn't jt?
-We 41-all We
£b lit no
Hitomi9
Umei
I'm sorry I cant
make it today.
But I thought I gave you
a grand send-off so
I g t this..
Firestories. ?
got these from my late
husband s mother
Was that back in
•fhe Meiji era?
The Showa era!
Does the fire cbme
out from this?
it's called flrestones, but
only sparks come out
t's used to exorcise
the bad spirits
People in the past used
to hit the two stones
togefh r when they
were going out.
Havent you seen it in the
historical dramas...?
When the wife sends
her husband off
I've seen it.
Are you ready7
Go ahead
Hitomi..
t's norwo king.
Is itdaifip?
Let me^e&|hat
Where did you
leave it?
In the kitchen.
No wonder \t'§ damp.
Maybe it s moldy.
Hitomi
it's not workin
I have jo o
We have to exorci £
the bad s Irifs
Here we
This c Xfld take
forever...
You'd better^
Youjejicht
I'm sorry
Not at 1i
II do my best
Katsu. She left1
Once this is finished,
let's get • eady
for 4he -rehearsal.
ix thfriight
o erthere!
They were preparing the
hail for t i opening
in two hours
You're KEN an f
CHEAPASS aren' ou?
May we $hake>our hand7
Jjiankyou*
itomi9
UIUJOUI po
That p "t r
Is?
a picture us
e Tigiimejigo
This is EIJI
J^L
me looks like a tiice u ,
but you had to wltc
Wfien he got all wor ed p
about his dancing
That's right
e" lliaveib
<Jo ourtiest
V ^: too Hitomi
pQjypur est
will
Good mornmg
Hitomi^
How^our foot9
It sDkay Nothing
to worry about
Don't take it lightly
I'm really worried.
Don't get upset
This is a list of doctors
th 1 Moe found for you
This
Dep lidmg on your
condition, there
are different specialists
J'm sorry for making you
all worry so much
You g I us even more
worried when you
keptf sistm that
you were okay.
Sefe?
I guess it's okay
lEvery Tie' ell Explain
the ^otedure, 1> will
you all gather
he stage?
I'll change first
That hurts1
Maybe I got too
carried away
There Wfer6l28 units who
would be competing in
the T Icyo preliminaries
Out th t only a few vfould
fe'choseh
tom vepnto
ihe national c mpetition
-tcvi "tor the title of
the best str a e
If they didn't mak^t
^st the preliminaries,
Hitomi and the others
dream of app &ing on
Dance Beat would end h te
ROSE 1/1 ARY.KI^tart/
*
tfr reiieirtk
"Hitomi?
I'm \ay!
I'm sorry'
Please go on to
the next unit
L Vs Jiave the
ne limit.
lAfc UMALL V?"S 1CK
You re Dtaii
right are you?
You have*! sprain
don't you?
I'm sorry
Hello hota?
We were just leaving...
We'll 'cheer har nough
for you, too
Sh ta! Be sure u cheer
her on from izu Oshima
Did you lear that7
Talk to you again
Katsu'
We should get going
I'm waiting for
a video letter
Video letter7
Shota s mother made a
video with Shota s
message to Hitomi
And they sent it so that
it would arrive m time
Let s go. Katsu
d like to go but
i can t go yet.
Shota sent a video message, but
it hasn't gotten here yet.
pftatffe ait
of Tit n
B on t hur , we
e tin time
Why r ou two dressed
ike that9
Hip op! A cap an
a -smr
A t-shirt and a cap1
At- n r antia ca\1
t II de ntis^w he
son eating t.
Vo loo ik you'ff otng
)h) m
JMhat's r cavith rying
t n ^the s^rit,
and cheering iheirhon?
Katsu! ou'd better hurry,
or you'll £e late.
I know. but>e re waiting
for something..
Yu... ou'xe my friend,
aren't you9
Of course You re
my best friend
Sn that case, we ll go
on ahead, so can you
wait here for the
delivery service?
What shall wexlo7
Whfere ss the neare I
TiospitaP
They re all on
lunch frre&k .
if we wait, we
miss our turn
I don't have to go
lo the hospital
As long as put
spirit into it
Hitomi
Don't over Jo it
Shall wet:hange our
dan€fe*sleps to ta f
some Uhepressure
If i&mi'sfooP
it'st^ate for that
What are We goin
to do then?*
Hitomi9
Let me see^hat..
You really did it,
didn't you?
What do you want to do?
want to dance
(CHEAP 5S Its your
turnto re "fearse.
We'll come, und check
on you again later
Talk it over
carefully
We will
hank you
What £hS1l we do'
I'm going to wo
•Jill • *
e^do
It's one hour before
the opening.
If i lose. I'll take bver
the restaurant
I'll quit dancing, and take
over the restaurant
That's okay with
you, isn't it7
I I
I'll eil
Hello'
Hitomi.. It's your iom
You came?
4 wouldn't jthss it1
It's y r ay
to shine.
What's ^yrorig?
She twisted her ankle during
the rehearsal earlier
That's terrible1
It's swollen1
I'm okay.
\fthat shall we do?
Let's do jt
We jdont ha$e a
choice, do we9
But JHitomi cSuld
barely stand...
Can yoCFdance llkeihis?
Sure I can
Did y li ee a doctor?
There s no tihlg^o we
were going to . .antje
thexiance leps^ut it's
too late for t tod
it s n6thina..
I'm fine.
You 're not Jin !
It hurts, o 1 it?
It s swollen'