CHAPTER 20
The Next Step
Episode 116
Written by
SUZUKI Satoshi
Music by
YAMASHITA KosuKe
You did it!
So ROSE MARY is going
to make their debut
We did it!
You did it!
Congratulations!
Thank you!
Can this really
be happening?
Yes it can!
Wait! It's not what
you think
What do you mean?
What is it?
They're going to make
their debut, but
though Yuka and Junko
were scouted
you weren't included,
Hitomi
The're forming a live-dancer
unit, and two of them will
be Yuka and Junko
This happens ail the time
When only several members
of a group are chosen
it has to do with image
and character, and
things like that
That means those two
had ability, doesn't it?
That's great..
Shall we celebrate?
I'll call there now, and treat
you all to "monja'
Its too early
to celebrate
What do you mean?
They both plan to
turn it down
Why?
They don't want to do
it without you.
Hitomi
It's been a while
Moe told me
I'm sorry you're holding
back because of me
It's not that.
The dance was made for
the three of us
That's why we don't want
to do it without you.
But Junko
You always said you wanted
to make a major debut
It was your dream.
Wasn't that your goal?
And it's your chance,
too, Yuka
It's your chance for everyone
in Japan to see you dance.
You both have the
ability.
The ability to dance on
stage professionally
It would be a waste for
you to turn down.
Up to now, my goal was to
go to Dance Beat, right?
My dream was to go to Dance
Beat with the three of you.
That's why I really,
really enjoyed it..
It was totally fulfilling, and
I had the greatest time
So when it was over, I didn't
have any regrets
But it shouldn't be
We all have a long
future ahead of us
When I heard about you two,
it made me realize that
I need to start
something new
It's only natural, but
I fee! like it's telling me
to start something.
So while your debut is a chance
for both of you, it's also
a big chance for me to
take a step forward.
Your debut is something
that I'm proud of, too
So...I want you
two to debut
All right
The other day I ate together
with my father and mother
for the first time
in a long time.
It wasn't too bad.
What about you, Junko?
How are your parents?
I'm sorry I made you all worry.
They're fine now.
Are you going to tell your
father about your debut?
Actually, I already
told them about it
And?
? actual*!
I for it
He's really something
else, isn't he!
He is, isn't he?
So no more obstacles
in the way of your debut
Let's make another toast!
We just made one
iA/hoc rfes9 It's something
to celebrate, so we'll
make as many toasts
as we want
Stand up
You want us
to stand?
Don't worry
Ready?
Here's to Yuka's an Junko's
shining future
Here's to Hitomi's and Moe's
unlimited possibilities
Monji is sweet
youth, isn't it?
It is..
I'll see you.
Let's all do our best
We should get together like
this once in a while
Yes, let's!
Let's get together again
See you!
Take care
You, too!
I'm glad for Yuka
and Junko.
I'm glad, too
I want them both to
do their best
I'm full!
Thank you for the meal.
Are you done already?
I ate "monja,' o evfcn
if tried Uo
eat too much..
I'll givel i^sei to
the two of you
Are you sure?
Go right ahead
Thank you.
Ray!
We were talking about
what we should do after
Dance Beat was over,
I never expected him to
be selling dried bonito
I was shocked
But it's
good for KEN
It's just like him.
When we re dancing, rather
than think about our moves,
he moves with his
body first
What are you going
to do now?
I've been thinking about
several different things,
but what are you
going to do?
I heard about Yuka
and Junko
How do you feel about them
making their debut?
I'm really happy.
After all, we were
a team..
But it made me think that
maybe I didn't have the
ability or that I was
lacking somehow
It's not just Yuka and
Junko.. everyone
around me seems to be
moving forward..
I feel like I'm being
left behind.
Better not to rush
to an answer
You have your own style
of dancing, don't you?
Why don't you take a good
look at your dancing again
I will
Hitomi!
Hello Ray
Our cherry blossom viewing
party will be tomorrow
It looks like the cherry blossoms
won't fast much longer
All right
If you want to,
please join us.
Please do
OK I'll come
Let's a ty!
Th
Flower-viewing. This will
be my first time
Come to think of it, Hitomi
didn't come for our flower
viewing party last
year, did she?
That's right
Katsu was so angry!
He kept calling your
cell phone
All I got was your
voice mail
You were dancing,
weren't you?
Dancing?
It aswi tfen
OCK6
The time when you and Ken
^Ja e dance floor.
^atlime^
It made me realize how
awesome dancing was.
It was good for you,
wasn't it, Hitomi?
It's like you met your
life mentors
That's so true.
m ountlngo th two
it jnJjmaiJ r
y e sure
Isn't it supposed
to be a cat?
gu pm around and
around when you
dance hip hop,
Tti/ou9
There are people who do,
ke^his
p... - lip... 11} .
h s more like £
on uance me
You can dance any >
s is your hip
Drink up. £ t up
This atmosphere is
real, isn't it?
Do you like this
kind of thing?
I enjoy it
Shall I have
more to drink?
Go right ahead
Dad.51?
Try to keep,
Yujiro.
I have to work tomorrow
I'm thirsty
That's enough.
There's more to it.
You've had enough
I'm not the eyebrow type
Ken! Ray!
Can you dance the
Mayuge Neko?
No, I can't
I'll teach you.
OK, I'll try
Me, too
First, start with the
mayuge neko pose
What shall I do?
Nice, isn't it?
You look cute, Ray!
You're doing great,
Suzuki!
It was an enjoyable
flower viewing party.
But Hitomi still didn't
know what her next
step in life would be