HAPTER 18
Season of Love"
Episode 108
[mom w <108
Written by
SUZUKI Satoshi
Music By.
YAMASHITA Kosuke
"Hngli liSu litleBy,
KrtPpbN G Q 1)ENtjfefwbRK
Why^on't y t^nd KEti tell
e^eryo^V^trpth?
Be atise KEN told me
n6f to say anything.
He was tr>ingtonjpi>>1d
Elilferfionor
D ncing is our friend
e didn't do anything
o betray pur friend
Betrayal wa mt the reasoh
for'EIJfs death
It was all a misunderstanding.
Hitomi?
What fo7
About KEN... 'm sorry
dboot ail the things
| at j said... I didn't think
ftbout your feelings
W.tn I said those things.
i was just jealous .
It's nofthe kind of jealousy
fhafyou think
it's more like a big brother
not wanting a strange gtiy
taking his little
sister away
o.. I'm sorry
It) tferstand... Thai."5.
Itiave to apologize, 4ob
|fn sorry... Pm going
out for a while
Where are you going 7
Hey! Take an umbrella1
ake an umbrella'
it's going terrain
Hitomi..
Hitomi1
Moet Vou're here?
I wanted |o ik l/l0B0 about
wh F ttzu aid yesterday.
But th truth is..
o 4 /eally
kno either
It's if a mi "Lnd V$tanding.
rrisu. U Tstanding...9
So t tame to apologize
to KEN..
KEN fee back.
Over there
I'm going over e
h&f£ she so \tf51rked
up about anyWay?
There sglbtjjoirtfj
in he world 5flan
Like what?
hat would yo
ike to drink7
uhal" lemoyi4lavored
soda with Toehil)..
I'm sorry but we don't
ser^e "ciiTJhai" here.
I'll have one
of those.
Tequila.
Tequila7 I jl tiave
Awt for tfow
KEN
I'm sorry Ibput
said last night
I just wantedf to apologiz
to you... RAYtoldme
about ElJl and 1>
CHEAPASS
I'm really s fry abo
terrible things 4 ^f (J
What7 Do you still
be ieve in him9
Kazuf
It's coward for you to
keep /Mining away
Kazu .
EIJI wouldn't give up
dancing over
something Jike thit
You don't how the
truth, o^ou9
Only my brother knows
^hat was in Is heart.
But lie's not here1
That's whv I'm
going to ance
-toil sh TSldrTi dri K
it like th 1
But it's good
That s enough already
tiate ih s
t full-fle
et
-Even though 1.4
Wait a minute
No matter what
the ~eason
It s our fault that
£IJI died
EIJI w tildnt forgive us
if Say and I danced
e- EN1
Y zo?
^ op being a coward,
and {lance1
Hi)on1 betray Hitomi's
expectations.
ken*.
"Why wo 1 yo dance9
4) ou call yourself
a cfan ^r?
Hitomi
tfitomi respects you
So what s yoiir problem?
Stop *t
RAY
Watching you being so
wishy-washy makes me mad!
You're pitiful1
Why ddhl you
just dance?
What would you know9
You wouldn't understand.
I don t understand1
That's how it is.
That's just how it is ..
I don't understand
Damn! You'r? no good. The
way you complain about
useless things... You act
cooi but ou re not1
I'm no good eith r But I like
myself best when selling
dried bonito, yelling at
the top of my lungs,
and I feel like I'm challenging
myself as* man in Tsukiji.
That's whatl like
about myself
That's why I'm going
to do my best
Even if I'm riot quite
full-fledged, I'm still
going to do my best
Isn't... isn't it like
that for you, too*
Don't you like yourself
when yotf re dancing^
You like your Iff when you're
dancing, dont you?
I'm not alone, am Y>
Say that you do
He was my close friend.
The person i ££red about
the most, and he said he
wouldn't dancfe anymore.
I told him to dance
Then hetofd me
You enjoy dancing with
RAY mor "than me"
He was fight... S mewherpdeep
down inside, th t's how I felt
And EIJI re tiled that
betrayed EIJI
It s all my fault*
KEN
I want to dance
with you
I want the two of us
to dance ag^iiri
Let s dance the
way we are now
Let's dance with all the
burden we're carrying
Isn't th t what
a dancer is?
We re dancers, aren't we9
We have to dance
We need to dance
I'm a dancer
til do it
441 show everyone
who I am now
Yujiro... It'sHitomi.
I'll open the door
You brought him home?
1/Vhere did you go?
You're soaking wet*
o old do you
think you are9
Didfi start fighting
-■again somewhere?
e !l talk Ibout
4 at Another time
See you'
Men... are really urtcool
Thank you
o \J night
Sorry ibout that.
Dad...
What s it >
I'm going to do it
Because like
dried bonito
Never mind that
ake a bath, and
go to bed
I'm going to do it
Did you hear me?
All nght
I'm fading to bed
You're go tig to
catch cold
Hurry, and go to bed
Pm going to do it1
CHEAPA % put their entry in
or
the 2008 Danfkfieat
Tokyo preliminaries.
"Ever o jth<3iife e
Uujjjii vm '
d n IfSg and^omincg
a ce Beat is just
aroQncI the corner