CHAPTER 14
Mother Shows Up
Episode 80
I'm sorry to worry
all of you, but
my grandpa made a complete
recovery and is home
from the hospital.
Thank you!
I'm so glad.
Now you can do your best
without worrying about
anything, can't you?
Thank you.
It was tough on all of
you, too, wasn't it?
We've known each other
for a long time,
we only did what
was expected
y/e .us^iave to help
each out whenever
anything happens.
Thank you so much,
everybody
From now on, I'll do my
best at dancing, at work,
and at home again.
a Ij^jjy)
Clo ninggfore...
Mr. Wakayama! Hello.
Actually, it's
about Shota..
What about Shota?
Shota! I'm going to turn
off the light soon.
I see...so you're going
to enter that Dance Beat?
I'm so glad!
3 a ISO to continue
dancing with those two
so owTmr lievedt.<it
we decided lo do it
I think I'll sleep
go09 tonight.
Good night
Hitomi
I need to talk to you.
Sit down.
Actuaily, it's
about Shota.
What about Shota?
Did I tell you about Shota's
mother before?
Yes, you did
Isn't she the one who
brought Shota to the
child care counseling
center, and left him
there saying that she couldn't
raise him anymore?
I wouldn't exactly put
it in those words...
Because there were a lot of
circumstances involved.
What about her?
She contacted the center,
and she wants to take
Shota back with her now
Why?
I don't know all the
details, but it's
probably because she's in
a situation now where
she can raise Shota
Which means that he would
leave the house
Of course
If his mother's going to
raise him, there's no
reason for him to
stay here
I can't agree with that
Why not?
Because you've put all your
effort into raising him.
It can't be helped...
After a!!, I'm just
a foster parent
Promise me you won't talk
about this in front
of the children
I wouldn't say anything
How could I?
The next day Hitomi and
Katsutaro went to the
child care counseling
center
I'm goin to explain
everything that I can
about what has been
going on until now
Ms Inoue has been in
charge of staying in
contact with Shota's mother
regarding his foster care.
Ever since spring two
years ago, I haven't
had any contact with her.
She moved without
letting us know
Last month, we suddenly got
a phone call from her
One month ago, August
This is the child care
counseling enter
Yes?
Ms Saito?
Shota's mother?
he s
a her living
situation had changed
and she wanted to
take Shota back
How did it change?
She's getting married.
He brings in a stable
income, so she can
raise Shota without
any worries.
And something like this
won't happen again.
Even if she says that,
I wonder
We've had quite a bit of
discussion about that, too.
his is thefnSte jal e
have n oa in
illji)liL
hota'jgjji 1 gave birth
to him as an unwed mother
After that, she worked at
nig Is, and tried to
make a living, but she
changed jobs often,
f,-aftcfher income
was unstable
She gets lonely easily, so
she tends to rely on
men ot, so^she w Did
put the men ahead of
her child.
She didn't have much of a
desire to raise a child
so Shota wasn't getting
enough tofel.
Wasn't there someone else
who could look after him?
Shota's mother's parents
divorced when she was
little, and her mother
raised her. But when
she was in high school,
her mother passed away
Her father went back to
his hometown, and he's
still aliyfe'drid
well there
But they don't have
contact with each other.
n i iu jsu aia
j' .jjw^Jy
Ktnq or n into
CO
er
iio,
ti ♦ j ^jn
a tee ir ent
ul jijj • J/tu)i Jli,
si ts eon cam
% couldn
a s him m re.
n now she called us and
said that she's getting
married, so she wants to
take Shota and raise him.
But you didn't hear
from her in over two years...
Should we trust someone
like that?
he s s true
r in more
th igh
n iron i o aise
6 11J XJ-J]JL
Ms. Inoue..
Why don't you contact her
and have her come in
for an interview?
All right.
I'll do that.
hj) jhlJ J J J
SJilhiUJ
Mi « Dm
iFre oka
J 3pitil?* 3L
I'm really sorry
How is Shota doing?
He's living with a foster
family and doing well
e s
Shota's m
Saito Mikie
3SETG /o
We tried to contact you
a ffiim ?H8flime£ ut
you moved without
telling us.
I'm sorry.
What were you doing
for over two years?
You should have
contacted us
I was in no position
to do that.
I was having problems
with my boyfriend
Weren't you worried
about Shota?
I never forgot
about him
It's just that
I wasn't qualified
to raise him.
But you are now?
The man I'm going to marry
says he'll help me
to raise him, too.
I'm planning to leave my
current job by the
end of this year
I'll concentrate on
being
This time, I as
As far as
her desire to raise
Shota is very strong
Of course, we have to
check into the actual
living situation, too
In order to do that, we
paid her a home visit.
We had her fiance
come over, too.
Are you living
here now?
No, we're not living
together yet..
Although, I spend the
night once in a while.
We're looking for a place
now where the three of
us can live
We'll find something
this year... won't we?
We plan to register our
marriage this year,
but the wedding probably
won't be until next year
I see... What kind of
work do you do?
My parents have a Japanese
restaurant in Akasaka
Mikie's fiance: Imasaka Iitsuru
It's an old traditional
restaurant, and I'll
eventually take over. But
right now my mother
is running the restaurant.
I'm in charge of a branch
we have in Shinjuku
tlepartment st 1
In that case, you'll have
a stable income
I guess..
Just in case.
I brought last year's
withholding form
If you don't mind,
I'll have a look.
We couldn't find any fault
with her fiance's income,
and he understands what
happened with Shota
and seemed willing
to raise him
It looks like her life
has stabilized
She's more stable
mentally too
There was a big difference
from how she was before
So after taking all of this
under consideration,
we decided that she's
presently qualified
to take Shota in
and raise him.
I understand
Thank you for
understanding.
The next step is for
us to talk to Shota
We have to think of
Shota first, so we
want to see how he feels
about Jus er
and if he wants
to see his mother
eil have a ps ch 1o ist
come a o ith s
Do you think you could
bring Shota over here
without telling him
about his mother?
r we can come
to get him.
No... I'll bring
him here
Thank you.
Mr. Wakayama.. 7
I can't agree
with this.
What are you
saying, Hitomi?
Do you agree with them?
Of course I do
They explained
to us very carefully.
HoW can you agree
to this?
It's so sudden!
You're going to just
bring Shota here
all of a sudden
Stop , Hitomi
h or>
Because you raised him la
with a lot of love
You cared for him, and
SCO
Icied
him. and ou
put all that effort
into raising him
Yi someone like that
really raise Shota?
Don't talk like that
She's Shota's mother
But .
She's Shota's mother!
She's the mother who
gave birth to him...
She's his real mother
Hitomi..
I understand how
you feel but
I want you to think
about Shota.
Shota's mother has finally
been able to make an
environment where she can
raise him properly
There are a number of
situations, but if
we think about Shota,
it's best for him
to live with his
real parent.
Excuse me, but
I'm leaving.
Hitomi!
I'll go after her
It's okay
II maffe her
understand
I'm sorry s e was
orude to on
I'm sorry..
No, it's all right