CHAPTER 8
"Two Kinds of Love"
Episode 45
Sano...
Good morning.
I won't interrupt.
When you walked me home
yesterday, you told me
about your real father,
didn't you?
I was thinking about
that all night long.
About how sad it was.
So Yuka is staying at
Junko's place?
That's unexpected, isn't it?
Isn't it?
They never got along.
She must really have
been in a bind.
After fighting with her
father, she left home,
but Yuka doesn't have
too many friends.
But this your chance.
For what?
For the two of them
to become friends.
Then it won't be a dream
anymore for the three of
you to form a unit.
That's right.
You said you wanted to
dance with those two.
It might become a
reality soon.
It would be great,
wouldn't it?
Ever since she failed the
audition, Hitomi had
become impatient with
her dancing.
The classmates who had won
the audition seemed more
alive in their movements
and their expression.
She felt she had to
start something.
Unit?
We have to do something.
We can't let Kyoko and
her unit beat us.
You can't form a unit unless
you have a goal.
I don't want to do it just
for self-satisfaction.
So our goal will
be Dance Beat.
Are you dreaming?
The two of us were no good
at all at the audition.
That's why we're going to do
it with the three of us.
If we have Yuka, we're
guaranteed to be good.
She won't do it.
Don't you feel anything
between you since
you're living together?
Not at all.
When we're together, she's
either listening to music
by herself or watching
a dance DVD.
It's fine with me since
I don't have to talk
to her or worry about her.
I'm going to talk to her.
It's no good, Hitomi.
Yuka!
What?
Will you join Junko and me,
and form a unit?
Our goal will be
Dance Beat.
Why do I have to dance
with the two of you?
We don't think alike, and
we're on an entirely
different level,
aren't we?
That's why it's good.
Junko has the determination
to rise up in the world,
and you're very stoic, so
it'll be like a chemical
reaction and create a spark.
What about you?
Me?
I...
I'm big, so it'll be fun.
I'll be your weapon!
I'll make an awesome weapon.
I'm not convinced.
You're living with Junko,
so couldn't you consider
it as repayment for a day's
food and lodging?
Of course I'm grateful, and
I'd like to return the
favor someday, but dancing
is different.
Also...
I think we're alI fated
to be together...
When you came to Tsukishima,
you liked it, didn't you?
What does Tsukishima have
to do with dancing?
It does have something
to do with dancing.
Here it is.
Isn't it nice?
Can we use this
place for free?
Sure you can.
You can use it whenever
I'm not using it.
You're very generous,
aren't you?
Look at this...
When I see a lousy dancer like
her, I can't just ignore it.
The only thing I ask is...
When you all become successful,
you look after me in my old age.
I'm just kidding!
What do you think, Junko?
Being able to use this place
for free, isn't bad...
What about you, Yuka?
How about the sound?
How rude! The amps and the
speakers are top of the line.
Listen to this.
Here you go.
It's a great studio, isn't it?
Isn't it? It costs a
lot of money.
Dancing is my life.
Look at this, everybody.
Awesome!
It's awesome!
What do you think?
This is a strong argument
to form a unit...
No comment!
Why?
Before I do that, there's a
lot of things I have to
think about... I can't always
stay at Junko's place.
Should I go back home, and
if I don't, what am I
going to do?
I don't have time to be
thinking of forming a
unit right now...
On top of that, I'm running
out of money.
She's a little depressed...
She's not used to not
having any money.
Sano...!
Shimada?
Shall we go this Sunday?
Where to?
To the place where you parted
with your real father when
you were five years old.
I wanted to see it.
I feel like I can understand
how you felt if I could just
go to that place.
I don't want to go.
I know I told you about it,
but can you just forget
about it already?
Goodbye.
Sano!
Akira... What are you doing?
Were you thinking
about Naoko?
No, I wasn't.
But she really is a
nice girl, isn't she?
What high school is she going
to take entrance exams for?
I don't know.
It would be nice if it's
the same as yours...
It doesn't matter if we
go to the same school.
Good night.
He's embarrassed.
How embarrassing.
Thank you for the meal.
I'm a little drunk.
That's right... you drank
a little too much.
I got carried away...
There wasn't anyone
to interfere, too.
Are you talking
about Katsu?
Maybe...
Mari...
What is it?
What are you doing?
I really like you, Mari.
I had fun in Kamakura, so
do you think we could
make it official... would you call it
dating or is that the wrong word?
Is dating a little
too formal?
Yu... let's not
do this.
What are you saying?
I said... let's not do
this kind of thing.
Be careful...
Don't fall down.
Good night.
Wait!
Mari!
Good morning, Ume.
The owner of a clothing
store has to be a dandy.
Good morning!
It looks good on you.
Yujiro...
What's wrong?
Aren't you going
to work today?
I don't feel too good.
What's with you?
I have a fever.
It's just a hangover.
Come with me...
Just come with me.
What is it?
Watch the shirt...
It's brand new.
It's brand new...
Forget the rest.
What does he mean?
Last night, I got drunk at
Mari's place, and I held
her hand...
You did that?
What did Mari do?
She pulled her hand away,
and told me that we
shouldn't do things like that.
She said you shouldn't
do things like that?
That's right.
Does that mean she jilted me?
I don't think so.
Haven't you heard...
"Even if I seem indifferent,
I burn with passion for you."
Do you think there's hope?
I think so.
Thank goodness.
Is that why you were
drinking all night?
After I came home, I drank the whole
bottle of sake that I opened.
You're hopeless.
Thinking about it gave me
a headache and I even
have a fever now...
What should I do now?
What am i going to
do with my life?
Don't get carried away.
I'll go with you next time, so
for today, don't think about
anything, and go to sleep.
Shall I think about it,
and go to sleep?
Don't think about it!
That's right.
I won't think about it,
and go to sleep.
Got it?
Okay... I got it.
I'm glad I talked to you.
You have great
literary talent...
What's wrong?
We figured out that it's just
a fever from Yujiro's wisdom.
Sorry to worry you.
Is that all?
Good night.
I'm leaving.
A part-time job dancing?
AII the part-time jobs
on the reception room
bulletin board were filled,
so I bought a magazine...
Look at what I found.
Looking for a dance performer?
It's 8000 yen for three hours!
It's a Sunday afternoon job,
so it can't be one of those
dangerous jobs...
It's for an event.
You probably have to do one
of those things the idols do.
So what if it is?
It's 8000 yen for three hours.
I think it's a good idea.
Leaving the question of
forming a unit aside.
it might be good to see
how the three of you
dance together.
If it's some kind of party,
maybe there'll be some
important people there.
Maybe a music producer
or something.
It's your chance, Junko.
But you wouldn't take a
part time job like this,
would you, Yuka?
I'll do it.
I want the 8,000 yen.
I want to eat something
besides "gyoza".
That's it then.
Give them a calI, Manager.
All right. I understand.
I have the address, so
I'll find it on a map.
Thank you.
It's okay.
The four of us have to go
to the office in Aoyama
on Sunday at 10.
From there, they'll take
us to where it's held.
You said "the four of us", didn't you?
Who's the fourth person?
Me.
Are you going to dance, Moe?
They said they need
four people to dance.
I can't wait... can you?
I'm looking forward to it.
What's going to happen?