HAPTER 19
>iowdown"
Episode 113
Written by.
SUZUKI Satoshi
JVIusic By.
YAMASHITA KosuKe
That was entry number 24.
ROSE MARY*
Give them a hand!
It tonsffeaily good'
^Yuka!
'You'were great1
tj w~?e/eally<jreat'
JD 13 eaia it was
great, too
Thanks for coming
1 remembered how you used
tow tCh television and
fiance till the time when
you were little
We us tltd clap and enjoy
watc Ifttj you
It was fun back then
After watching you dance,
i began thinking how
nice it would be if we
could be a family
like that again
C me, arid have dinner
with us soon..
I'll brinp a bottle
of wine then
I'll see you
et'sgo Dad
Thanks
To all of us dancers,
being able to welcome
this unit back again is
really and truly a
great joy
F uryears ago, after a
tragic event, this unit
went from three to two
Today,-these!wo will d nee
together for the first
time in four years
Togetie ith£IJI
the! Irdljdanc ?...
Entry number 28
CHEAPASS*
it really seemed as though
iJI was theVe with them.
Entry nu t) r£8.
CHEAPASS
Give them a hand1
My brother was there
with you.
My brother was happy
that he could dance
with you two,
wasn't he9
Yoti have now seen all
28 entries dance
Jow the judges Will go to
a separate room to make
their decision
n the meantime, aii of
you can party along
with the DJ
I cant wait to3)ear
the results
But
You were pretty good.
He raised me1
Did you hear that1?
Yo » were pretty goo
Moef Moe1
a surprise
Yo i n't have tocbme.
m ot ^oing to dance
Of course we
have to come
We're here because
you're not dancing
All the people who danced
had people to applaud them
but only a parent would
applaud someone who s
not onstage to dance.
My d~"ti and mom
/ioe's always indebted
to all of you
Here ylj go, Manager.
You're embarrassing me.
We ll see you at home
Thank you
ankjou very much.
ou have
Wh
nice
arents, don't you7
i Thisiscute!
It's cute
Kazu?
Are you leaving r
already know we-won f
win with that dan V.
I'll be back ex
I'll choreograph a more
cheerful dance for us.
Following your example
kee you1
& \ you1
Thank you alt
for waiting
Her6 are the results of
the judges deci Ion!
This is a tense moment
Only the judges and myself
know what the results are
Let s get started
Nl£t£rt with the Judges
Special Award...
ffie winneF/>f this award
£ rtfint go oh to the in s.
«u jnreco nitiono
libilit y^nd achievem
tye'd like to Vesentth
tyi h this^special a
The Judges'Spe 1*1
A^arci goes tt>...
-Entry number fa,..
l^VA^I
lease come tip
I can imagine the ' otions
this special awar rings
Congratulations, KE
And RAY!
Ypu u filledjwt
emo ion with this Judges
Special ivwar^. Please
say a few words.
Thank you, everyone.
I'm really happy t *be back on
stage as CHIiAPASS again
after all these.years..
I hop o I II ontinue
ai) o* JM hf
Let's do our best
Thank you1
Th5tXvas great, Suzuki1
Yuzo? Who's Suzjki?
His name is Suzuki /ten
His name is Suzuki?
Thank 70U tor "Waiting.
i d like toannoun €the
teams \ ncwiTl^be
advancing to the nation
wide final rente t
Only three teams out f
the 28 entries for this
Tokyo competition will
go on to the nation
wide final c est
The irstteamis..
Entry/lumber 2.
Z ~y OTE TE
With their salaryman
dance.
T %y II be going on to the
nation-wide contest
rom the judges . Hereis
your ticket to the finals
The second team is
tntry numb
JAJrm\i u
Aren t /ou glad t
wasft't a bad dream7
Herets^our ic e. o
fu Ins frpm thejudg ^
a€ongrSt|H liorf^l
Here's the last team
Entrv number .
Twenty- hree!
dW TICK
He e« the!ast1i£k 1
o he finals.
CTigratul lions.
MARSHffi tLOW"STICK!
These three teams have
won tickets to the
nation-wide finals
Give them all a
big, big hand'
That's the effo of the
Tokyo competition
for the 2008 Dance Beat
Thank you afl
for coming