CHAPTER 12
I Can't Go to the Festival
Episode 72
Tetsuo
What is it, Mom?
I'm going to stay here
in the tenement
e everyone here is
more like my family
Sorry to bother you
Dear urry'
T4ie4iSn to party at Ume's house
turned into a disaster.
The next day
I'm sorry to call you all
of a sudden like this
I was surprised
Is it about yesterday?
AluallyrTr a little
regretful abt) t whit
kt^UJ?. Jj"1'
have<g ne4oo far
It has nothing to do with
the shopping mall.
I've already given
up that idea
No... I was being
childish..
I'm sorry
I'm actually happy you said
those things to me
I just wanted someone to
hear how I feel right now
How you feel?
I thought you might
understand the best
I felt as though we were
in the same position.
Considering your relationship
with your father
And you left, and abandoned
Tsukishima once, too..
To be honest, there was a
time when I looked down
on Makoto's way of life.
He had no sense
of adventure
He just stayed shut up in
his own little world
in Tsukishima.
When ! was in high school,
that's how all of the
merchants along the
shopping street were.
I thought it was
a bonne life
I understand. I felt
that way, too
That's why I wanted to
succeed in the big
world outside of
Tsukishima
I thought my mom
would be happy
But when I came back during
the festival, I felt like
a stranger when I heard the
sound of the Tsukuda Festival
Then I thought I didn't
belong there anymore.
I just stayed away
I feel the same way.
I still can't go to
the festivals
That's why, out of stubborn
pride, I tried thinking
that what I have now is
better than Tsukishima
And I wanted to ask my mom
why she was still clinging
to a place like that
Yesterday, I said it was
for the sake of mom's
happiness, but that
was a lie
It's my go
On the taxi home, I had an
argument with my wife.
When I complained about
the way she disciplined
Takeshi, she told me
How can you say
anything when you haven't
done anything?
She was so angry
I couldn't handle it, so
I got out of the taxi
before we got home
stopped at a bar, and
I drank myself under
the table
What my mom said as I was
leaving just kept going
around and around
in my head.
That the people in the
tenement were more of
a family to her
I knew t. sat
H ouidn't ake
a real fanfily
She told frie what I had
known all along.
That's when I finally
remembered that
I was raised in
that tenement.
Katsutaro and Yujiro used
to scold me as if I were
their real son... And they
really worried about me.
I used to love festivals.
I was proud of my mom's
inari sushi
Why couldn't I make
a real family?
I got depressed
as I drank
When I couldn't get any
more depressed, I went
home, and I became defiant.
I'm going to do things
the way I want even
if I have to fight
with my wife
That's all... Thank you
for listening to me
Tetsuo's declaration
T^it,sffim!wanteH
to say...
tftrv^ talle
ou
odt. and just | Iked
T>ut I have t>^jo'
I'll liout the
tenant spot.. J
I'll get th.l.. *
Thank you
Whether it's mother and
son, or father and
daughter, parents and
children are really
bad at expressing their
feelings, aren't they?
If it weren't for being
embarrassed and stubborn
pride, the parents and
children of this world
would be so happy
Don't you agree?
I do
See you
What's wrong?
Do you remember Tetsuo?
Ume's son
The one who left
Tsukishima...?
I heard all about it.
You had a fight
with him?
Today, he told me that
he wasn't able to
make a real family.
That's why he's going
to try all over again
diieu i, I ^IbUO b
Declaration"
Was he just trying
to get back at me?
Do you want another?
My treat.
I'd better not
I don't want to cause
trouble for you again
Don't worry
about it
Go ahead and
get drunk
There are days
Thanks
When 11 la Grandpa
about that, he
Was happy... But he got
embarrassed wheril said
you were his
daughter, after all
That's not true..
He was probably
laughing inside.
That old man's always
laughing like that.
Excuse me
Takeshi?
Go on, Takeshi
Say it really loud.
The other day, I broke
the planter but
I blamed it on Shota.
I'm sorry I lied
I'm really sorry
Shota..
Takeshi..
Shall we shake to
show that there's
no hard feelings?
Put your hand out
Youw nt hoi
t now, will yoOi?
He went and apologized
to Makoto, too
My wife told me
not to, but
I convinced her
I talked to Takeshi for
over an hour
It's the first time we
talked that much.
Letqcrfh Yi
Sorry to bother you
Mom?
What is it?
Go on...
I'm sorry t i H he
food you made the
other day, Grandma
I'm sorry I p!ayed my game
while we were eating.
It's OK
We'd better be going.
Already?
We'll come back..
After we become a
real family.
Let's go.
Everyone!
Today is special.
After the fireworks are
over, go back to your
bed quietly
Yes ma'am
You have a nice view
from here, don't you?
We look forward to it
every summer
Good evening
Momoko?
Momoko, What are
you doing here?
I came to see how
you're doing
I was in the
neighborhood
You don't have to
be so surprised
It's a surprise to me when
you come to see me
Don't talk as if
I'm a ghost
Sit over there
Good evening
Good evening, Aunty
He called you "Aunty"
Stop it
That's really nice.
It would be great if I had
a beer right now
Don't ask for the moon...
This is a hospital
How are you feeling?
Not bad. I don't
feel any pain
Really?
How's your work
coming along?
I'm doing my best.
It's really hard though
That comes with
any job
Thank you for that
The towel you gave me
when you came to visit
I use it to wipe my
sweat all the time
I bought that in a rush,
so next time, I'll bring
you a better one
That was good enough
After all that happened,
it seems father and
daughter are getting a
little closer now