C APTER 9
I'm Getting Married"
Episode 51
What do you think, Hitomi?
Do yoli think Dad
will like him?
I think it's important to
take him by surprise
You know how Katsu is so quick
to start an argument
hat should I do?
How about if 'he two of you
standby at Mako s place,
and Hitomi will see if lie s
n the fight mood, ihen
call .you two over?
hat might be
Will you do it, Hitomi?
This coming Sunday
Got it. We'll wait for
the perfect timing
Yuka'
Sbyfare^e I to being
% tiftie rich jgirl.
Farewell, little
rict^ qirlf
Let's race!
4/Vait!
I'll give you ere itfo
making thte ffccision to
move from that mansi Yi to
this cramped little oom.
She's right. There's^
world of difference
between this cramped little spac
and your big. ancy/iouse
It's okay rjn go na o
make a fto^wsta't
frofnjhispram
little a p i r m rt
I wish you allj^ou n ee
saying "cran ^little..."
I want4o liange..
If I do that, then I'm sure my
dan Ing will chlhgertoo
1-et's hurry,-and eat, so we
can-put your stuff aftay
After all, this place so
"small and cramped.
oa t«
What are^pu iioing
orry . you anted us
fo Jiurry,^nd£*t, cig 1?
jot hat!
What's with hat^aCtee?
ou put tooVn cti "rayu"
(sesame lot chili^il)!
Doni I alwaystell y u'^St
wiat makes pa ks ihe
jjyofi' s he sa h?
Yes,
This is how Junko and Yuka's
new life together started.
hat's good!
And also, Momoko who has been
transferred to the company's
And also, Momo "5W % has been
traInferred to the company's
o yobra ch office...
You mean Keiko to e
over o e I m
she was gettin rie
i hats fight.
But you arid Grandpa started
fighting, soshecouldn i
bring hSrself to tell him,
and she anded upjjomg
home^without saying anything
I feel so bad
about that
11 • v- bxj/^v/ii^yjitm
e to be real careful
7ft
appen to push the
lLLllLJ 'JilitOib
ii\% Ipp JjIJU
j j ugimoto..
u ^4iere eally
Working overtime?
Yes.. What about you
Mr. Sugimoto?
for ot omething
jng jlng to spend the
ight here, nd -o
ack to the main office on the
first train in the morning.
Branch Manager Sugimoto
ugglinq the work between
h \e and -he main office
is really hard
I'll leave everything
here in your hands
I may be the branch manager
in name, but you're the
real branch manager.
Stop that
After k\l you've always
been the top in sales
Be sure you sell our products
to all the department stores
here in Tokyo.
have faith in you
I'll do my be t
d better be going
ood night
So ry fbout that
I heard everything.
You're really important
here, Mom.
That's right... I'm pretty
important here
I'm impressed.
It's hard being a
It's r Ully
I-know it's hard, but
whfcusJhaP
It's lust plas ic that
we iflsfe to pack the
tooxe f "ka s obushi"
(dri ifbonlto flakes).
know that! masking
^od jJvhSt you're oing?
It relaxes me wh
I break the tub e .
TiiriK now
what ins...
Tou'-fetr rng to destroy
ycur ear it«y esires
Earthly esires?
Out-of .o i erationfo
jMSri's feelin , u put
a-iid on is urning
passion to tier, but
deep o n in is hear
he just can't orget.
Jh Ys why he' a in
those smolderin
feelings "hebyonp,
feelings on ne, a d
I ^e...
IV//
Jil O/ajyi Jjliy
ri e^ire ...
u s already tie r
over 500 of those
He has 500.. My a
has 500 of them.
You have 5-0/earthly desires?
Ii /i/iJ! I i
No, that'6 not t.
The hardest thina Oi e
right novv is trving o
figure out how to . aV
up with her
Once th n .
you, t' ^ard t6 make
isn't it?
p isntii?
JHello'
I bought too much "shirasuboshi"
small dried baby s Tdines).
h ^nk yoli for always
thinking of us.
hat are you doing?
m riot doing an n .
love tothis
When I break Jhe bubb e
on these, jt all
calms me oton
You^smash itlike hib...
And it fe Is so U
You, too?'M/\/h\iJ o s
it really calms me o\ n.
jajaliui^ ^iia of ^
I'll give ou a Tree
dri \ when you come
b mj'jb&x*
Go ri Tit ahea .
Thanks. a "71 drink
■attnyT>1 t ^ In..
To^eth r*with*Ksts .
Sure... Jl ome y.
• • •
hanK yen.
That went rath V
smoothly Dad
It did, dicln'J it/
/XjJsiiJtlJ »
her
iU lA JLto'l
Isn't it great,
Yujiro?
ijji'aji uyy^
di n'tP
I did it!
The day Keiko plans to
introduce her fiance
to Katsutaro is here.
Are you ready? I'm going
home now \o see what kind
of mood Grandpa is in.
it's okay, I* I'll you, and
give you t e * o" sign
All right.
Its nerve-racking, s.t t.
Especially §fter what
happened with Momcno.
i It ^vas really £ ethin',
wasn't it?
Do you remembe t.
I can't forget
My dad was still all e
That's when yp and ! ust
started helping p e,
wasn't it, Hiros
Shall we explain t
to Mr. Katsum a
L t's do t
You're talking about when
iftf i jiu : stii, i 111 uibuwnmy
you! Don't ever set foot in my
i jubfc dLjdir,, div.ii i you.
Th t avas the second time...
Whe tie b oug t Hitomi
WhatVm talking "bout is
seven years before that.
The first time Hitomi s
lather Nagase Wataru
came to visit the
lppongi family.
Vlbmoko's Elopemen a .o.'
o o 6 lo a
tie ortab e shrines^re oming
Uiuijh ilia iiraa^m
tt i y ite.noon of
t e su utta estiva!...
Mom o i . nti says.
Da ... herejs someone
ant you to fneet..
This is Nagase Wataru "
ey, a . lease let
m omoko *
as aro s shocked!
Th s rivo.o an is the
e yjp to e of the
hs nvoousman s h
juj j/fta
^ Jti^h ^JjIOjj^j J utlU YJiU
o I e erfit n e
n o ntown Tokyo. Mom T<o
Irea knew that he would
p e the marriage That's
hy e brought him over
durin - e^ i a , .oping
jjv .^ijijjau
n the s "Fffoise aril!
conf o e festival
h s not the Way the ball
oun es in the real world!
What! This is perfect
/!') Willi h utt/iymy
ecious omo o
Can you carry a
ortable shrine?
O comfsc n amateur x:an't
carry a portable shrine'
to rsedn Amateur an'l
carr^fc Vtaline! '
3D Yhewlcjht lone as
Vc to t let ou have my
precious Momoko'
Mom s traged! "You're
amdiot, Dad! V *t\\
taying in this house
any longer'"
s if they were following
f he unds of the f "Clival
fa in a theiwo of
"b m left Town.
Tli ' h ull accounts
Momoko s lopement
ou for lisle Ing.
hat's so funny
Ho "*c£n you Be
so carefree?
What are^ou going to do
if that happens to us?
It won't happ . There
isn't a festi al Ve
today, is ere?
That's what
I meant...
I'm talking ab it Dad won't
allow us tp get married.
If that h s, then you
can just run off, and
get married..
I don't wa:.t that!
I want to hav D d's blessing
when I get arri a
In brderto make sure the
timing's erfect, I'll
go and Judge #hat kind
of mood lie s in first.
We'fe counting on you.
Here's *he sauce 1 borrowed
from you the other day.
Thanks. 1 brought It back.
There was no rush..
The stuff you use for
business is different,
after all, isn't it?
Keiko...
Hello..
who's this
Mr. Katsumata..
Keikos fiance
She £jgoing to bring him
ov >J "l Produce him
to Grandpa today
Fiance?
This is Yujiro..
\He's a really good
friend of Dad's
Pleased <o meet you
m Katsumata Seiji
Please let me marrytfeiko.
Dlr.tfatsumata... This man
isn'tTier father
Are you okay?
What's wrong?
i is is em e. ; won e
how Katsu ill to e th s
I'm a little worrie
He's tt of resembles
your dad
You titnk so, too?
It's not his looks
He just doesn't seem the type
who would f t iff around here
I^agree with you That's why
I'm a little worried, too
You're worried?
So am t.
What's wrong? Why do
you two look so serious?
Keiko brought her fiance, and
sTie s going to introduce him
to Katsu today
Where are they now?
At Mako's lace
I'm going to
lake a look
J'mgoin to eilYuzo
Wait a minute! Make sure
you dori' tell Grandpa
I know
I know!
Just be sure to keep
Tt a secret
I ill!
I'm home!
Shota! Stop crying, and
move your hands
What happened?
ought Shoia was quietly
rawing something, but
he took ese arKers^rom
the store, ecause he
drew a lot, the Ink Went through
to the tatami m*t floor
Look at aRhe colors
you used... This isn't
going to tome ^f
It's n 1 going
t ^tome off
"What f uy is he?
He has SOme nerve... Asking
ttftrlarry Keiko
'She's like a little
sister to me
jSo ifjie s just playing
around, 111 kill him.
It&not coming off, s
It'js^a waste *four
*-whole Sunday
What is this anyway?
Can yot ry\a
ortable ine?
I've never tried.
Theft it's no £Odti
ncte Katsu hates guys
like that, doesn tjie?
Don't say that
1 waftt you to io T(
at 1s gharact f
He's a really nice person
Then just* H
Uncle Katsu that
Calm down..
What do you think,Ume?
Why are yo i in
our head like lat?
Because he's not
the right type...
Not for me^xit
for Katsu.
That's her.
Hello, Hitomi...?
Keiko? Go' Go! Go!
Well done, everybody.
T:'s really clean now.
hank you very muc^i.
"You can go, and do
whatever you want
Grandpa's in a really
ood m bd right no
Come right now.
Come as fast
as you can!
igfct
a a
All right We re
coming over now
^Are y TTokay?
These are really
we. one.
sis .n eresting
/jlVIKJ^ uisjtti
e a tie
Keiko is finally going to
introduce Mr. Katsumata
to Katsutaro
i
ifcaro*