-CHAPTER 20
The Next Step"
Episode 119
Z> (D—&J (11
Written by.
SUZUKI Satoshi
Music By.
YAMASHITA Kosuke
f ^yxjot together an awesome
groiFp for their :art-time
job as Mayutje Neko."
Hello'
YU su~6 a ^ full
it)? energy!
You're qoma to be etferrmore
eneideMc diter tnis...
Whiit sjg lngto i you
nergyis nbt the
Maneki Nekfc," but
fhe "Mayuge N Vo "
Here are the "Mayuge Neko."
Thank you'
It's over1
The children re?!l
iijia
It doesn't happen
that often.
It was great1
It was the best "Mayuge
fdeko" performance yet
Thank you so much.
Wei! done'
^Please come back again
if we have something.
The bonus, dear
I Added a bonus for your
great performance
Lucky1
We have to clean up.
I'll bring the car
so wait richtTiere.
Thank you.
hank you so much^
€N and RAY
Not at all...
It was fun
Thank oil.
J don't think I would Jiave
enjoyed something
like this before^)|it
I guess i feel 3
little freer now
I enjoyed toda*, 00
I made lip my rffind.
Abo t what9
fn going to e rk
To train all
over again.
Does )hat mean
that you're going to
dance on £tacje again7
I wasn t sure, but
i made up my mind.
Jfiis made me realize that
there s still something
more I can do up
on staae.
So I'm noin to tr
it on my own..
away from CHEAPASS.
I'J Believe n my own
dancing, and olish t
4i t's so coo), RA
o your best
Good ^uck
tfchat about you. KEN?
I don't know... But for no ,
I ll sell dried bonito
Dried bonito, huh9
I ll do my b t
oyour be t
ou gl&cHhat your
homeroom teacher is
Mr. Fpjita, Yuria?
He alread n
iDxiJn^
jSf^ jiy
his reqarcls. AVir..
Give him my regards,^oo
He£3 really good teacner
JHe really is.. After -when
Akira purposely got
zeroes on his^Tams^e
really was wdrrie .
I won t et zeroes
^Don t bntigthat
up *lready
Hitomi
You ye been realty quiei today
Eve rin< inner
-Didni vr -SJVIayLge Neko"
go we.ltbday^
Di3 you na1<£ a mi~T "kfe?
really well.
Dicf it?
re youjMStiired hen?
It's keen a while
since jyou glanced
jlrvihat 6£fe, y \i should
fake^ fcath and^ust
ao to ^leep.
Ye you home, Katsu?
I'm here
You're here,3oo,*Hitomi.
After y5u eat, Jet's go.
We fin s in
We were just resting
fyou'r'finis ed in
th€n let £ go.
To "Matsuri"7
Very ^ferpeptive
That's about the only
thini od ayaiyway
What is it you \ cinted?
We wanted to talk to
you about thin s .
Like Hitomi..
^wonder .what Ritomi's
Ing to donow
Didn't she say^he was
U 1ng to dance for
a part-time job?
KEN went,-too
1 hought that was
a good dea
It's a good way to
relieve stress
Good evening!
-What are ou
doingiiere?
Yuiiro aJk me to come
He said he w TMBto t fk
*tpjne a l>ut Hitomi...
Did v^iicall her, Yu?
IJUt
e ant to drink
with yo*i and Mom .
thought* as a ^ood
ch Yipefor U etwo of you
When 1 saw th iwo x>f you
puty ufheads together
because you ere^orried
about *Hit$mi,«l thought
it was time th 14he tyvo
q|^ou o back to
being ^ normal father
wand daughter again
Isn 't it about time you
started iSfkihpto each
other like any rtiinary
ather ancl jdau Thter?
nave a seat. iom
Sit down Momo
Right here
What would you
like to drink?
11iave a battle
xight here, Man.
That's right
Here you go
I'm going to pour
Thank you.
Thanks for whatyeu
did for Hitomi
i itomi said she learned
4 lot from working
at our place
leerfc
HIJjjll\J 3 72jj12jj£33J X)
im iJ xjota
^ YmJirJu] ^ajlraa
ia«T< you! "^Think youl
j} 3 3 hi }}
*You think I don*
no "that!
ijprobdbly kn w more
"Sn^you do
/hat^are you sayng
She and I were together
or>20 years!
She s only been with
you for a year'
hat you saying?
Now., now
/ Y ti know that you both
are about Hitomi, so
"St back to hat you
ere talking about
Ab Tft what Hitomi should
o from now ton
Jiat' oghts
tfiscu ..
That's true
If th\e's somethingt ^t
^Hitomi an get Yithusiastic
ab tit anSTget iifoit,
a decides that she
wants tb 5o it, thfell I
Nl 1f\are wh \ it is.
After I, she's seri "us
And cheerful..
S he jias leadership
qualities, too.
She takes after me.
hfe gets ihat
from me
Calm do 1
Say somethin . Man
"fe.
No, it*
Jgavebrh 6-her
I'm home!
Good evening*
Moi^i'
You were toaether7
We were otfethfr vJith
Yujiro at M *tSbri.'
How nice that e
getting along
Have a se 1
Are two going
«o talk?
Nl jusfgo
upstairs then
Wait a minute
We ant to talk Jo 6u
Sit over there, Hitomi
Me
Momoko and t were
just talking...
You teally have a iot
of go tJ points
I'm not saying that you
sho Id work in an office
You can decide whatever
you want to o, but
If that's at this
is aboii hen..
ant to keep da cing,
fitter all
realized today that
J neeato
ance
realized it when I went
to do that part-tiifte
j 1) dancing as
Mayuge Neko"
You told me, didn't
you Mom.. ?
That you could w tk harder
bebau fe people would
say, iiictiiKyoj.
I he children really
enjoyed our*Jan<fc...
And a lot oT thfem
thanked us
I v as really happy.
I still donl knowjvhat
form it'll like, j)ut
I'm going to continue
dancing
I'll find something so that
it's not just for my
own seif-satisfaction
Isn't that making
progress.. ?
Just getting to
this point
Good night
Good flight.
! guess we'll just have to
wait and see for a while
Since Hitomi says she's
making progress
I guess so
There's no use pushing
her too hard
Vlomoko.. i =eard
you re working hard
Hitomi t 1d me
That you're really
working super hard
A s just that
we're busy
We don t have too
many employees
That's an added "burden
for you, so be sure
to take careDf
yourself
Thank you
Ill talk to you if
anything happens.
If anything happens.
Momoko
Be careful
Looking for a way that
she could continue
dancing in a way hat
was suited to her
That gave Hitomi the
feeling that he
Jiad taken a step in
a new directi n