CHAPTER 8
"Two Kinds of Love"
Episode 43
They're holding
an audition...
The song will be the
d-Darts debut
You can do it solo
or as a group.
You'll make a great yvefc
when it comes to imp
I'm a weapon?
But your dancmgliad the
one thing that was
mos- moorian .
e> njoying y urselves
ie: ju were dancing...
Watching ou two
a o a e
Kcuslbng...
Old o ant something
r housed
No... It's nothsng
We're leaving, Hitomi!
We're leaving, Dad!
They're full of energy,
afen't they?
What about y\i?
JNow that ou failed thejudition
I'm over^t aire %
I can't be depfessed forever
just because \failed
one audition
Now know Vm a Jousy
dancer, butigot to
befriends ith uka
and Ju to
I see... o your best
f he children are
rooting for you.
Old you see Akira
Klo, I didn't.
Hey!
Akira! You're going
to be late
Akira!
What are you doing?
You're going to be late
I'm leaving!
I'm leavirtg^iow
Hitoms?
Good morning
What's wrong?
Akira was touching
his hair.
Anyone touches their hair .
That is... if they have hair
It just seems unusual
1 wonder if he found
a girlfriend?
Wait a minute!
I didn't notice
any signs..
i- The other day, there was a
girl standing out front,
and staring at thetiame
plate outside otir house
-She looked Jike sr.? might
be in middle sc.iool .
Maybe it's her
% "Tsukishima South
Middle School
Shimada.. ?
Shima .
Sano..
Shimada Naoko
oodmor fng
ere. Thanks.
You^eadihem already?
That was re lly fast
Ill bring you more
Sano...
What is it?
The other day when I was
out walking, I just
happened to go by
yoiW house.
There were a lot of different last
names on the nameplate
Are you living
with relatives?
I'm
a foster child
Foster child?
My father and siblings aren|
my real father or siblings.
But they're like a
real family to me
Can I bme tffer
to your h lise*
Midterms are coming up soon
I'd like to shoyv*ne
how to do ome of the
math problems that
I don't understan .
What about today?
Tiere are days when I have
to help out, but i tlay
I don't have to..
Realty? I'll comedy
in the Evening
I'll see you then
Akira s at fh \ a*ge n
o e6 What's wrong with
having girlfriend or two
must be quite popular
ter wooing in Tsukiji, he
seems to have n lured .a bit
Girls don't ifliss that
ir r
-Fiitiitr irt ruiix^*
Really? Then hemust
be really popular
It's okay for Akira...
But the problem
is y d y
The way he's acting
at his age.
What ^happened with Yu TTff^
his cite with Mari when
the ent to Kamakura?
JitOii
I don't a to talk
about tl^at.
■He's head over heels..
Actu lly, he's
beyon that
This s great
srf t?
If you of tSnTiere,
you won't ver lose it.
Thank ou
I don't know/iow you fin
jchic things like this
I'll put it in ight away
What did she give you?
It's a " hakin-bukuro' tea
To h pouch)
You put money in it.
InKamakura. there's shrine
called "Z niarai Benten"
Shrinetcoin-washinq enten
jj ))i oil j11x • j v lu^l^
there, mbney js p.jose
to^accum ate
So we went th and e each
^ashe ive-yen coins, but
if we put it in our wallets, we
igfit nd it by mistake.
So Man ought these, so we
can put ur five-yen coins
inside,(and k ^p'it as
a good-luck charm
That way we won't lose it.
TheSe were u ight, so
b light wodiffere t
colored ones for us.
So we*have atn ing pair "
of" Ticikin-bukuro."
lia e some sfioppin o o
I'll see you later. Vu.
Goodbye
Thank you
Matching "chakin. '
o nds like you ha
fjn in Kamakura.
e sure i .
Wh on't the wo
0 • u • • i
Never niirrcJ J<a Pleura a.rear! /
•I've had eno gh of it.
Don't be je ous.
Why-don^ou otoa
kyabakura" (babaretxiub)
p goto-a-^ abakura,"
nd I'll {jo to ama ra
iveme*a break!
) 1
Junkol^Good morning.
oH-morning
What's wrong? You have
"T> spirit
How could I have any?
We failed the audition.
It's in the past now
•Maybe it was a mista e
to pair up with yoi
Why did I tell you
I'd dance with you?
D6nt say that now
hat&jgomg n
Good morning
KEN is giving lessons o the
nes who passed dition
Let me see..
The kids from the pother
schools are here, too.
HesTeally strict
e s totally different from
when you're talking to him
You can come inside,
and watch..
It'll be a good
lesson for you
Sha!l we try dancing once?
i s essonfor he apinq
itomi w ^rea.ly surprised by ..
TJie difficult f their
Sjiovements, the^vay
their bodies o ed,*he
uniformity and the high
degree of perfection th§t
was expected of you during
the professional level lesson.
rid it made her
mp tient..
It's n \ at all
what I waht
You have b listen to thf*
music more close! .
Once more.
That's all for o a
Thank you
Good work, Kyok6, Chisato
and Kuriko.
I know it's hard, but we re
going to start my lesSon now
We'll start m five minutes.
I'll see .you a e .
KEN'
he iso mackerel was
delicious.
iease come again.
I have a chance..
as atching our l"¥son
t as a esome..
It ade me mpatient.
can tell you is
o iry your bes .
I will
ee oU>
se etting impatient.
When you et impatient,
o art o *Weat.
The wSat will come
ri ing down,
wettin he floor, and
ing ou slip and fall.
I carfj help but
inpatient.
If I don't keep up, the
ap ill keep growing,
n i ' I Fleft behind.
Excuse me
Yes.
I'm a classmate of£ano from
Tsukishima Southed iddle
ch ... My name is
mphada Naoko
Is that rig V
I'm lira's fitter
l'rv pleased to meet you.
a/hat can we do
for you today?
r midte ms are coming up
soon, b I came to have
ano ifIp me with my mat i.
Is that right?
Hitomi..
Just a minute..
She's the girl that was looking
at the nameplate the other day
It's just as thought
It's his girlfriend
I'm sorry
Will you call Akira?
What am I sayina?
Akiraf You have a visitor
Come .on
I 'm sorry the house
i mess.
^This is Yuri "Sna Sh la .
Akira s ounger^iblings
Hello.
ImHitomi.,.
M saw y to out f'&ntlhe
other day, didn't ?
hat's right.
Hello..
Shimada.
Sano...
Come on up.
If you'll ex use me.
Go ri§ht ahead.
Hitorhi.
id yoirtiear frm?
Come on up.'
Atura las a girffrien ..
SheVs really cute
■et's serve tea.
Shall wetnake
English tea?
H^l-take-out cookies.
Let's go, add
rfeckMv)ut.
This hardly happ Yis...
I'll take this to them
Hitomi..
Leave the door open...
The door..
We don't want anything
to hap; ^fTi
m netting
i feel like a mother who's
meeting JierjsJi^Jirst
girlfriend, or^omething
ike that.
Take it before
it gets cold.
Hey! Go away
Yes?
I'm coming in
I rOjght you
some tea.
III serve it.
^hank you.
Thank you
Naoko'S .appearance has brought
a little excitementlo the
Ipjpongi family.