CHAPTER 14
Mother Shows Up
Episode 81
So after taking it
under consideration,
we decided that she is
now qualified
to take Shota in
and raise him
I understand how
you feel, but
I want you to think
about Shota
Shota's mother is finally
able to make an
environment where she can
raise Shota properly
Excuse me, but
I'm leaving.
Hitomi!
I'll go affer her
It's okay...
I'll make her
understand
Vm sf>rry s le as
snr • yj
I'm sorry.
No, it's all right
I can understand how
Hitomi feels.
Tak gi!
Even if her living situation
has changed, she totally
abandoned Shota for more
than two years. I have
doubts about her love
for him as a mother
When a child e raised
rovide wha sista "te
■ Tit ¥ssar , if the
parent no lo or needs our
assistance, then we should
7?
Or
t we
live to I hem.
When you consider the
foster parent's feelings...
What we have to do now
is to accept how Hitomi
and Katsutaro feel.
ir^ra, srtitt?
That's how l^feel every
sc. nothing 4 ike
I I
Have you calmed down yet?
How can I?
How can I agree
with this?
After all the care you
put into raising him
You're hopeless
Don't look like that in
front of the children
I know, but
I have to take Shota to the
child care counseling
center tomorrow
You should ask Shota if
he wants to see his
mother mot.
After all, you're
his father.
Do you think Shota will
be honest with me
if I ask him?
He'll worry about hurting
my feelings and he'll
absolutely refuse
to see her
The best thing is for
someone at the child
care counseling center
to ask him.
What is a foster
parent anyway?
It's too heartbreaking
That night, they had dinner
just like any other night
Is that right?
So you thought when they
said 'typho ikka," they
meant a typhoon family?
They didn't mean a family,
they meant that the
typhoon was passing
through
That's righit. After all,
kka" means family
So t ha a moihe
nd a h
And children, loo
That would be terrible
ley ould io e
o ses wa
Wouldn't they Hitomi?
That's right.
Hitomi didn't really
feel like laughing.
I'm going up. Shota
Wait for me
Good night, Hitomi.
Good night.
Shota.
I have to talk with you.
Will you come with me
to the childcare
counseling center tomorrow?
Will Akira come, too?
What about Yuria?
No, just you.
So after school, don't
stop anywhere, but
come straight home
hi'ji *
I think he'll say he does
want to see her.
Why would he want
to see her after
she abandoned him
all this time?
Don't say that in front
of the children
I know
But I feel sorry
for Shota.
Being subjected to
this all for
an adult's selfish reasons.
I'm going to take Shota
by myself tomorrow
Why? I'm going, too
With that attitude, ave
Yio ioea wnit yoL' I ay
at the center
I'll be fine. I'm worried
about what will happen
look at that!
What are you doing?
My eyeglass case!
DJj
What's wrong
with her
n £ acting strange
The miso mackerel
is ready
Here's your miso mackerel
large bowl medium serving
with extra pickled
vegetables
r having medium bowl
large serving with feg
nd extra pickled
vegetables
But I'll take it.
Hitomi! That's mine!
I'm sorry
Wheres my stew?
jJjHi JLOii
beeftoftP
Give me an egg that's as
big as an ostrich egg
Can you change my miso
mackerel large bowl
medium serving to stew medium
bowl large serving?
Adults are so selfish.
What's wrong, Hitomi?
Don't take it out
on everybody
I'm sorry! I heard all
of your orders
So don't worry about it
What's wrong? you've
been acting strange all morning
i making mistakes on orders
and dropping bowls..
We're dine here, so why don't
you leave early today?
In fact, I insist on it
You're throwing the whole
place into confusion.
I'm sorry.
It's Shota's mother.
She shows up now and
she wants to
take Shota back
When did Shota come to
live in Tsukishima?
He was in the third term
of the first grade
before that, he was in an
orphanage, and was
going to a school nearby
How did he end up in
the orphanage?
It was really terrible
She brought him to the
child care counseling
center, and told them she
couldn't raise him anymore
and she wanted them
to take him in
It's a pure case of
child abandonment
She worked at nights, and
she never fixed his meals,
so Shota used to eat raw
n ant ramen noodles
But why did she suddenly
come back now?
She's getting married.
She said their income will
be stable, and she'll
be psychologically stable
enough to raise him
properly this time.
But shouldn't
you be glad?
After all, Shota will be
able to live with
his real mother
Are you taking his
mother's side?
I'm not taking her side,
but there must have
been circumstances that kept
her from raising him.
If her life was unstable,
then leaving Shota at
the child care center might
have been the right thing
But she didn't even contact
him in all that time
Normally, a mother
would do that?
She should have been worried
about whether Shota was
well or not
Doesn't it mean that she
doesnt have any love
for him as a mother?
You can't just say that
without reservation
Why?
She's his mother after
all, she wants to take
him back, and there isn't
a mother who doesn't
love her child
Even if that's true, then
it hasn't gotten across
to Shota at all
I wonder about that
What if it were you, and
I left you with someone
for two or three years when
you were his age?
Would you hate me?
In the end, Hitomi
didn't go to the
child care counseling
center after all
Let's take a break
Go over the parts where
you're not confident
Hitomi.
Is something wrong?
Your movements are
careless
If you're not careful
you'll get hurt
I'm sorry
I'm home
Where's Dad?
He took Shota to
see Mr. Wakayama.
at the child care
counseling center.
m i t?
I don't know
I have crackers for you
Go and wash your hands
he ~ olull
o on gy
Chil care counseling center
Is that you, Shota?
That's so co 1
What time did you go to
sleep last night?
AM 30..
B
Did you dream?
What did you dream
about yesterday?
Baseball.
So you love baseball
Then, do you dream about
your mother, Shota?
Do you remember
your mother?
Not much
Do you want
to see her?
I'm sorry
rd to £it
s ill. isn't it?
I keep wondering what
Shota will say.
Have one.
Thank you
Your mother called us.
She wants to see you.
She's sorry she didn't
call you before now
What shall we do?
Do you want
to see her?
Katsutaro fend..
Hitomi were worried about
what Shota's answer
would be.