APTER 13
The "Birth of ROSE MARY"
^Episode 78
lar s y*\ - 5
It's rosemary perfume,
and aroma
»1fs a present fror*
me and Mart
rm ^appy...
Thank you'
ou orked r "ally tiard
so just relax.
We jrp rooting for you
feoyou'll doline
You'll do fine!
Just fine!
What time does it^tarl?
hota and he thers
ill com , o .
■see
f,pnlyi could iiave^een
rlieisedfrom e pital
ust.a wee., a tier
o-how do ou hi*
-you'll o..
hen y 1! carry fe ^portable
shrineif you'reYiot in
Srmon . no matter what
y ^u do, t's uarari eed
>thatH won't o smoothly
fiu're i ^larrfioft^, it'll T>ve
&nd down so smoothly
What m ^n y harmony is
that ^ch p rson carrying
thrthrine trusts
ec&h other
^rs Used to compl le
trust in each ther
if th Tre'p eve person
you caTitjrust. then no
fitter fiow "STTI you try,
the shrine wonljgo up.
k. if thfc ™ is weak
^a d small, »as long as he
Ishows that e as thfe
spirit, youyfeel that.
nd it gives youl e
spirit to do
That's how everyone fe s
so ^hen itromes time
to lift the shrine tha
feeling flows inside you
and the shrine g fes
up sifioothly.
and the shrine goes
up smoothly
No matter how many tim
I experience that
it's still something
I can't explain
U ^t make sure you trust
eth other, £nd ma te
ure everyone Joists you
That's nat it means to
carry « port tie shrine.
«s what it me n o
carry a portable "hfine.
Do your best'
3 JoVJ jL\
The c >ite 1 IS
about\o ^fin
jLk
Good ornmg'
Hitorfii
Good morning
Will you li len
for a minute?
I've got it done patf
Are you eally
sure abotit that?
I'm really, really,
really sure
is this the place?
It's chic, isn't it?
Do y come here
often, Yuzo?
Pf course
I'm a city bo
Everybody!
Hitomif
You came?
Look at this, Hitomi!
ROSE M ttY
e re rpo ing or you
Do your best! Win that
500,000 yen!
\1onja" is jKingl
J nib' iP- /i
ie ll do % est!
;7e re going to win it!
Tory and dante are summer^
special attractions
The £007 Summer Dance ontest,
Natsu Con" is about to begin!
Summer!
ur first ry s a group
"tj^ir led OSHIDASrilir
ive the s a hand!
$ ¥500000
Is that hip
Hop...
Put it together, and
it's hip hop!
Eilry numlfer five..
FLASHSTREET BOY'
Entry number n ne
YUMI AND CHI^JOl
Give hem^fiand.
Thank f>d!|
Let's co. to lie..
Ne t^ve^iave entry
number-IB1
The^came^ll the way
from Oscika..
BLUE SHOES! Give
them a ha* d!
BLUE SHOES
That was entry number 13...
B <JE SHOEs!
6i\^hem a hbnd.
I'm getting so nervous!
Why am I so nervou *?
Because you're determined..
That's why you re
so nervous
Hitomi! Are you sure vou ve
got t down pat?
I'm sure. I practiced
this morning, too
TTtet me.
What ^sis^o^ejiave
to trust in Hitomi?
Shes$1na!e-rinded
ppongi)
Th >i yft&t basis do we
have to \r jst in Junko?
Her^Jetermin 1k Tito
rise upin the W rid.
Thenyfcftjba Is do we
have u"trust in Yuka^s
Ihat^fo admit it
b*1 she's go W.
Thenwr^S ^sfe do we
havelo Trust in Moe?
Her bility to soothe
your soul..
W ^tjbaSi"tilo we^iave
o trust in us?
We're all different
but we're together
it's r§ lly fate,
jsn'tjf?
Isn't it?
Wh 1's t! at?
Rose ^r -tragratice.tr
! feeMike we
Iiri do it
We ca i!
Thank you, everyone!
s continue
Next is fttry number 25
From Tsu ishima, the "monja"
town, w fiave ROSE MARY!
£ive them a hand!
ROSEMARY
That was wfcsome!
The audience ff ally
got into it, tooT
fteally?
Hit mi... really
did haveit down pat!
You did it, Hitomi!
You always surprise me'
Tjiank you.
This unit is the best!
I want to go on forever
together like this.
That's all foY the
individual awards...
il that eitj \he
anno n m lilt ^fthe
winnin 4t~arfi.
l*Tite>n ill ilhe
00 000 iz nd
the lame that goes
with it ?
This is h inning team 1
/r
This is the in Incgteam
of the 20 Natsli Con."
It £ entry num or 5
JROSE MARVI
gjtican't be helped, Kazu.
We're not on our
home jround.
i nkyou!
mmer of 2007 is
len BE TCYliaH
heir m 1ft of glor
-And th? beginning o
attle^hairm - azi
her team.