HITOMI
CHAPTER 7
"Let's Be Friends"
Episode 37
Raising Akira, Yuria and Shota
has something to do with me.
I'm going to
quit dancing.
Doing both is you,
isn't it?
Be presumptuous, and
keep dancing.
It's finished.
The point is how to find the
time for you to dance.
With this, you won't have
to overdo it, and you can
manage to keep on
dancing, can't you?
Don't cry, Hitomi!
April, 2007
In order to give Hitomi time to dance,
the children had divided up the housework.
Listen carefully, Shota.
Don't think of it as
something you don't
want to do because
it's housework.
It's our duty...
In other words,
it's our mission.
Answer me by saying,
"roger".
Say it.
Roger!
All right.
Let's go.
Good morning, Hitomi.
Good morning.
What are you all
doing here?
We're here because...
it's our mission.
Your morning mission...
Everybody will hang
the laundry.
Roger!
Next, Shota.
Roger...
Mornings became even more
efficient than before.
This is next, Shota
Roger!
Roger...
It's really a great help to have
them helping out like this.
That's how much they all
want you to keep dancing.
Aren't you lucky? You can
go back to dancing again.
I owe it all to
the children.
That's true, but don't you also
owe it to that teacher, RAY, too?
She came down here just to
give you encouragement.
Dancing and taking care
of the children are
what make you Ippongi Hitomi...
Isn't what she said?
I'll have to find some
way to thank RAY for that.
Hello!
I came to talk to Yu today.
Me?
The Sunday after
next Sunday...
In other words, will you be free
the week after next Sunday, Yu?
I'm free... It's our day
off, so I'm totally free.
What is it?
If you're free, shall we go
somewhere faraway (toude)?
"Toude”?
If you flip it around, it comes
out to "detou" (date).
Sure, it's okay. Let's go on a
"detou" somewhere faraway (toude)...
I'm so glad you're free.
Actually, my fortune said if
I go somewhere faraway on
that Sunday, something
good will happen.
Will you think of where we can go?
I'll think about it, too.
Ok, I'll think about it.
I'll stay up all night,
and think about it.
We'll talk out
it later then.
Let's do that.
See you!
Goodbye!
Thank you!
Flip it around, and
it means "date"?
That's mine, Dad!
RAY!
What is it?
Thank you for coming all the way to
my part-time job to talk to me.
Thanks to you, I found the spirit
to come back to dancing again.
It's okay.
Is that all?
It's not much as a
token of apology, but...
Please continue to teach
me from now on.
There's going to be
an audition...
The alumni from this class,
d-Darts are going to make
a promotion video.
And they're looking for
background dancers.
Quiet down, everyone.
So they've notified dance
schools throughout Tokyo,
and asked them to recommend
20 dancers from each school.
And HIPZ has decided to
recommend this whole class.
Hashimoto Junko
Kitagawa Yuka
Calm down.
Don't be too happy...
You're just being recommended...
You haven't been chosen yet.
They're looking for an
original dance to the
beat of the d-Darts'
debut song.
It can be a solo or a group.
The deciding battle
will be next Friday.
The place will be
Club BROCKS.
It'll be like a battle
between schools.
I want you all to uphold
the reputation of HIPZ,
and do your best.
This is a first chance
for all of you, and
I think it'll be a
good experience.
I won't complain...
Come up with your own ideas
to choreograph your dance.
Today, one of the judges
is here to greet you.
Those of you who attended
the d-Darts' debut event
last month have already
met him, but this is
KEN, one of my old
dance partners.
He'll be in charge of
choreographing the promotion video.
I'm looking forward to
seeing what you can do.
I think it's awesome that KEN is
going to be one of the judges.
I'm all fired up.
What is it?
I found this picture
on the Internet.
I knew that KEN and RAY used
to dance as a unit, but this
is the first time I've seen
a picture of them.
The legendary dance
unit, CHEAPASS...
They never came out on
television, but they
were really popular
at the dance clubs.
They were both really
young, weren't they?
It was seven years ago...
RAY was 18, and
KEN was 23.
Who is this?
That's EIJI... He was a
really close friend of KEN,
but he died in a motorcycle
accident three years ago.
So CHEAPASS broke up, and
Ken went to New York alone.
Everyone thought that
he wouldn't come back.
Is that what happened?
That's why it's so awesome.
He not only came back, but
he's going to be a judge
for the background dancers.
I'll have to do my best with
a person like that as a judge.
That's right.
Pass the audition, and become
the talk of the town, Hitomi.
So who are you going
to dance with?
You're not planning to
go solo, are you?
That's the problem...
Kyoko, and those two have
formed their own unit...
Yoshiki and his unit have no intention
of including a girl in their unit.
There's only...
Those two...?
That's just it.
How about it? Want
to dance with me?
Will you dance
with me?
I have a plan.
Shall we go, and
have tea?
Let's go.
I'm coming!
Our first goal is to win
the audition, of course.
I could do that
alone, but..
I have a vision
beyond that.
And that's... a major debut.
A major debut?
Our goal is to appeal to KEN and
the producer of the record company.
The way to do that
is to stand out.
That's where you come in.
You're really tall.
You'll make a great weapon
when it comes to impact.
I'm a weapon?
And besides, you'll emphasize
my adorable and sharp appeal.
Was she praising me?
Nevermind! If you can
pair up with Junko,
it'll be a chance for you.
That's right... If you
audition by yourself,
you don't know if
you'll win, do you?
But if you dance with me,
you're sure to win
the audition, so why not?
That's right... You'll be
the talk of the town.
I see...
I'll be the talk of
the town, won't I?
AII right.
I'll do it, Junko.
Let's work together.
Okay! We'll start
practicing tomorrow.
Why are you here?
Watch your finger...
I'm home!
You're early today,
aren't you?
I was just talking
to my friends today.
We're going to be
auditioning.
That's great
You have to chop
the garlic, Akira.
Roger!
Are the children preparing
dinner all by themselves?
They said they
would do it.
They said they can do it if
they have the cookbook,
so I'm just supposed to sit
here, and read the newspaper.
What are we going to do if
it doesn't taste good?
No matter how it tastes,
when you eat it, just
say "it's delicious!"
So you just want me
to flatter them.
Don't call it flattery.
We can't fail this mission.
Do you understand?
Stir-fry the meat and the
garlic for 20 seconds,
then put the vegetables
in right away.
Roger!
Let's do it
Shota... the minced meat!
One... two... three... four...
five... six... seven... eight...
It's ready!
This looks delicious.
It's fried rice with stir-fried
vegetables in a gravy sauce.
Yuria was the one who
suggested that we
try to cook the dinner.
So you can practice your
dancing even more.
Thank you!
Thank you...!
Will you do this everyday?
Don't get carried away.
That's your job.
This is just once
in a while.
You're right.
Let's eat.
You cut the vegetables
really nicely.
It's delicious!
I didn't have to
use flattery.
Were you just going
to flatter us?
Hitomi!
Guidance in education.
It's delicious.
Sapporo
So, you're going to
an audition?
Aren't you lucky that the
children are helping you?
After dinner, they even
helped with the ironing.
I guess it's okay then.
As long as the children
are on your side...
Just do your best.
If you collapse doing
what you love to do,
I won't complain.
I'll do my best.
Hitomi's first challenge
is about to begin.