c hpter 16
Goodbye Shota"
Epis He 93
<£6*3* J
Written by.
SUZUKI Satoshi
JVIusic By.
YAMASHITA Kosuke
_Wa aya
{
"Engli Ti Su title By
fiippbn go "t>hn network
If you can orgiveme,
ill ou come, and
live with me ori
lie island?
Let's put an e ^ to this
loneliness already
M the two pf you come,
and live with me. P
Sing hotawith you.
After talking a Jong time,
Mikiejagreed to her
father's suggestion
The two of them went to the
^thild care counse ing e er,
and explained the
situation.
I'm very sorjy for all the
troubl lhat Mikie caused
After hearing wra hey
proposed to^io,
c lid care counseling center
"decided to check if it
would be an enviro merit
suitable for Shota
They m^ticuloiis!y€fiecVe"Q
ifito «osiiio'« Income nil
"Hidings Viditions.
AncUiad m Yiy discussions
And once they came to a
decision, Mr. Wakayama
and the other? ent to
see thelppongi family.
i ie' ath 's income
s ery stable, and
the li trig c Editions
e the best
Toshio as never remarried,
so lives £lone in a
single-family home
nd here's a grade
scnool pearby too.
But on i j<no w if Shota
woj d agree to it, or not.
6f ourse, e intend to put
Shota's opinion hrst
He might feel lonely if
he'£ going to be so far
away from this house.
That's true.
I .talk Jo hffta, and
ti g*
If he'/S agreeable, then
we'll have Shota me 1
with his grandfather at
the center once
All /ight.
We re counting on
your cooperation
So we were woraenng what
you thougH of living in
Izu 0$ Ima with yourvmother
and Toshio, y Ur grandfather
Your mother las agreed
to it, so we want to
know hovt you feel t)out it.
What do you hink, hota9
It's up to you... It hasn t
"been decided et
Either way is fine with us.
Juk tell us what
you think, Shota.
usF hink it over
very carefully
I don t care where we go
as long as J'ntoge{her
with my mom
As long as you're with
your mother .you don't
care where you go9
As long as I'm ith my jmom,
anywhere fin ith me.
Ifujht... QUell your
motffer that then.
ere you go
Thanks
Shota's moth t made a
good decision
It's probably the best
lace in the world
that she c^h live
without worry
It s good for fehota and
his mother
That's probably true
What is she oingto
do about work?
She ll find so thing through
one of their relatives
Is thft right?
%ut e s really going
Are you feeling lonely9
0?€0 rse!
It's across he ocean..
What are you saying9
You can get there in less than
two hours on the boat jiow
it's closer than Osaka
But.
Shotas going away.
It's okay for you
to cry here, but
be sure you smile
in front of Shota
i&hota's.. going to
Anko Tsubaki"
J-ie said hexlbeSn'ttar^
where he goes as long
s he s with liis mother
It's enough
make you cry
Katsu
It makes f %ad that
he's g ing toliave
to .arfwith Shota.
You must e feeling like
the fati^r of the bride.
{Even-though you kno^he's
leaving... You know that
it's for.Shota's sake, Vid even
though you're happy.
It^till makes you sad.
Katsu.
You did a fine jdb of
raising Shota
Thank you
I'm so sad
^t s thetlay when Shota
ill me 1 Toshio.
|1 poJ, j'if
e ea'ly^/oYVed
ai\, i n t'ie.
es?
Jh nk on for waiting
Mom!
I>n sorry A haven bep
ableto^ee you, ho a
ere you lonely9
o.. I wasn't lonely
bee use I knew t was
going to see you.
fi „ lold you about your
<grandpa. didn t they9
He's here now
e came to see you.
an I call him in7
Are you Shota?
I'm your grandpa.
Yes9 Come in
Excuse mfe
How is it going9
t's going well.
As soon as he $w Toshio's
face, Shota smiled
They're drawing pictures
together right now
They are? I'm glad.
It s a relief, isn t it?
It s great, isn't it?
What are they drawing9
Baseball.
After the first meeting,
he three of them met
a number o times.
hota' Dad1
unch is ready
It's flood
i s e icious
Is it?
When a foster child leaves
is foster home,-and goes
back to live with is rpal
arent,-it'6 called
temporary measi re
y-rtx jxmjiHh/jjj)
ariousan e ,
argjcouiTSeling e. ie
hav a e in
^re arationsfo? hota
>Jj)] fcjjjv
Sochi kayo
ih-Wl rt jilt
Shoia ill - iving wifh
s mer Saito Mikie
II t IUIII. I lidlltt UU
or jetting u n
t/Vhten*vi!l le e^ in
e discussed it with Mikie,
but how do £ December 26th
souhd to you9
Its h a terthe ast
day of class at rade *bx>l
That's not even
a month away
I don't see why .not..
It's good timing.
We waited to ask you...
Shota s grandfather Toshio
is really grateful to you,
and he really vants to
meet with you directly
If it's o ay with you,
could you come to the
center on§ day soon.7
I see .. If that's
hatji ants...
I anted to meet Shota'
g ^dfath once, too
He wants you -o come,
too, Hitomi
All riglUHIt) le.e.
Thank-you
The countdown to the day
Shota leaves as started
a
IT osuke
J- 7, J— frk <* Together
j y ^
OfBcT> n^^J-tz^h
« t niii
n±i -fz mt
)\j\l;:„(Ha'ppv
(Lucky!)
US Oancing!)
215 (Dancing!)
Sffio (Dancing!)
a^uivj
) JO) -Y frhj Together
zfj > > !
have fun'