CHAPTER 17
Dance is Life
Episode 99
Written by
SUZUKI Satoshi
Music by
YAMASHITA Kosuke
MIT
English Subtitle by
NIPPON GOLDEN NETWORK
Hitomi and Junko were in
Utsunomiya to visit
Junko's mother who had been
in an automobile accident.
Don't say that..
Just think about
getting better
Aren't you glad that all
you have to do is stay
in bed to get better?
I wonder if it was the
traffic safety amulet
that we got at New Year's
that worked
It didn't work! That's why
I phlli
You're right
I brought her
This is Hitomi, the friend
I just told you about.
Thank you for coming all
the way here.
Dont move! You're
making me sore
Please don't get up.
I'm sorry...
I'm glad it wasn't
serious.
I just have to stay
in the hospital for
about two weeks
Is that right?
Dad bought tea
I bought bean jam cakes,
and rice balls, too
You're going to spend the
night here, aren't you?
You can have
a late night snack.
Thanks
Didn't •.'<)« .;ar to
work overtime?
At a time like this, I have
to do my job as the eldest
son since my little sister is
too busy with her dancing
I'd better be going.
e IngJiome?
Are the trains
still running?
No, please stay
e ad f We TTt
go home this late
e ake hfcr on
he axi. Keiichi.
Please stay
OK... I'll take you up
on your kind offer
Hashimoto Gyoza
The name of our restaurant
has our last name in it,
doesn't it?
When I was in grade school,
there was a mean boy who
to T< my-name, Hashimoto
Junko, and he erased
-*he-3Hh" from my name, and
turned it into "gyoza"
Hashimoto Gyoza
Things like that happened
but I have to admit that
our gyoza are delicious
There are a lot of places
with delicious gyoza,
but I like ours the best
Everything is
made by hand
My dad wakes up when it's
still dark, and he starts
by making the wrappers
He had someone helping
him, but he said his
work was sloppy, so
he fired him
He's a real craftsman,
isn't he?
That's right,
He's stubborn.
When I quit my job as an
office clerk to go to
Tokyo, we had a big fight
He told me, "Are you
planning to become
a dancer or some
such nonsense?"
But now he
41 3.JVJ
Ill I f
The gyoza keep
us connected
As long as I eat gyoza,
I'm still his daughter
Junko... Won't you come here
and have some beer?
You, too, Hitomi
Is it OK?
Shall we make gyoza?
Do we have any?
Yes, we do!
Really?
We have all the ingredients.
Give me a hand.
S t 1(3
Is it OK?
Why not?
Shall we make some?
Really?
This feels good.
Be sure it's
saning up
OK...is this OK?
It'll pass
Hand me a plate, please
This is great!
Here you go
What's going to happen if
you appear on Dance Beat?
It's not that anything
will happen, but it's
the goal of all the
dancers in Japan
Will you earn a lot
of money if you do?
Not really
It s like the "Koshien"
high school baseball
championship... You don't
work hard for the money
It's not like the "Koshien"
If you win the Koshien,
everyone will say how
great you are
But no one knows what
Dance Beat is
Even if you won, it wouldn't
be anything to brag about
around here, would it
I'm not doing it so I can
brag to the neighbors
It might be OK for you
You're doing it for your
own self-satisfaction,
but you're putting
Mom in a bind
When the neighbors ask
what happened to you
since you went to Tokyo
She can't say anything
If you could at least come
out on TV
When are you going to
appear on TV?
I don't know
Hurry and make an appearance
even if it's just as a
background dancer
You're putting us in an
embarrassing position.
It has nothing to do
with you, does it?
Of course it does
All you've ever done is
make the family worry
When she was in high school,
she went astray and
went around with some ladies
motorcycle gang
Going out with some
weird characters..
You'd look like this
or like this
Mom and Dad cried and
begged her to at least
find a decent full time
job, so she found a job
as an office clerk.
Everyone was so
relieved
Then she suddenly decided
she wanted to go to Tokyo,
and become a dancer
What was that anyway?
Ever since I was little,
I loved watching
dancers on television.
She's always talking
nonsense like that!
What's going to happen
to this restaurant?
The way Dad and Mom are
now, they can't go on
like this much longer.
They'll have no choice
but to lose it
Dad must be so frustrated
that the business that
his parents handed down
to him wont go any
further than his
generation...
Wait a minute, why do you
make it sound as if it
has nothing to
do with you?
Aren't you the one who's
supposed to be thinking
about what happens
to this shop?
Are you telling me
to take it over?
You're the eldest
son, aren t you?
You take it over
versinc ot a job at
hefcan , bad thought
\ rott
ere going to
a*e over e business
don't know anything
about that
V\/h hy fi were in high school,
Ve 'hde'y W help him make
the gyoza wrappers
as a part-time job
Dad was training you!
And trying to straighten
you out at the same time.
He thought you'd eventually
marry someone from around
here and take over
the business
You're trampling all over
his hopes
But he supports Junko in
what she's doing now
Every so often, ver
to Junko's place to eat
the gyoza that he
sends to her.
He's just trying to make
sure Junko doesn't forget
about gyoza completely
He's trying to tell you
to come home someday
and make the gyoza
in his place
I wonder about that..
You wouidn't understand.
Even Junko doesn't
realize it
What I said earlier..
I wasn't kidding!
Mom's really worried
about you
About Dad and about
the restaurant, too
Are you telling me
to quit dancing?
It's a lot easier than
my quitting the bank!
The bank may be important
to you, but dancing is
just as important to me!
Society doesn't
see it that way
The bank is 1 ."bo times
more important than
your dancing!
It's no use talking
to you!
Junko!
Let her be.
To be honest, I have no idea
what she wants to do!
Do you?
In any case, dancing is fun
Putting aside things like
making money, becoming
famous or coming out on
TV, it's a way
that you can express
yourself, an
You can do that by going to
sing at a "karaoke" room
I'm trying to tell you
it's not like that!
I don't understand
you either
I have no idea what goes
on in the minds of
people who are dancers
Junko?
Why does my brother have
to say things like that
about me anyway?
I do think about the
business and I'm
worried about my parents,
too, but I wanted to
go to Tokyo
I wanted to see how
far I could go
Is it impossible?
Junko.
Hitomi is good at looking
after people, isn't she?
She went all the way to her
friend's family home.
When she gets it in her
head to do something,
she just does it.
I guess you could say it's
a bad habit of hers.
but it's a good thing
Being there for
her friend
That's the beauty
of youth
It sends chills up my spine**
when you talk about youth.
I can see the moid
jgf wing on it
Running around for the
sake of a friend
They really are the days of
her youth, aren't they?
Aren't they? I'd like to
go back to that time
Me, too
Excuse me
Come back over here
Come back from
e oast
He didn't have to say
those things to you
He's too selfish.
Putting all the responsibility
on your shoulders like that.
He's just getting
carried away.
Just because he got a job at
the bank, and has a beautiful
wife, he thinks he's
something else.
He doesn't understand...
You shouldn't let what
he says bother you
But I'm already 21
It may be too late for me
to make a debut.
I wonder if my mom is
that worried about me
If I don't take it over,
they'll have to shut
down this restaurant,
won't they?
Good night.
Is that right? You ate
our gyoza before?
Wher'eve lTjoo/er
I ate
I 'm IWay scorned If she's
After all gyoza is a
completely nutritious food
It has vegetables, garlic
i ler nqr Clients
<s we l-i) danced
t omes in h Yicty
Thank you
If her friends are eating
too, we better send
a whole box
It won't fit in
my refrigerator
When you got into
the accident
/hat s t
Was it because you e
ui yio aujo
Of course not
Are you sure?
Then were you worrying
the business?
Thinking that Keiihi and
o take over f Y you?
You don't have to
worry about it
^ a such a nice day
as n a
fiat' t is.
Don't worry about it, and
just do your best
for dancing.
That's right
After all, you have such
a good friend like Hitomi
Doesn't she
It makes it even harder
for me when they say
things like that
Since they're giving you
their support, let's
do our best to get
into Dance Beat
In any case, I'm not going
to dance class today.
But if we go back to Tokyo
now, we can make it in time.
I'm just not in the
mood to dance.
I'm wondering if I should
even be doing this
Don't say the same
thing as Yuka
Forgive me if I don't say
anything on the train back.
Junko...