CHAPTER 9
"I'm Getting Married"
Episode 49
Looking for dance
performers...
It's on a Sunday afternoon
so it couldn't be anything
dangerous, could it?
It must be some kind
of event.
I wasn't going to tell you about
going to the amusement park...
I'm sorry.
He's my only father.
The father who abandoned
me never existed.
Your father had his reasons
for leaving you...
And I want you to become
a kind person who can
understand those reasons.
May 2017
We're leaving!
Akira!
What happened, with Naoko?
You mean Shimada?
She lent me some
books again.
Did you make up?
I wrote a letter
to apologize.
I told her I was sorry
I yelled at her.
And what happened?
She apologized, too.
She said she was sorry
she ignored my feelings.
She did?
Isn't that great?
You'll get to be even
better friends now.
I'm leaving!
My phone...?
It's Mom...
Momoko? What does she want
so early in the morning?
Do you want to
answer?
Of course not!
I don't have anything
to say to Momoko.
Unlike Akira, you haven't made
any progress, have you?
Never mind! Just hurry,
and answer the phone.
I'm going to water the plants.
Good morning, Mom.
Hitomi? I just got to work.
No... I'm at the Suzuran
Cosmetic branch office.
We just moved in today.
It's in a building in Ginza.
It's just one floor.
I'm going to be working in Tokyo
as the assistant branch manager.
You're going to live here?
Watch out!
Stop that!
Hello? Hitomi?
Is that right? Momoko's
coming here?
Where is she going to live?
In Kamiya-cho... she's renting a
condo that the company pays for.
So you can see her
everyday now.
You should let bygones be
bygones, and try to get
along with Momoko, Katsu.
That's right. We can invite her
over for dinner once in
a while, and we can
all eat together.
Don't be ridiculous!
I have high blood pressure.
Momoko living in Tokyo means
shortening my lifespan.
How stubborn!
Ms. Ippongi...
Have some coffee.
Thank you.
Are you settled in yet?
More or less. How about on your side?
Do you have enough help?
We're fine.
The lay-out may change a
little, but you can come,
and take look this evening.
Ms. Ippongi!
Your business cards are ready.
Assistant branch manager...?
Sounds important, doesn't it?
It means you have a heavy responsibility,
You're going to make Suzuran
Cosmetics that was only
known in Hokkaido, a brand
name throughout Japan.
We're going to sell it to all
the department stores
in Tokyo, so be prepared.
So Momoko's the assistant
branch manager...?
She must have worked
really hard in Sapporo.
So it seems.
She started in sales, and she
must have sold lots and
lots of cosmetics.
It would be nice if she and
Katsu could make up.
That's what Ume said, too.
But Grandpa doesn't seem
to have any intention
of even trying.
By the way, Yu...
Did you and Mari make up yet?
Let's not talk about that anymore.
Sounds suspicious to me.
He hasn't been to "Matsuri" lately.
What happened between the
two of you anyway?
You were getting
along so well.
He won't tell me
even if I ask.
What I think is that he
probably got drunk,
and held her hand.
He took hold of her hand
like this, and said,
"I love you. Mari."
And she told him, "Stop that,"
and slapped his hand.
You idiot!
Don't talk about that anymore!
Why?
You don't have to
yell at me.
I'm eating!
Eat your lunch already!
You don't have to tell me. I'll eat.
He did it, didn't he?
He definitely did it.
No mistake about it.
Dad...?
Keiko! Are you off today?
No... I just got off
from the night shift.
I see...
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
Just something...
I'll tell you after I offer
incense to Mom.
So, Keiko... What is it
you want to talk about?
It's...
I'm, sorry! Can we talk
out in the store?
It might be easier to talk there.
You're right...
Sit over here, Keiko.
So what is it you want
to talk about?
It's...
Wait a minute! I think
i just saw something
really disgusting
walk by here.
I knew it!
Hello!
Hello, Keiko.
Hello.
What did you come here for?
I don't have any
business with you.
I didn't come to see you.
I come to tell Mom...
...that I've been transferred
to Tokyo, and I'll be
living in Tokyo now.
I heard from Hitomi...
Your office is in Ginza, isn't it?
It's really close
to Tsukishima.
i o riea with you
ai gmg^rojnc here
i i Uhreaienthe
j lie afety of the
pie roun here
Jjjy'i tsj iltii
Ingslike that
n ro tof eiko
I'm *5iftgjn
Wait a minute. You didn't submit
ajpermit to come in here.
So y/here do I get th V?
I It's I) ck at your place,
of course!
-Thank you
Keiko... The day of the
funeral was the first
time in 17 years thaftAomoko
came back to Tsukishima.
S thought she wouldn't
come back, but.
She had no qualms about
coming back home
She must really have
nerves of^steei
After what she put her
parents through..
Isn't that enough?
It's all irrthe past!
No, it's not*
haven't forgotten
ner e Niusband, Nagase got
4iimself in over his Jiead
in de , and do you know
What he asked me Jo do?
e ed me to sell the
house and store, so
he could pay off Jiis debt
What do you think
of that?
On top of that, she took
his side, and told me
Just sell the store, Dad
Why don't you just
sell the store? Give Nagase
a chance Once we pay off
"the debt, we'll make
a orofit"
gt's unbelie able'
^ou really re a
alicious p frson
If you'fcant to bring th \
up, t on I haven't
forgot fen what you
told me either...
CarryingHitomi,ivho
was still this little.
You told merTm
disowning y W
Do *t ever set foot in
thsh use again'"
That's why i couldn't come
home until the 'uneral.
Momo
dako
Are you fighting again?
You're scaring off
the customers.
They won't come
in here now
hy do you have to fight
when Keiko's here?
That's right
Keiko should hear this, s5
tie doesn't make the cime
mistake with a man!
Besides, Momoko, you're
a bad judge of men
Will you listen
to this, Keiko?
Her ex husband, Nagase
was so flashy
He started some kind of event
company in Roppongi
He told me because of the
bubble economy ^he was
going to be flood ~d
with business.
And fie was going to make
ifijch
so mucn money
I hatemen like that!
That's enough already.
I'm leaving.
! shouldn't have come.
I was transferred, and
I'll be working in
our branch "office
in Ginza
That's close by!
you should come
here for lunch
I'd like to come and
eat your "monja,"
but 1 won't come near
this house again
I'm sorry about that.
N *t at<ail.
I'm not t Ikin' to ou
I'm t Ikingio Kelko
Tfie nuisance is gone
What a relief!
Sorry V^eep you
waiting, Keiko
^a k o me^about?
ever mind.
Hhink T be e go, (oo
You on eto o
What's t?
It doesn't have
to be today
I'll come back again soon
doo^Jby*
What's jSith jier anyway?
She came here because she
want U to talk tb me
lie just g 1 off from
he night jshift,
and came over
After a fight like that
^anybody would have
a hard time saying
^anything to you
o i think so?
0 jcourse
What? You had a fight
with randpa again?
I had some time, so I thought
I'd stop , and at
«whSt happens...? Oontyou
think fe should have been
alittle happy that J 41 be
living close by now?
I'm 3ure he's actually
ha|ppy about it.
1 don't know about that.
Of course he is.
Atter all, You're
his au^hter!
Living in that house,
J /ealize that even
though Akira, Yuria and
Shota a. §n't really
his children, they're
like a real family
You're his real daughter,
so I don't know why
you £an't get along better.
Keiko came to talk to me
when Momoko suddenly
showed up here.
Keiko was so surprised
hat she went home
without saying anything
That's because you and M fn
started fighting, isn't it?
Why can't the two of you be
more civil to each other?
I'm not fighting with her
because Twant to
it's just that jvhen i see
Momokos face, alt the
fcnger froVn the past just
comes flooding back
Excuse me! I'd like
to buy a^shirt
Isn't it strange?
Wheft rm srttin e
store, I don't get a
single customer, but &s
soon i come in here,
they come in. What
is it anyway?
I'm coming!
My -iiorie!
Its Keiko.
Hello!
Hitomi?
Is Dad near y?
No...- He's in the
store right now.
Act ally; I nee to talk to
yo <3bout something
I went to Tsukishima to
todayf but I couldn't bring
myself jo tell him.
Actually, there's someone
I want you to meet.
Don't ell me..
It's your bo Triend
I think you could siy he's
a little more than ust
a boyfriend..
Do you meaft
you're getting m Tried?
I guess 4hat s"what
I'm trying to say.
Can you come out tonight?
i tdl i 5ui c tdl u
I'll meet you at ROSE
at about eight
I won't tell Dad .
I mean.1 won't
teil Grandpa.
I'll see you later.
Was that Momoko?
No.. A friend.
A friend?
What shall I make
for dinner tonight?
A friend? You mean Yuka?
Keiko is gointf to introduce
tier to her fiance
What is he tike?