CHAPTER 14
Mother Shows Up
Episode 79
This is the winning team
T> "t 2007 "N isu C n
It's entry number 25.
ROSE MARY
We did it!
It can't be helped, Kazu
We're not on our
home ground
Let's go
Kazu
Today is the anniversary
of my brother's death
I can't forgive you
We did it!
Congratulations, Hitomi!
Congratulations?
You made me cry
You really worked
hard, didn't you?
V u really did
Y ll., <0 t< at how
good you've gotten
Hitomi
What do you think
J)J*?J"
Hi doing it in
lace o Katsil
Hitomi?
Not you, too, Ume
You were good today
You made a
good unit
Thank you
But u don 't know what
will happen tomorrow
A not is a
living thing
Wh t'STicjht today is
differeni^rom what
may tfe right t morrow
2007'fle?"B
eptember, 2007
2007^9^
lt'£<Se tember arid
Katsutaro will be
coming home from
the hospital
There he is!
Welcome home
Thank you
Were you all waiting?
Shota wanted to
give this to him
Here
I made this
What is it?
What could it be?
What's this?
Complete recovery
Is thistrie?
Thank you... Thank you.
I'm so glad
Katsu
Welcome home
I'm home!
f«n home!
Thank you so much
I'm sorry to worry
all of you
That night
They had a ceiebration to
thank the people who had
helped out while Katsutaro
was in the hospital, and
to celebrate Katsutaro's
release from the hospital
You're making
too much noise
The whole town
can hear you.
Here you go!
Thank you!
It's about time
Do your thing
Everybody!
I'd like to thank you
all again
ROSE MARY won the
dance contest
Thank you!
Qot my share of
Ihe prize money
So I have presents for
Grandpa and the children
Thank you!
Congratulations on your
release from the hospital
It's a mini bonsai tree
Thank you
Akira, do your best on
your entrance exams.
A^harppen!
Thank you!
A cake cookbook
for you, Yuria
Thank you!
Make us cakes!
Here's an official professional
baseball for you, Shota
Thank you!
It's used in professional
baseball games
It's like presents from your
first salary, isn't it?
It's the first time she won
for her dancing
Thank you so much!
OK everybody..Let's
all thank Hitomi again.
tfd j>ei
Thank you very much
You're welcome
Give them a hand!
Good evening
Momoko, over here
You made it
I |[dt frr^ork
done early
You didn't have to
try so hard just
for my sake
I didn't come for you
I came to see everyone
w? W t» •
Come and sit down
What was all the
applause for?
Hitomi bought presents for
Katsu and the children
with the prize money
that she won
v M X ttftlgoti
-dUg t "Sharpt>en.
I got a professional
baseball
How nice. Why didn't you
get me anything?
I'm your mother
You're so petty, Momoko!
Is that all you can think of?
Getting something for yourself
jJittiiD* »
/Jft'ii J;>yo» 4)
Wh ley i) were in ^
hospitcl everyone
here did so much for you
They deserve some
kind of reward
Wh 1 Jiave you
grt rtthenfc
Nothing... It has to
come from the heart.
Who cares about that
Give somet
I want something, too
Why should I give
you anything!
I helped at the store,
and sold two shirts
You don't have to make it
sound like such a feat
Just because you
sold two shirts
That's enough already
This is supposed to
be a celebration
Got that?
By the middle of September
Katsutaro's leg had
completely healed
We're leaving!
I'm leaving, too
They're so full
of energy
Miso mackerel
is ready
Thank you for waiting
Miso mackerel, large bowl
medium serving with
extra pickled vegetables
Thank you.
I'm starving
I've gained so
much weight
You're getting
nice and plump
Wait a minute!
I'm sorry to worry
all of you..
My grandpa recovered
completely, and is
home from the hospital.
Thank you for
everything
Now you can do your best
without worrying about
anything, can't you?
h ri you!
Itwasrou li n 11 of
you, loo, wasn't it?
lAteVe Known ea 1i ther
fo a lonq time so
was expected
We j u T\iaveto to ea ti
other o t whenever
anything happens
Thank you so much,
everybody
From now on, I'll do my
best at work, dancing,
and at home again
The roses are beautiful
Are you sure
it's OK?
' tib. rItrdbe dC ,1
It's from all of us
Thank you tot ell
you've done
In that case
Thank you!
So what are you going
to do now...?
Dance Beat!
Wasn't that yourjjoaP
Are you going to j&fiter
it as a unit or
We're going to talk about
that now
Can 11II you
what f wish 7
I want you to do it
Because of your name
ROSE MARY
I felt as though Mari
and I, and everyone
else are all out
there with you
Hurry and decide
I'll leave the studio
open for you
HJ better putt is
in a vase
What liatlwedo?
I want to do it
After all. wew Yi
There's no reason
why we should quit
What about you, Yuka?
I thought about
giving it a try
Then let's do it
The level is different
this time
There's a big contest on
a national level that's
held every year for
street dancers
Dance Beat is one of those
nationwide contests
that Hitomi and the
others are aiming for
It's a big event that's
equal to the Koshien
high school baseball
tournament where
only the best of the best
units can win
He p eliminanes will
Bin March to we
ti vb five months
L T«do our best so
we can make it
INh i ut you, Junko?
I think I want to
give it a try
It makes me happy
that we won
I'm happy, too that
we won but what
makes me even happier is
that we had fun dancing
together up on the stage
When we danced the Matsuri
Mambo, it was the heated
atmosphere of a festival,
but up on the tage, we
all did our best and
had fun dancing.
Let's aimtotrec
perfect unit like
IRAY a ^ KEl3,i0 ^
• • t 1 I ^ ijfj
It smells so nice
Did you decide?
We just decided
Let's do it
Considering the
circumstances
Thank you!
I'm so happy!
Before you change your
minds, let's seal the
deal by putting our
hands together
Ready
ROSE MARY will come
together as one.
and aim for this
year's Dance Beat
Put our hands
together
Do your best
all of you!
We will!
I'll be routing
for you
Just a minute
have*oi>e
car t£fl %re
Hello Ippongi
CI thing Tore..
Mr. Wakayama! Hello!
How is your leg?
It is? I'm glad
I put non-slip rubber on
all of the stairs in
m el retiow, Isoth Tit
won't happen again.
ms try to iv >ryyou
Thank you very much
Whatdidy foe 11
• OUi • •
Actually it's
about Shota
What about Shota?
We were suddenly contacted
by Shota's real mother
For the past two years
we couldn't reach her
At all, so it'st>eeri
a problem for us...
According to his mother
circumstances have
changed quite a bit so she
wants to take Shota back
I pee.. Shota s m ther
wants Sh tafoa
We're home Dad!
I got a hundred
on my math test
That's great!
This is really great
Congratulations
f at was great
You worked hard,
didn't you?
Go, and put your
b bags down
Sorry to keep
you waiting
Shota just came home
What do you want
us to do?
We'd like to go over
the details with you
so can you come to
ie cen or scon
Alright I'll bring
Hitomi down with me
tomorrow then
I'll see you
tomorrow
Goodbye
Hitomi had no idea that
this sudden announcement
would cause problems