HAPTER 11
Summer Withoit'tBrandpa"
"Episode 65
rui/^A,©^ <ii/»sj (65)
After having too much to
drink at Rose s bar
Momoko spent the night
at the Ippongi home.
What happened?
It's late, so vtfh on't you
spend the rig \< here?
Maybe should
You scared me.
Cheers!
Do you remeffiber what
you said earlier?
What you said at
Rose's j)lace.
I can't remember at all
What did 1 say?
You said you ran off to
get married, teft Jiome
and threw everything away,
but you don't regret jt
J may have exaggerated
it d little
There s one thing
I regret
Is it about Grandma?
I made her sad until
t ^{Jay shetfied
She was cau Tht between
me and Dad... And
I wish she could have
seen more of you
But! can't do anything
about it anymore.
You can do something
a ou ii now
Just make up with Grandpa
! think that would make
Grandma happy
It's not that easy.
Why not?
You both just have to be
honest with each other
If I did that, I would wonder
why I made Mom so sad
for over 20 years
1 think Dad feels
the same way.
it's going to take time
to melt the ice ^hat s
been building up
for 20 years
Hitomi
Look the other way...
I'm going to cry
Get sticky.. Get stickier
and stickier
I'll bet you'r Arprised that
I'm still here enl you?
You can't avoid me
I'mgoin 'totryto
get alo ith you
Otherwise, won't be a 1e
to help out here, will P
rmxomingtoatk
again tonight
eat!
Break's over
This time, I'll have you
dance ne by one
If you don't try som n
neW, you won't be e
m Ve on to the nex e
Let's start with Hit
While she darihed, Mo ^>ko's
words ke ing through
Hit >n!'s head
it's your life
Decide what you want to
do with your dancing
iJJlJ IJUimi) >
sh a e ling erto
find what she wanted to
do ith h V life
That's pretty heavy
Even when she's drunk.
your mom says some
profound things,
doesn't she?
She's more profound
when she's drunk.
She normally doesn't
say things like that
So what are you
going to do?
J don't know but I thought
i d start som thing.
Like what?
That's why... I'll start
something that shows
hat I'm moving ahead
This is it! TJie summer
fiance \:onte£t
I'm going to get t^
500,000 yen prize
I'm go ng to talk to
Yuka anh Junko
1 already told you
about
t\lat!
You might as well confess!
I have the proof.
Yuka'
What?
e ou looking
or a fight?
Let's not fight
Do you want to
enter this?
jT he summer dance contest?
We can form jjnit,
and ente is...
I'll be the maf&ger
I don'jt /antlo'
Mot with t Is
selfish girl!
I won'i do it Ither!
Did something Jiappen?
CrabUhefra
Crab! The ra
Crab7
e th chip in for food,
e can co feat home
The standard menu is
gyoz " (potstickersj
The "gyoza" that Junko s
family sends to her
The rest, | try to juggle the
finances by going to
ties ermar et right before
clo ing, so 1 can buy
/egetables at alf price...
But it would be kind of
t)oring if e only
'tJid th tfe decided that
e d splurge once in a while.
wThat's the crab?
hat' rig"Y..
ra
e^te ialf last^veek,
onJ yatft/a
to eat the rest on Sunday.
But she ate fall
by tierself!
You ate it, didn't you?
if was you. wasn't it?
dmitlt! You ate it!
I saw that!
It was you!
Why did you do that?
When! was alone in the
apartment I started
to feel miserable
tTf Jiavrany money, and
here's 410 gx tement.
So I thought I'd just
eat it all up'
You're just a little #
rich gir, afterall.
u can't live wi
^iout
being extravagant
It's your fault for
be so unrefined!
"What^
Do you know fthat she does.
She w Iks around the place, j
munching on rice crkckerS
So the Whole place is covere
with crac or crumbs!
It ~icikes me feel even \
more miserable
o noticejthe crumbs,
hen lean it up'
o t want to
otice it'
Calm own
L t's not fight over
silly hinjgs.
MitO
Look at this'1
Let's go for
the usto!
Why are you so
/ired up9
hy are ou o
ired
It's been four months
since v fe tar e
taking lessons
And we're so ca g pp
< with school, ourjobs
f and problems at ome that f
we haven't found our
own dance jet
think that's why you
feel so miserable.
u tiaven't one anything
ye , o you're starting
et impatient.
To be honesJTffi g Iting
inpatient too
warit o eToh
*t)ance Beat but
tfiaven't thoug 1 fbout what
I want to do fter that.
Do I want to e famous?
£)cri want to be rich?
Is it okay>qs i iig as
I'm haviSg fun^
1 doriTknow the
answer yet
In any case * ant to
/Start something, and
1 pi looking for.
t his ate, ear
/e ven realizeit.
So e o this.
r ut I can't get
hlo hat today
ry. I pass, too
Vuka!
it's not just he crab..
Tfiose two jusTBon't get
%ng with each other
e »
I asked RAY if ,cari
practice here nee
in a while
Is that righ 9
People just don' ge
along to begin with.
If you talk,\rou end
up fighting
Maybe we dance to com ey what
e can't depress in Worc^s.
Just believe inlt...
Believe in dancing.
ou'll find your true friends
through dancing.
Try dancing together.
etlsigorMcif*
itomi! JA/h Ts wrong?
Yuka! Junko!
Yufca! Junko!
Just believe in dancing..
All e ave to
do is ance
What is she yelling a ouf?
How embarrassin .
I'm not going to give up
until you two agree to it
o hurry, and m 1<e p^
with each other'
See yo
What's with her?
She's fired jjp,
isn't she?
That night
Akira.. W^i is it°
there's Hitomi?
She on b return some
fflsi ies to me
Is something wrong?
Shota seems to
-have a fever.
You're rig OVpu*have
a little 1tt>ffl fever
Did you ^tclmcold?
That's wh 1 you get Tor
leavinq y vr stomach
exposed when -you took a
nap in me auernoon.
Let's o ^nd
c^llflitonu
It'll probably go
up some more
The doctor's office
is dosed already .
I have some medicine.
I'll go, and get it.
I won't drink
your medicine
Why nffi? Why*Jo
you say that?
Because...
You're 0 H's enemjf
aren't you?
Sf ota's rejection was
unexpected