CHAPTER 11
Summer Without Grandpa
Episode 66
Was it a summer cold?
Shota had a fever
The doctor's office
is closed already
I have some medicine
I'll go and get it
I won't take
your medicine
Why not? Why do
you say that?
Because
You're Dad's enemy
aren't you?
You're Dad's enemy.
I'm not his enemy
I'm his daughter
Then why do you
fight with Dad?
I'm going to Dad
Dad's in the hospital.
Then I'm going to Mom.
You can't do that, Shota!
You have a fever
Come back
What are you doing
down here, Shota?
You need to be back
in bed upstairs
He wants to stay by Mom.
Put your head
down slowly.
Are you in pain?
A little
Can you stand it?
If you can't stand it,
call me right away
Don't hold back
Don't force yourself. If I
have to, I'll carry you to
the hospital
It's ready
What did you make?
Special cold medicine
OK, ready to try it, Shota?
I won't drink
your medicine
He thinks she's
an enemy
Because she doesn't
get along with Dad
It seems that way.
fiU^^SXlij
sn ht?
But Shota, my medicine is
also Mom's medicine
What do you mean?
I learned how to make it
from Mom over there..
She used to make it for me
when I got sick
when I was little.
You made it for me, too,
didn't you, Mom?
Can I taste that?
I recognize this scent
It has ginger in it,
right?
Mom made it for me before
You're right, I remember
having this too
Shota, this is Mom's medicine!
You finally felt like
tasting it, huh?
Just try and
taste one mouthful
It's Mom's flavor.
She was a really
nice mom.
I'm sure she was to you all too
She was nice
When Dad got made at us,
she'd comfort us
Hitomi, did you know her?
She came to see me once
in Sapporo
I've seen Mom
crying
Me, too.
Where?
In the kitchen..
When I came home in the
evening, she was
crying in the kitchen.
Was it because Aunty and
Dad didn't get along?
She might have wanted
to see Hitomi.
Mom...
I'm sorry
I feel really bad about Mom.
It's the only
thing I regret
It's OK... what is it?
Why did you and Dad fight?
Hitomi's dad asked Dad to
sell this house and
lend him the money.
Dad thought that was outrageous
and got angry.
What did you do?
I was his wife, so I asked
Dad to lend us the money
But wasn't that
in the past?
That was when Hitomi
was three years old
But Dad hasn't gotten
over his feelings
from the past
You all better go to bed
It's late
Ok, Goodnight.
Good night.
Ah, Aunty.
Thank you for making the
ginger medicine or Shota
Good night.
Hitomi, you go
to bed, too
I'll watch over Shota
Mom...
The next morning..
Are you awake, Shota?
I'm awake.
You are?
Your fever went down!
Your fever went
down, Shota
His fever went down.
The ginger medicine
worked
It went down?
You're right
It did!
Thank you, Aunty
Where are you
going, Shota?
To tell Akira.
He's still sleeping
What a relief
I'm going to sleep
for a while
That kid was pretty heavy
Mom
Thank you, Grandma
Momoko made hot
ginger medicine?
At first Shota didn't
want to drink it, but
after taking one sip
he said, "It's got
Mom's flavor" and he drank
the whole thing
By morning, his fever had
gone down completely
Grandma's hot ginger medicine really
amazing, isn't it?
And so is Mom, too
It's not that Momoko's
so great...
It's the hot ginger
There you go again.
saying spiteful things.
Oh yeah, I brought
you something.
What is it?
Tsukuda Dance music
The festival is already
next week
Even though you'll be here
at least you can hear
the music
Here's the player
Hitomi, will you put it
over there
Thank you
Thanks. Do you know
how to put this in?
Of course
It's too bad, isn't it
Grandpa
Given how much you
love the festival
It's just a minor
festival this year
If it were next year's
real festival, and I
was laid up like this,
I would have to go
even with this leg
Good thing
you broke it this year
I don't think there's a
good or a bad time
for breaking a bone
I brought something, too
This photo.
I made a copy for you ...
Grandma and the kids.
You can look at it when
you're feeling lonely
Thank you
OK, time to head home
Take care of yourself
Thanks so much for the visit
You understand, right?
Just push the button
Just push it, OK
Don't listen to it
Thank you
Great, is it this?
This is it
Setsuko...Momoko made
the hot ginger medicine
you taught her to make.
Momoko did.
The regular town..
turned into a
festival town
It's a minor festival before
the real Tsukuda Festival.
It's the middle of summer
in Tsukishima