Ti VTER 11
Summer Without Grandpa"
Episode 63
Everyone was going to
pitch in to help the
ippongi family while
Katsutaro was gone
It's dangfer* \is, ojust
hi
Bre Wastjs almost
ready ira
UIUJ01U P0Q9
Even Keiko came o he p
when she got off rom
he ght shift.
Good morning,^itomi!
Good morning
Can I help with
something?
Can you do the laun r
I'm leaving!
iter Hitomi e es,gAkira
will help Shota and Yuria
with their homework
It's Makoto's jo o
open the store
Welcome!
ease come in
me watches the store
in the mdrhing
our grandpa
tte's fine, thank vD.
f we can do anything...
just tell us!
You want seconds?
I'll g it
While Hi o i is b|}sy working
at the diner in Tsultiji..
Wh le it "mi is busy wo kin
diner in Tsukiji..
The hungry children c m
home frorrfthe poo.
Do you wan som§
barle^ tea^
kay' Comingri ht p
Today fJ\ar\ brought's fne
food for them to ea , o
e.. I'm so grateful
everyone's helping out.
Yuria nicl^Sh ota are he ng
iM^j^jv'iy
That's great
Everyone s orkin
hard to gl thro i
this while you* e o
Even Momc...
Momoko?
When ook over frfcm Ume
o wal *h the store
Something I'm not
sed to doing
Hello!
Momo.. You came
I promised Hitomi..
only have 30 minu es
bef rte I have to go
out and make sales calls
Even thaf would
be a great help
Hello!
4Q|ike short
sieeve otse...
SV/u-s-eeve. .
They're . ig i. or here.
Feel free to look
through them
How aboul this one?
Isn't it bit flashy?
M 1 at all. * ummer,
so his s LSt ig i .
You think so?
See hbw rt looks
on you...
I suppose so...
Here s the mirror
ookstjood
on you!
You think so?
This might be nice, too
"You cart wear it ntil
t's almost autumn.
Jvhich one should I take?
They both look
C I ijj 1 •
Just like a ce! trnty
I don't which one
to t !<e...
An nliolimeat all,
s sojd two pie
Ywo pieces..
She's /our daughter,
ifter all.
She's something else.
Wh \ are y8u saying?
Just thinking about it,
makes me fee1 sick.
Jyuaaali }
fJUJ
jDbep down inside, he wa
happy that Momo was
helping out at home
hinK so, too
rfeniietear that she
sold o blouses,
he smiled a little bit.
This sa ood chance
o th two to
mafte p i i ach other.
lit e it more
+iitomi...
The surgery is scheduled
for tomorrow
Tomorrow?
Katsutaros physic
condition has improved,
and the doct t h
an opening, too
So it's scheduled to
two in the afternoon.
How long will it take?
JiiiV ^
It's a sim e a 10
to set the bone n his
knee, so t-s ing
All right. I'll be here
All right
et's call Mo ..o... It's
good chance to get her
o come, and see him.
Do you thin
she ll come?
We'll make her*
You're ighty
ha . o c oc
2 p:m.v Branch office e in
It's not going to be
ajor«surgey, s it?
a <s e 'In ...
n 'fifomg to-be
ett i)igsurgei
ecaifte £f Crandpa s
Yid 1§«li!1c f?STo!i8lh',f"
it's goin o e a
ifficult eration.
lim^* jjii J-UP!^ J
number of doctors
JA/hen fieardthat,
I joUov jiit
I ee.. It's goin o
be that diffic
1l/j"h. I o
I should be able to
a"ke't' jr 0 30 .
T^ 1 oulB toe great.
tian^pu'
i ;going or^pur ake..
So don't get the
rpno dea
now th
ill see you lere
itcTm ...
oo .what found
SUMMER DANCE CONTEST 2007 J
SU 1MER DANCE CONTEST 2007 i
su 1MER DANCE CONTEST 2007 I
S MMER DANCE CONTEST 2007 »
SUMMER DANCE CONTEST 2007 i
II
i m
seme hls^i
Mka^ntf unVo
It's imp ^s b e. I'm to
busy thi^ummer
The next day...
Katsutaro's surgery
has already begun.
Even if they said it's
a simple operation,
I'm still worried
So am I.
Mom!
I'm glad you came.
How isjt.gotf»§?
He's still in the
operating ro Hi
Whenlt's over, say a
few nice words to him
It's probably reallf
hard on him.
8 S '
Are you awake?
ha \s for coming
tHe'said he made it
through safely
Mom came, tbo
What are you doing?
bAuii
I said... he surgery
didn't take that long.
Did it hurt?
all.
It was a major operation
with a number of doctors
working on you, wasn't it?
There was only one doctor.
He just opened the knee,
—and seweb it right back
up again... What are you
talking about anyway?
t's probably d's
easiest operation.
Hitomi!
! guess I exagger led
it a little'bit.
I wanted you to come.
Is that what it was?
Don't scare me like that
ou
o worried that
est in le middle of
ing,*and
an ver here
ou keepsaying Mmoo, moo.'
Are u a cow*
Momo was really worried
about /ou, Katsu.
^Vhen she heard ou broke
jiia hliiia
rushin; over, pale
a. w
I was iust surprised,
na sa .
as re surprised
t happ rf
You fell down the stairs?
I can't believe you got
hurt inside the hbuse
Maybe you're getting
senile.
What a hingtosay
Once my knee heals, the
rest of my body is
IHtMiIiil J/^ \
She idn' ean
what - le a
Don' et o
j-iin lyuih lili! I^^JjyKv
Pjjt thepxygen
TSk&ack on.
^You're n 1 even worried
Iboutme, are you?
You ne or camfe to
viSiTVne .
Li only came because
of the surgery.
id you want me^to
cv.me, and visit you.
Jt doesn't matter to me ..
ected you 4o
oie o ..meanywa .
eemn ou just raises
jjV « Oli^i^
(i on't cortie
o fee you again.
ffh ing back to work
Go on back to Wprk
You're busy, aren't you?
What?
Maybe you should take
ihis chance to o e
some weight... From this
angle you loo ike
a raccoon dog nament.
Momf
Why that ittle...!
~Calm down, Mr. Ippongi
I don't mind being called
a raccoon dog, but she
called me an orname T<
Do you believe that?
He's as healthy as a horse'
Ho d make up
s ory like that?
I'm sorry about that
But what a relief I'm glad
to see that he's£11 right.
Here .
What is it?
For your grandpa.
1 forgot to give it him.
Give o m rself
I do J hav time
ere... Take it
Ill 'eave the
est to you
hat a com
licatfeti
air
This is from Mom.
Getjots of sle
II come back again.
I'll see you.
Never mind'
Never mind.9
hat is this anyway?
It& a^towel. oWel.
Neither father nor daughter would
show their true feelings.