CHAPTER 14
Mother Shows Up
Episode 83
I'm home
What? Did you lay out
my bedding
So you could go to
Thank you
BLiJiJ i
I talked to Yuzo and Mari
about Shota
And...?
Yuzo said the same
thing you did
He doesn't want to see the
mother who abandoned him
What about Mari?
Mari said it's not
that simple
No matter what kind of
mother she is, she's
the only mother he has
in this world, so
she's sure he would
want to see her.
After talking to them,
I feel so much better.
They eally listened to
what I had to say
It's good to have friends,
isn't it?
That's right.
It's good to
have friends
Friendship's something
to treasure
Katsu sure has it
rough, doesn't he?
What do you mean?
Did I say something?
You did.
What is he having a
rough time with?
I'm not telling you
Why not?
You're a blabbermouth
What are you saying?
I'm a Tsukiji man
If you tell me not to
tell, I won't tell.
I'll zip my lip
You'll unzip it
right away
Don't talk as if I'm
a cheap wallet
If you're troubled about
something, tell me
We should talk about it
and try to work it out
together... Isn't that how
we do things?
I don't believe
you said that
M\*)et
And besides e re
iaiiici xiiiu pyi i«
If Uncle Katsu talked
to you, and you're
carrying the burden, then
I'll take half of the
burden from you
Twice the happiness, and
half the suffering.
Isn't that what a father
and son is all about?
It's about Shota
What about Shota?
Don't tell anyone..
All right
Promise me?
Akira! Shota!
Good morning
Good morning. Hitomi
I'm leaving!
Akira and Yuria seem
to sense something.
I think so, too
They're very
perceptive.
And Shota seems to be more
cheerful than I expected.
He's trying to pretend that
it's not bothering him
What goes on in a child's
mind is a lot more
complicated than
adults realize
Good morning!
Good morning, Hitomi
Don't break any
bowls today
1M
You saying it
will make me even more
conscious of it!
Here's your miso mackerel
large bowl medium serving
with extra pickled
vegetables
Good morning!
lite J J-Le
jjlJj] ^ IfflDte'
bf
I'm sorry I scolded you
yesterday without even
izin
j vara jonmiDJi
How do you know
about it?
ow (Jo I -kno
ig 1 l tere
Hey
Hey Hitoml
Don't give me a
Did you hear about
Shota from Yujiro?
That's ie ri
isn'tfb
What a problem!
Hey! Will you stop
telling everyone about it?
We don't want the children
to hear about it yet.
I know that!
I'm selective about
who I talk to
Hitomi, just
befr^Ti.
You're not beint selective
about it, are you?
Iin everybody
r n fyou?
Good morning, Hitomi
Yujiro!
You EPhim about
Shota, didn't you?
Everybody knows about it!
You mean you already
unzipped your lips?
But this is something
you want to share
You really are a cheap
wallet, aren't you?
Yujiro..
What?
I just got something
really interesting.
A video...
Isn't it too early in the
morning for that?
Silly! It's not
what you think
lt's an
p erefnxh rgeof
the festi 1ft-so ou
ouldn'feee
Mari's Matsuri Mambo
hen J wastlancing. ?
That's right, you're
in the video, too.
One of our customers
had taken this, so
when I told himdhe'Jet
me b Tro s
di n't s% it. Hurry.
and i Vto ^Efe it
i rial s great
This is nice
If the est
The best in
all Japan
I'm not that good.
I'm talking
about Mari.
But it's high spirited
isn't it?
Even a woman would
fall in love..
Sexy, isn't it?
Add an egg to the orders
of these three
My treat
Really?
This will ! 1<efne fall in
I \e all ovfera ain.
bo ^vanllb
ry again?
Tiall P
7il?J}J3 3 hi iiiUfbj^ ,
n rig ram aritjn
this town sn't there?
What shall I make today?
I want curry..
Okay, I'll make curry
Will you help me?
After we make the curry...
On my way home today
I saw Shota
He kept staring at a
mother and her child
Really?
It's not as simple
as I thought it was
Do you think there are
feelings that he wants
to express, but can't?
He does have feelings he wants
to express, but can't.
It's deep inside
his heart...
And he's carefully
locked it away
So we have to help him
to unlock it
I'm going to
take a bath.
You're going to
take a bath?
It's been awhile
How about if we take
a bath together?
I'll leave the
rest to you
You've grown,
haven't you?
How tall are you now?
I'm 51 inches tall.
Four feet three?
Is t H ighP
Your head got pointed
It's pointed
Close your eyes.
If the soap gets in your
eyes, it'll sting.
Shota?
Do you remember
your mother?
What do you remember
about her?
She used to tell me
stories in bed
She did? What kind
of stories?
Brementown Musicians
Brementown Musicians?
What's the story about?
A dog, a cat, a donkey, and rooster
chase off some robbers
How?
By shouting "Meow! Woof!
Hee haw! Cock-a-doodle-do!"
That would scare the
robbers, wouldn't it?
Boss, & witch lives
inJl^Mouse
I see... Your mother
told you that story?
She's a nice mother
isn't she?
Shota?
Do you want to
see your mother?
I want to see her.
I see, you do?
In that case, let's
go to see her
Look at that,
it's pointed!