PTf R 13
The Birth pf ROSE MARY
Episode 73
O-X(
It's Xh Viddleof August,
atsutarp s ca t has
een emoved. ancl i s ecovery
is Vriing along smoothly
terihe'con fon Miori
ith h V son. he's
life has s Itleft^Jown.
And Hitorffi has formed a
dance unit together
it irikb nd Yiika f ?
n ance ccn e^i i
t..e\ ." o f>timmT
Moe is their manager-and
th 1r jgoahs lo win
the contest.
That's all for
today's lesson
Starting from tomorrow,
we won't have any
lessons for a week.
I'm going ,10 take my
summer vacation.
Are youtjointj somewhere
York...
^/ow! That's gre^t
px those who are oing to
enter the contes , t
time to practic
much as you can
How many of yo a
to enter the con
here are quite a
Jew of you
Do your best, so you can
show some good results
Y 6ne s going
b
nedule
%r ih Wl*
h bou tudio?
lacked ose... He'll let jus
se it in .e i.ornings
Okay, everybody.. What about
an
ie're going o tike otf
f we m Tie 50 ,000 yen,
andtiivide our
t'JI *%eterth n what we
jmakeWrkin art-lime
I'm g ing to take off. too
Letjg practice from
morning till night
Tcay, then... If you
a\fe anything else
nee to do
ell rril no
can't start hat earl j
% he rmn
o ably after nine
Tiythin else...9
I Jiave o visit my grandpa
From nfefotwo
n fh ng...
ike to J avefor
romtitfe...
I h veto fix din fer
or > hildren
W itatnlnute...
Ilhoug 1 you said we'd practice,
from fnormng till night
But I'jlbe bac1K at nine
after I £lean up arid
do the ironing and stuff
T I s so n fficient
\goin J6 make
Xi§ ait o you?
n rmstrft amwork,
5hSts g In to be
it tap oblem
isn it?
/have
lot of
4h ng do
How about this then?
^et sihold a training
iCamp.
Training cairn?
Theft's right
i e re Nl jg Ing to stay
e. -at \ir"Ta %?
While dance sc 04
we'll II live together.
We Jl be prac icing i
Rose> place, so it'll
be convenient h n
it Jl help to make tfr
teamwork fetter,1
bu e n elating out o)
he. ameiice
h.. sort 1 thing..*?.
hfe ha 4*1 h school
e SllleS ^ "fefa
o or t > hey hold
r nn cam s^o^thfr.
That's what I thought!
i s okayjvith me so
JUS
leek /iflf "kira
uria^and Tiota
n suKishima .
Ttol • • •>->!
The children all
agreed to it, too
They look forward to having
my dance friends over
kira's a little bit
embarrassed though
Unlo^al- J
o in lly g 1 the unit
oqe..i that y Ufilftays
re med^ *t)Jt?
ov finally at
i tartingiine
After my friends ran out
on me in Sapporo
This time I'm going to
get my revenge by
gelmjtj into Dance Beat.
'We're going to
quit dancing
You're kidding*
If we get over this, wetan
getpn with our liv S.
it's your life
Decide what you want to
do with your dancing
an belie
n anting
You'll find your rea!
friends in dancing
Do your best.
I'll call you again
Thanks. Good night
So the "gals' are going
to be iSymg over
Why doltel
so excited?
I'd better start
planning
Their dance training camp
started the next day
Good morning
So we'll ^ejiolding our
training camp here
^ftOUf^r
starting today
tarting today
III do my best
to help out
Shall we start preparing
breakfast Ihen?
i brought something
for all of you
Gyoza (potstickers)
from Utsunomiya.
jFjbr breakfast?
e ll have "gyoza"
for dinner
Okay!
This is fun,|sn't it?
It's the first timej've
grilled dried fish
You like this, don'l
you Yuka?
m wing the life 0
a commoner
■She's not a commo "fer V>
it's unusual to her..
.And Vs nice having^
rice in the morning.
10 better not
eat tooYnuch
Shall I take out e
, tckled vegetable .
Gan you do it, J nko
-»No problem! I used tb do
it at home in Utsunomiy^.
Teac us *bw {octanc during
y iir training c p
You want to danced
Me,Too.
You do hat woiild\)e
goo o, e ch you?
What abo ' uge Neko"?
That's od idea!
It's ect for
I r n
They'll teach you...
We'll figure out
a time for it
All right!
Those three are staying
over at Hitomi s place?
That's right.
Starting from today
A training camp (gasshuku)
for "gals" so in other
words, a "GALSshuku"
That's fc good one.
When it comes to girls,
my mind is so sh^rp
that it m^kesmy
head spin
I know. I know
So the three are Junko.
Yuka and Moe.
nc u ing i omi, nere
are four of them
There are one two
three.. four
Founof us, |oo
There are only
three of us.
You counted yourself twice.
You've not as sharp
as youthink.
can call one of my
assmates to make
our of us, and with the
our of them, we can
have a co-ed party
A co-ed party?
That'll be the best
event 1 the summer
Won't it*
This might be your
N, last chance, Makoto.
That's right.
That's the point
Although we're all single,
you have a longer career
as a single man, Makoto.
That's right..
Jt's okay.. I'm not
thinking about getting
married or anything
like that.
So it's okay
Really? Shall we
forgfet it th
Aren't we going
to do it?
Make up yourtnind'
L rg dolt.
-He j/ants to do it.
Good morning
You're Ifhere..
orry to bother yfcu
in the ^n n ng
It's oka y
oupporting young eople
is one of m o "bies
Use it as/Tiiich
as you ike
even have a {lew.mirror
eady/o yen
Thank /od
What about your name?
The name o * our gr tip.
You k bw lik * orr \hing
Musume" or "Something Gals '
That's right! We have
to decide on a name!
t doesn't really
matter does t
Ma l)e "Tsukishima Gals"
Monja Komach '
ljio eyou're not-serious
aboutulonj Xorna i '
a-You sound likeyou could
ar^eslWCfka
It's just thisDne
ime nly a
One timefSfily?
Isn't it?
ut we're forming
a unit.
That's right
A unit to win the 50t),000 ye
in the summer tontest
So e'll only be on stage for
that one time only won't we?
Th Vjsliot a unit.
So-what's a unit
o^you t Tfi?
A group or fellow
members.
In music it would
be a band
-You play music together
II le time Vith
Ve are members.
om tning likefhat.
You struggle together
and build your own
kind of dancing
oday is the beginning
of that
he eginning s hen we
in the 500,000 yen.
i yve lose, th stio
ext tir^e for this unit
You mean you'JI
bre T<*up9
You mean you'll
b eak tip9
^That's right.
That Ao cut and dry
You'r hinking of going
to Dan Beat witn the
three o s,aren't you?
hat would be great
You shcul know that the level
s entirely different
This is Shibuya
club ev
ent..
Dance Seat is where awesome
tdancers rom all over
Japan come together
nl/v but...
And besides, we already
know that Junko and I
are aiming for differe 1
things, so maybe we
sholdrft force ourseive
to work togetf^r...
You're right... We col .d
go for individual awar s.
individual awards?
tiSFs jight *lt fal
thing to^towit ja
>unitrt)ut an aWard O an
tilling ndi i ual
DAJiCE CXDVfTE?« ^O.
¥500.000
TtVatfilining prize f"?
iiShflDi 1
h in ng iz o
iinl 323W3D m
If I'm looking to be
scouted. tfien that
would be better for me
Having quit my job as Ti
offic ^fclerk-Jlhink
Mv a ut time that
I shov^ome results.
could o omejdo-ikfe
dance mov£S/«nd show
them JTiy .charm
ike this.
V \Go to some talent scho i
jand do h t
utely refu
do something ike
We're all going in
different directions
et's all get on
the same page
Fjrst, jV ^feded lo/igure
outth§ir«dari moves, ut
Use msthatJunkoand
Yuka ere determined to
3 •JiW J X
St ¥50o mo
stick t"their own styles
3 >*fj i
Si ¥500,o oo
This is ba ..
Hi ¥500, o
Thils really ad
I think his ould bring
out my individuality.
SI SIL|| )fU I
mo e like me
What about if we t Ice
the whole unit jnto
consideration rnstea
of each individual?
e an do that ater
)(n hungry!
hall* e have lunch?
et's do that.
We' e having somen
no dies, aren't ^e?
That's Tight.
Cold somen noodles ere
great during the summer
t)oks like they can V»ly
agree on when to gb to
eat doesn't it?
9 days to summer contest