vrii 1)
Showdown"
Episode 114
mpomi (114
Written by.
SUZUKI Satoshi
«Music By.
YAMASHITA Kosuke
Th Tokyo prelimin ties for
«*P3nce Beat was/>ver
Hitomi didn't make it.
What are we fcjoing
to do from now?
ROSE MAkY9
i c TTContinue.
Which means 9
Were the judges
really watching?
The other dancers
were really good
Hitomi..
ame-as scho 1
entrance exams.
ssin score is
95 points, isn't \V>
So evp.i if you got a 95 i)u*
a lot of people scored 96
or higner, you may not pass
since there's only a limited
num fspaces
for each school
That's right..
Gooc: evening*
Mom1
~Hitomi! Htoroug t
your favorite cake
Thank y&u!
What a feast!
Party" for Hitomi.
*<Ul9you care
to jIj)
Is it okay?
All jght1 I' e made
jLfOJ
om. ?
/lorn.. 7
Ditf yotfgo out of your
in a totiuylhis
TJ^nk you
Wh 1 a re you saying?
HoWsyour ankle?
Nowt ^t it's over, it's
£t Ttifig lo hurt
Hitomi
tie's takin it/tetter
ex ed
I'm so glad.
HowTinusual to see
oulwoti Te
1twas>iot today, so
colild us ^a-drink.
It's the excitement from
hfe «dlntr"~ ntest
HoWxibOUl a£eer then?
oufids good
hank vou
How's Hitomi?
-SheStaking it "a *ot
better than I expected
.She talked quite a bit
during dinner tod
I'm gldd to
Miear that
ere..
Thanks
How was it at "Matsuri"?
The "Monjayaki Brothers"
were there.
Since they went to cheer
you on at the dance
contest, they closed
the "monja" shop
Mako and Hiroshi both said
they thought your dancing
was really good.
It was really cool
They did?
So what are you going to
do about ROSE MARY*
We broke up.
Junko promised her brother
that she d take over
their family business
She has to keep
her promise
That's right
After we finished dancing,
I really felt great
Because gave it everything
I had, and I felt like
We had all become one
So I have no
egrets at all
There are times when you
score a 95, but you get
beaten by those who
scored a 96
Just like y li said
Junko has to Quit dancing,
and go bade \6 erfamify
home nUts\inomiya
When I think about that,
I wonder if there wasn't
something more I could do,
or maybe
My dancing was lousy,
after all
ft just m tie me think
f eV ral da^s l let
Let s start our lesson...
Several days later, RAY was
giving her final lesson for
her year-long class.
Since her ankle wasn't
completely healed yet
Hitomi was playing it safe,
and just w tching today
RAY's final lesson ^vas
the game as glways
As if to say that dancing
was like going to s ho f
or Working at a job,was
elimination of the little
hmej^you do day by day.
Ac ualiy we have one
m re announcement
to make io alt of you
This is not just RAY s
-final class, but as of
today, she is leaving
this dance ^chool.
As itStight this class,
I learned a lot from
all of you, so n that
sense, I was Iso ne
of the students \
Jhiss voT
I love dancing, so I'll
continue d Tiring.
But I want to think about
ho r going to continue
Just tike all of you who have
finished this lass today,
I want to find my oWn path.
Thank vou.
et's meet again
! heard... You didn't
make it to the finals
But was thanks to you
at we were able to
et this far, Rose
Wi limit you, there wouldn't
a ROSE MARY
You don't have to flatter
me like that.
So>e<Hike to show you our
appreciation with this
Thank you very much'
Thank you1
Dance is love1
It's not whether you
won or
losf
What's important is w "ether
oti all burned up your soul.
How about it*
Did you give Spark
o your
Yes, we did1
from h Ye, .unko?
I'm going to Utsunomiva
from h€Fe, and talk|o
them about *he restaurant,
then I'll c me back h4^
and move out of my
^apartment.
Maybe I'll go, and live
with my parents.
I could live alone, but
it would be a waste
to pay rent
That 5 a good idea
Since it seems like your
dad wants to make up
with you, too
And ext year, maybe Moe will
Co out on Dance Beat
It's possible
hy/lonj y u try?
I impossible. No wa 1
See ou'
Take care!
ee you again'
Yuka! Junko! Moe'
Thank you1
^ jijH
I'm home
I'm home1
What are you doing?
It doesn't look like
I'll get any customers,
so I was going to
close up shop.
II help^you
T "links
JPiit that II he
dA/aj inside
was *alkin ith
Junto's join home to
Utsunomi a, >a s
~^gomg to Jive vith
J • * Jl J11
s fe.. So ever one s
going to a e heir
.pwnpani n ife
Jt'.s a b o
fix i«J
What are you
going to do*
I feel like my
canvas is blank.
So what kind of picture
are you going to paint
on that blank canvas?
ounds like the
rice is ready.