CHAPTER 14
Mother Shows Up
Episode 84
Shota? Do you want
to see your mother?
I want to see her.
You do want
to see her?
I do
All right. Let's go
to see her then.
Good night
Shota..
I heard
You did?
I'll call Mr. Wakayama
tomorrow
We need to tell Akira
and Yuria, too
What's going to
happen now?
Shota and his mother
will meet once, and
if there aren't any
problems, they'll
have a number
of meetings
If Mr. Wakayama and the
others are satisfied
that everything's OK, then
they'll live together
It's sad, isn't it?
We should be happy
He'll be going back
to his mother
to his real parent.
Before we eat, I have
something to say
Actually Shota's mother
contacted the child care
counseling center, and
she wants to see Shota
Shota said it's OK
so he will be
seeing her in the
near future
I don't know what's going
to happen after that, but
Shota will be going to the
child care counseling
center every so often from
now on. So don't worry
That's all I have to say.
Shall we eat?
Eat lots of "natto"
(fermented soy beans)
Is that right? Shota said
wants to see her..
I asked him what he
remembered about his
mother, and he said she used
to tell him stories in bed
I could tell that he
misses her, after all
I understand
We'll make the arrangements
with his mother
We'll let you know the
details later
Thank you
Shall we contact
his mother then?
I guess so
I'll leave that to
you, Ms Inoue
He said he was happy..
Katsutaro said he was
happy t eft Shota
told him how hef It
But I'm sure that's
not all he felt
I'll be able to
see Shota?
Thank you
So I'll be able to live
with Shota again.
We'll go over the details
on that day but..
This is just a step in
preparing for your new
life with Shota
Xi can't live together
after just meeting once
TFII have a number of
meetings before that
ore ildlivin ith
r amily oes
Xoii
bjr^ ins b ^
liijjnlliij niftji i
fn^y-stre e r le
y ee ing e e a im ^
thd Siting he till
he g ith h e
:p ? Tit efore fe ly
The meeting between Mikie
and Shota is the first
step in the preparation
All right. I'll see
you on Saturday then.
Thank you
Goodbye
Can you see him?
On Saturday.
What shall I wear?
You sound like you're
going out on a date
Can't you take off
from work fSda 7
I'm so relieved that
feel like going
out to eat something good.
1 can't! After all. I'm
the manager of the
branch in the Shinjuku
department store.
Manager? It's just a
little booth in the
basement level of the
department store
We sell a lot of
bento boxes
Depending on what day it
is, we sell even more
than the Akasaka restaurant
that my mom runs
Will your mom i e
lot for a weddin 11
I wonder..
I'd better go.
Are you leaving?
Thanks for the meal.
Department store basements
are great, aren't they?
You can sample a
lot of food
After we finish our sales
call, shall we stop by?
How can you be
so carefree?
3*~Bay, we're going
to get the account.
So be prepared
•) • l)Ji!j) •
Suzuran Cosmetics.
I have an appointment with
Department Health oi ita
hosjrm-argfe
! cosmetics.
llriovrausta
mute pie se
is this what you're
looking for?
Thank you very much.
I found it!
Is Imasato in the department
store basement?
Imasato?
It's a Japanese restaurant
in Akasaka
It's quite known
I wonder if he's
the son
It's Saturday, the day
that Shota will be
meeting his mother
Are you leaving
already?
We didn't want to
keep her waiting.
sma? Let's go.
Be careful
Akira ahd Yuria.. e
an feye on the hoQy?
Have fun, Shota.
I'm going now
We're leaving.
Thanks, Ume.
Don't worry
It's "ankoro mochi" nc e
wrapped in bean jam ,
I already opened it, but
one is enough for me
so you can have
the rest.
Thank you!
Thank you...
Shall we 4eave some
Let's eat.
Thank you
Let's give one
to Mom first.
His mother is here.
She is?
Inoue is talking
to her right now.
She's supposed to meet
with Shota after that
I hate to ask this, but
could you wait here
until the meeting is over?
Normally, the real parent
and the foster parent
don't have much
interaction
i e to avoid any
problem between them.
It won't be long now
When you see her, greet
her cheerfully.
Yes?
Shota. Your mother
is here.
Shota?
"PIOUQ
i his reunions ,tiId cause
uite a stir In the
Ippongi family