Trying too Hard to Find Happiness
Episode 57
Hitomi?
Keiko!
What are you doing here?
We came to see the orphanage as part of our training.
I was raised here... before I went to live in Tsukishima.
Oh, really!
This is one of our graduates.
I looked after her for three years
I'm sorry to intrude
I came here today because I have an announcement...
What is it?
I'm getting married
Really?
Congratulations!
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
We have three different dormitory buildings
Lined up here
There are about 60 childcare facilities
like the one that Keiko was raised in
There are approximately 3,000 children living
in facilities
fieyv aising l ren whoYGUso e nor
UtllCI 4 4JC Jdlbtiu tiy theirowrTfarllies.
There are about 100 children currently living here in
this facility
Of those 00 children, Ihere e children
living m tns dormitory fiey re ivided into
our group of eight
The youngest is in the first grade, and the
oldest is in the sixth grade
There ree staff members caring for
the eight children.
They treat them like their own children
I'll take you inside now
Hello!
This s h i jn o
They eat me Is fe , o .) j) J .MilJ
This is wherethe Ti!l?r n Jb> Oil J iillJ b ij'i!) JbU
You can o at the bath ove e, too.
If you have any questions, don't hesitate to ask.
a c If there are two t ren in each room
After they get home from school,
this is where they study and sleep..
They share the dressers.
They decide who shares the room by compatibility
Basically siblings are together in the same room
Of course, we do our best to take care of the children
However, the staff can't be on duty for 24 hours a day
So we can't have the same people who see them off
in the morning, welcome them home in the afternoon.
But when they go to a foster home, the same people who
see them off in the morning will be there to welcome
them home everyday
You'll befi leidfflal with the child q ne
That's why j wan to ask "Tltitju*
the children with a completely normal family environment,
and treat them in a completely normal manner.
These are children who have been raised in an environment
Where they couldn't trust their parents, those
they should have been able to trust the most
so it's hard for them to develop
relationships with other people
The most important thing is for you to show them
that they can trust people, trust adults.
What's the best way to do that?
You all have it right here
That's all I have to say
Thank you
Hitomi... Are you done?
My training is over
Will you come to the playground with me
and talk to Mr. Kubota?
It's my favorite place.
Is it this way?
It was your dream to get married, wasn't it?
I wanted have my own family life as soon
as I could because
I didn't have enough of that in my life
I'm really grateful to you, Kubo-papa
when I came here, I was an unruly child, wasn't I?
It was terrible
You'd run through the halls carrying a mop,
breaking the window glass along the way
Yelling, "I'm going to mymofti," and I had to
after you all the wa j o iinjuku
middle of the night.
But I'm no longer unruly like that.
You used to scold me every single day
At the beginning I hated you.
I eventually understood you scolded me
because you cared about me.
When I realized that, I learned to love you
Dad and Mom in Tsukishima took really
good care of me, too.
They helped me come this far and meet
someone who asked me to marry him.
h & true, that the most important thing is
that you work hard at it
That's why I want to congratulate you
I'm going in to see the director now...
He had visitors earlier
Go ahead
H ¥% \ C '
She's really grown up..
SheTlk^sjf she owns the world.
When she first came here she didn't trust
any adult at all
Is that right?
She must have been lone!y
She was so wild. She didn't open up to any
of the children or adults here
Just look at how she's grown, and now
she's found someone to make a home with
It makes me happy ..
I couldn't be happier
e s^ilce, snlfcfe?
He said he couldn't be
I'm really happy, too
When I went to the staff room,
everyone was so happy for me
For the sake of those people, I have to be happy.
How are things with you and Mr. Katsumata lately?
I haven't heard from him for the last few days.
He should be back from his business trip
by rib v^but.
Ma oeJ sti \ild give him fa I.
Shall we take a walk?
Let's go
Hitomi couldn't bring herself to tell Keiko
that she had seen Mr. Katsumata in Atami
Hello?
Are you home?
Y htji^old?
jfou sho have^nied rite! u) i'Jjj J • • n
don't care if it's messy
r i. with i omi right now, soi'llb nghT^/ithme
You do have a fever, after all.
You're not coughing, are you?
No, but my throat's a little sore
Let me see
It's a little bit red
Just drink this. It's one of the best
medicines on the market
I'll get you some water.
Thanks.
You should stay in bed
I don't know why you have to work
when you stayed home from work
I can't stay in bed
My deadline is tomorrow
Excuse me.
You were on a business trip the other day, weren't you?
On Saturday.
That's right... I had to go to the Kansai area..
Kansai (Kyoto, Osaka)?
That's right.
Did something happen while you were on your business trip?
Why?
For you to get sick like this
I was just worn out, that's all.
Anyway when you finish that, go right to bed!
I'd like to stay with you, but
I'm on the night shift tonight
I'll go to bed as soon as I finish this
Thanks
Shall i make you some rice porridge?
Do you have any eggs?
I should have some in the refrigerator.
Sorry to trouble you
When did you buy this egg?
I think it was the day before I
left for my business trip
I'm sorry I'm such a bad host
Not at all... In fact, I feel like I'm in the way
No, you're not; it's better that you're here
We haven't had time to go out lately so if
you weren't here, she would probably scold me more
Thank you.
Not at all
Hitomi! Sorry to keep you waiting
At least I got him into bed
He really needs a lot of care
I had to work even before I go to the hospital.
What is it?
I have to talk to you about something.
What is it? You look so serious
Can we have tea somewhere?
I have to go to the hospital
i do aye time
We can talk while we walk then
No... It me right here
You have me worried.
Not here
It's a little too close
Just thinking that he's right here
Is it about Mr. Katsumata?
I saw Mr. Katsumata with another woman.
But it could be someone from his company...
They were wearing cotton kimono
and walking arm-in-arm.
Where?
At a hot springs in Atami
I went there on Saturday to dance for a part-time job
But he was on a business trip in the Kansai area
That's right
That's why I thought it was strange.
Did you talk to him?
ixlon \hi he noticed me
It was someone else.
No, it wasn't.
I'm sure it was Mr. Katsumata
But it couldn't be him!
Why would he be in Atami with another woman?
Why don't you ask him?
That's not necessary
Don't be ridiculous!
e n e ray e
It was someone else
I won't believe it.
Don't ever bring it up again!
Keiko..