CHAPTER 7
"Let's Be Friends"
Episode 40
Just try it once... See how the
three of us dance together.
I've reserved a studio to
practice at from today
until the audition.
I'm going to practice
there by myself.
You two do your best.
What are you going to do?
Shall we do it with just
the two of us then?
Since coming to Tokyo, this
will be her first real
audition, and Hitomi is going
to give it all she's got.
I'm home!
You're just in time.
We were just about
to start eating
at this very moment.
Really? Thank you so much for
preparing dinner, everybody.
Also, thank you so much for
letting me do what I want
for the past few days.
Once the auditions is over
tomorrow, I'll go back to
doing what I'm supposed to do.
But if you pass the audition,
you'll be doing the promotion
video, won't you?
I'll just be one of the
background dancers...
If that promotion video
comes out on television,
you'll be on it, too,
won't you?
I might be.
Do your best, Hitomi.
Thank you.
They're all rooting for you.
While we were preparing
dinner tonight, they
all worked hard without
complaining once.
Thank you.
These... auditions depend
a lot on luck, so just
do your best, and don't let
the pressure get to you...
If you get in, it would
be nice... If not...
I'll do my best.
Hitomi!
Yes?
Just the person
I wanted to see...
You have that auction
tomorrow, don't you?
Audition...
So being superstitious,
I thought I'd bring
you something for good
luck, so I got you
some "katsu" (to win)...
It's liver "katsu" (cutlet).
I brought enough for
the children, too.
Thank you!
To thank you for the pot
stew the other night.
It smells good.
May we come in?
Come on in.
Good evening.
Thank you for the pot
stew the other right.
You have that thing tomorrow,
don't you, Hitomi...?
I brought you this.
"Katsuobushi" (dried bonito flakes)?
It's something that we give out
to our special customers.
When you're faced with
a challenge...
It has the character
"katsu" (to win)...
That's awesome!
There are four inside, so
give them to the "gals"
that came the other night.
Especially to Yuka...
Since we said things
that upset her.
All right. I'll give
this to them.
See how worried everyone
is about you, Hitomi...
You'll have to do
your best...
I'll do my best.
I'll call whether
I win or lose.
I'll bet you don't
think you'll lose.
I won't lose.
Thank you!
It's the day of
the audition.
(Club BROCKS)
The people in Tsukishima
are so nice, aren't they?
Giving ns somet Ing
like this.
What good is it going to do
for you to take this
You're not even
auditioning
Don't say that
I'll be dancing^it ^
you in spirit
Yuka's here
Yuka!
i know thereof been a
lot between us. but
,et's do our best To|<ay?
Katsuobus V
What is this?
You know that dimwit named
Yu Id who vasjiaying pot
steW^vith usjat the house
He felt
bad about what
he did to you. so
he wanted me to give
you this.
See? It says "katsu.'
For good lu ~k
I'm your enemy..
And you're giving me
katsuobushi'9
Whyn t? It just eans
I want us both to do
best, that'll!.
I don't think that way...
I don't like pretending
to be friends
Who do you think
you are!
Don't waste your power
It's KEN, -iitomi
Hitomi! Appeal
You talked to KEN at the event
the other night, didn't you?
Just for a little bit
fpiat'£ right... You didn't know
who he was. and you
treated him like some ordinary
middle-aged guy didn't you'
I'm sure he remembers you
But what ml going
to say to him?
Say an ytTnng you want
Just get over there*
KEN'
We me "here the other
n'9ht, didn't we?
You're in RAY& class,
aren't you?
Yes. My name is
Hitorm
Ippongi
I'm going to be one of those
auditioning today..
1 won't play favorites..
I'll judge everyone
equally
Thank you all
for waiting!
eA\ art le ditions or
kground
Let me introduce you to
today's main host...
fiw/« joky b ia ut]j
p aye s
n ie ance
cene.
hey/e goingio be maj ?
□a ers in the dance scetie...
ere areihe d-D-a-r t-s,
the d-Darts!
Give them a hand!
1% get in we lljbefla tfng
with them, worTt we^
I in so^xclted!
The audition started..
dUSt Member what you
practiced, and give it
all you've got
Don't think of it as
a test.
just relax1
Understand?
I'm getting nervous.
Maybe you should eat
the katsuobushi.
Isn't that Tor cats?
But since you have it,
eat it for good luck
Shall we eat it?
It tastes like soup base.
tthirk I feel like I'm
going
to win now
Do your be 1.
We will
Next we have entry
number seven.
ere's Yuka from
I
Give hera hand
)q£poi|} f so jsnf s.jtf
she's good
Lets justgo up
there, and
Tiow'Some^artitUOe
Since we ate the
JratsuTnisTi.
That was entry number
seven
from hipz
Giveiier*atiand.
Jt'sbeen a blisteringtiance
battleup n ilnow
Good job
Next, we hatfe entry
number^ight
Iso rom IPZ.
iiiuo)j ue o>iunc
Giv them a hand!
Let's go*
That was entry ^number eight
Ju Mo and Hitomi
from HIPZ
Give them a hand!
Goo o ob
1 made_____istake
It's oka ... You got
St It
j)|JOM p 00
After all of the groups
had a chance to audition.
it's timen&w for the
judges' decision.
I'm going to announce
the winners now...
Entry number four.
ana from
the Aoyama Dance Schoo!!
Come up on stage
Mika and Emi
Congratulations!
udU ynp*
tf>e final
winner today..
The winners from'HIPZ!
She was s ft nervous, she
felt like unning away