TEr!3
The Birth Of ROSE MARY"
Ep!sod# 77
XTJ-i^J
It's KEN
Hey* KEN s over there
Where?
He £ over there on
the Harumi Pier
Where?
You must fce mistaken
£fe sfiot There
That ca
I didn't see
him eitn
jiim either
M «
* /V
School has started again.
The$tu Uteringlhe
jiV/^-lJJ »
"tin heirtn ings.
ve yo getting into
it, e 'rthey?
JS EN.
gain?
This time it's reall^iim.
He's*with RA J
I wonder if she's giving
him atjift from Ne jfork
It's the -O bnomi Gu ^an '{
Yo re igRt.
Did the ometo
fight aviin us?
No.. -S.Vs going
So a EN
The two of you
killed my brother!
ftiliJii/m tn ul»
/JiVl^ 'jJtiL Oi
eali
u jj»iUiir
tftfh £ 1 e aid
t lodksliKfeit has *
something to do
with RAY, too
I'll go, He leek
m ing
'HIS- i • : Jm
e knows ^ut th 1 11,
azu from Osaka.
Who is she*
Up! % ,1's hunger
sister
j'jju'a 3J
Who's EIJP
He was tie of the members of
CHEAPASS with KEN andpRAY.
tie died three years ago.
o t'" rue hafftEN...?
No... He dicln't kil!#iim.
Tit iat's what she think .
-1 li (ell you
i I about it
This is EIJI.
i J s rom Osaka, e c
o Tpkyo when he as 16,
|ind met KEN, who the smw
a , and they fo med
+IEAPASS together RW
sli t with the et
t started off with
st the two of them.
V hen they wire 18, rtiey^/von \
the nationwide itle
n Dance J3eat
ow! That's awe Ibme. v
e re alrea 0
Ever ompeted to tfy
to y their steps
The ere the ultimate
They iiJn't have anyone
wh uld rival them
But tiuess Tokyo wasn t
enougn forihem>s<when
heywete*22, hey
ent to Newark.
They wanted to tove
eventisgher, jso
the/iniined even though
they were-poor
That'^whe fclhey m 1 a 17
year-old girl from Ja^an
1 iit-ii ;b\< t
/ittfi iL U I)
mirae ,ous ^jmer
Three piece of a ic e
f>u tlfejuSf(Tijffto ...ace,
and formed the
perfect urjit.
erfect unit
that was ^
n vCHEAPA S.
When the lueffiftr
tqum lia eturn
o STpk Vthe^udientes went
lid... it was wonderf3l
fld Y's energy A Ih
ultimate combination.
mi theirpower of expression
mere sed many times
The^-had^he ultimate respect
and trust for each the*
That's^.in't take
io ^ ) »UU*>
saw true friends up
there on stage
The newl -forme EAPASS
"Titeie ance eat, cmd
tookthe-GrafTd
fflEftof twGyears Iter
tha rit,wa$"thf g e
erauf S.
After that.. .9
Their stage per^rrtSfices
idn'ttjo smoothly...
Thebalarfceb .ween
heihree was off
nd RAY }<e t i
er and bet er, bu
£|JJ a i3 e
Because of Htsomfl
Y lationshi
That^fes pa
It rriigffi have bee " e
emotional fe in'gs
inv 1 ing
Inanyicase, na^everit
was,*EIJI Variedgo ng
oiiTpri; l^ing e* ery ,ght
hen one-sumrnefr night,
three ye^rs^go,
KEN aiffl$IJIhadabig
fight righ in the
middle of he^fage
afClub BRACKS
I saw it, too .-It was
n^wesome fight.
hat was..
It was the last time that
we sa TEIJI ail /
"fie died in o pie
CCiflTft...
He drove right Ifftbthe
ocean ft his otcfcycle
Wa ic e?
e 6 n't kno
e was
unmista a >y icica
«IMli
TokytFBa
mipe .
EIJI's sister thinks that
it was as if KEN and R. Y
had actually killed him.
KEN and RAY carried the
^pain in their hearts.
After that, the wo em
disappeare r
clubs in Tokyo.
KEN quietly left
for New York...
And RAY ecame
a dance coach.
The;t$o!bf th -ptlt an
^endlo theirfiancm
EIJI's sistet's in o
enter the sumrrfn:oi es
Itieard from Moe.
That day isffteann ers Ty
f Of EIJI s SeatK
I think*she came to tell
KEN and RAY to co e.jnti
atch Tier daiKe
S le wa ^ed o tell them .
a e a respon ibilit
to do that.
You're off, Hitomi.
You're off th e, too.
I'm sorry
We an? win like this
I'm sure tha girJtftazu
is an awesome gancfer.
You keep talking about
forming a nit, but
you're the one who's holding
the unit ck
ito i*6 oing or best
Sto. siding ithhiiom
11 the time Mo%
This isn't some
friendship club
If we lose, there's no
use in continuing
There s no next time
for the tfnil
Shall we do individ
lessons today?
I understand
mhome
Sorry I'm late
Hitomi'
Hurry and come here
Just hurry!
Sit there
We're going io^how you t e
results of iir practice
pkay
it's the "Mayuge e o'
dance!*'
e been waiting
for this
That was great
Yoii
great, Sho a
ou worked hard,
didnt^ou, Shota*
^You practiced a lot,
too,jpidn't you?
e make a pretty good
unit, Qon't we?
You'jre e ly good
Perfect
Hitomi?
Shota,
What's wrong?
ffau can dojt
I know you can.
can do it
I did it.
Thank you
It's two days before
the sufhmer contest