HITOMI
CHAPTER 8
"Two Kinds of Love"
Episode 48
This is my only father.
The father who abandoned
me never existed.
A father like that
isn't a father.
Wait, Akira!
Akira!
Akira! Akira!
What happened?
Sorry about the
commotion...
Akira's hurting..
But there's nothing we can
do to stop the hurt...
Akira!
I'm in better shape
than you are.
Grandpa told me...
...about your father.
It was the first time I ever
went to an amusement park.
When he told me to
wait for him, and
sat me down on the bench in
front of the Ferris wheel,
it was fun at the beginning
because I had ice cream...
But even after I finished all
of it, he didn't come back.
Get up.
You're heavy!
I think...
I kind of understand
how Naoko feels.
About what?
Why she went to the amusement
park, and sat on the bench.
She wanted to feel what
you felt at that time.
Especially if she
cares about you.
I was lonely, too.
It's not even close to
what you felt, but...
I didn't have a father from the
time I was in the third grade...
There were a lot of times
when I hated my father.
But whenever I felt like
that, I would think...
If it weren't for him, I would
never have been born.
That's how I've come
to think about him.
Let's go home.
Everyone's waiting.
I don't want to.
I see...
I'll wait until you
change your mind.
Don't lie.
I'm not lying.
For an hour after that,
they didn't say anything.
Hitomi?
Did you fall asleep?
I'm awake.
Your stomach's telling
you to go home.
We have your favorite...
croquettes.
Let's go home.
We're home!
Akira...
I'm home.
You haven't eaten yet?
Yuria and Shota refused to
eat until Akira came home.
Akira...
I asked Naoko to go home.
Yuzo took her home.
Naoko just sat there, and
she didn't stop crying.
So when you see her in school,
you should apologize.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I'm sorry, Yuria and Shota.
I didn't mean to
shock you...
They were just a little bit shocked...
They're ok.
Shall we eat?
Let's wash our hands.
Time for dinner!
After dinner...
This is...
...a notebook, your mom and I
started when we took Keiko in
as a foster child... It's full
of things we learned.
They taught us a poem at the
foster parents' meeting...
It's such a nice poem...
Do you mind if I read it?
"There once were two women
who never knew each other..."
"You don't remember
one of them..."
You call the other
one, Mother"
"These two women are tied
to you and how you are"
"in a way that no one
else knows about."
"One watches over you
like the stars above..."
"The other one wraps you
in warmth like the sun..."
"One nurtured you inside her,
and gave birth to you..."
"The other one lived
her life with you."
"One gave you the strength
to go in search of love..."
"The other one loves you
no matter what happens."
"One made you a citizen
of your country..."
"The other one gave
you a name."
"One gave you the talent
you were born with..."
The other one nurtured that
talent, and gave you a dream."
"One gave you the power to
feel happiness and sadness..."
"The other one made you feel safe
when you were filled with doubts."
"One always remembers your
cute smile when you were a
newborn baby... The other one
encompassed your sadness."
"One parted with you...
For your sake, out of
love for you. The other
one wanted to meet you
so badly, she prayed with
all her heart, and the gods
brought you two together
without hesitation."
"And now when you ask the
question that's been
bothering you all this
time, with tears in
your eyes, Which
is my real mother?"
"My dear child... They
are both your mother."
"You were blessed with
all kinds of love
from both your mothers."
That's the poem.
Akira...
When you said that I was
the only father you had
in this world, it made me
so happy, I could cry.
But...
That's not true...
You have another father
The one who brought you
into this world.
You mustn't forget
your father.
If it weren't for your father,
you and I would never have met.
Like this poem...
Your father had his reasons
for leaving you..
And I want you to become a kind
person who can understand those reasons.
That's all I wanted to say.
That night, Katsutaro looked
through the photo albums by himself...
Although he is supposed to
be raising the children,
he feels that they are
raising him, too.
Akira wrote a letter of
apology to Naoko...
And he hopes that someday
he can meet his father
again with kindness
in his heart.
Hitomi went out in the
alleyway, and looked
at the nameplate with all
the different last names.
And she wondered how much
of the children's happiness
and sadness she would
be able to understand.
The May winds blew a
variety of emotions
through the alleyways
of Tsukishima.
Hitomi learned something
new again...