CHAPTER 11
Summer Without Grandpa
Episode 62
Grandpa fell down
the stairs?
Katsutaro had a broken knee
after falling down the
stairs in his store, so he
was going to be in the
hospital for about a month
I thought you'd be hungry
Go ahead and eat
Thank you
Listen, everybody
What's up, Dad?
Akira, Yuria and Shota.
You're the children of
this tenement here.
Isn't that right?
So while Katsu's gone
for a month, I thought
we could all help
Katsu's family
What do you think?
Excuse me
When I overworked myself
Vf
e asi time an
collapsed, I realized that
if I let stubborn pride
get in the way, I only
inconvenience everybody.
So this time, Please let me
rely on everyone's help...
Please help me out.
Please help us.
We're neighbors
aren't we?
I'll do anything
I can do to help.
I will, too
Whenever I have time,
I'll stop by here.
Thank you
Let's all discuss what
we can do to help
What about the
store, Yu?
Thats true...If it's
closed for a month,
he'll lose money,
6aij I.UOM
That's what I thought, so
before I left, I asked
Katsu about it
If he wanted to keep the
store open, I'm willing
to watch the store for him
What did Dad say?
He said he would feel
bad, and he didn't
want to me to overdo it
But he really wants
to keep it open.
Dad was proud of the fact
that he never closed
He said the customers made
time in their busy schedules
to come to the store, so it
was his job to stay there
and wait for them to come
What is it? Go ahead,
and say it
Why don't we just decide
to keep it open then?
I'll watch the store
When I'm watching the
store people buy
a lot of shirts
But we can't have you watch
the store all day long
Why don't we take turns?
Whoever has the time
can come and do it.
That's an idea
Why don't we do this then?
Let's make up
a schedule
Schedule?
We'll figure out what has to
be done at home and at
the store, and make up a
schedule of who can help.
We'll decide who can
do what and when
We'll divide up the work
That's a good idea
Let's draw up a schedule
for a whole day then.
Let's do it
You can be the "shoki."
What's a "shoki"?
Don't you konw what
a "shoki" is?
A cup or a bowl?
That's "shokki' (dishes).
You did that on
purpose, didn't you?
Of course! I don't want to
be a "shoki" (secretary)
I'm the chairman, and
you're the secretary
All right. I'll do it
I'll be right back.
What is he doing?
Let's start with morning.
ere i you gei
ITat. Yu 1>?
Don't get hung up on
details, **.
Let's get back to this..
What about the mornings?
In the morning, it's just
breakfast and the laundry,
so the children and I can
do that by ourselves.
When I'm on the night shift,
I'll come by to help when
I get off work.
That would help a lot.
After breakfast, you have
to go to your part-time
job, don't you, Hitomi?
that's right. So the
children will be alone
after I leave...
It's summer vacation,
isn't it?
I'll study in the morning.
I can look over their
homework for them.
We should do it downstairs,
so rio one can come in,
lid r t) the^place
Shall we do that then?
Do your studying downstairs
in the morning
Yuzo - you're not
keeping up
Hurry, and write it down.
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
All right?
Ne lis the store.
He opens at 10 o'clock.
I'll come right before that,
and open the store
We have to take out the
things on the wagon.
After I help out with that,
I'll go to tutorial school
You're going to take
entrance exams next year
aren't you?
We'll go to the pool
After I see them off,
I'll watch the store.
What time do they come
home from the pool?
1:30...
You have to eat lunch,
don't you?
On my way back from buying
my supplies, I'll bring
something by for you
I can make something, and
bring it over, too
I'll make extra rice
in the morning
Hurry, write
that down
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
I'm writing
Tie's going to cook
extra rice, and
Ume and Mari will
bring lunch
So that takes care of the
morning, doesn't it?
What about
the afternoon?
We have to go
and visit Dad
I can bring him a change
of clothes everyday
after my part time job
Before I go to school.
I'll stop by to see him
after my tutorial school
I have supplementary
lessons sometimes
and days won't always
be the same.
What about us?
I'd like to take you,
but it depends how
busy our shop is
What about you, Mari?
I have shamisen lessons
in the afternoon
Are you learning to
play the shamisen?
Idiot! She's teaching it
She's a master (shihan)
That's right! It's been a
quarter of a century
(SHIHAN seiki) since she started
started playing the shamisen
Depending on my shift,
I think I can make it
~t\$o days a week
Just as we expect
from you, Keiko.
The rest of the days,
I'll take you.
I'll leave the work
to Yuzo.
Just as we expect
from Uncle Yujiro
Wait a minute
You can't do that. You have
to take care of the books.
What is it?
What do vou want?
All right. After I take
the children, I'll come
back to Tsukiji, and
do the books
That's great
About watching the store...
The way we have it now,
Ume's watching the
store all day long.
You're right.
There's something
I want to watch.
What?
The repeat broadcast of
a historical drama
But, I guess I could stand
not seeing it if
that'll help..
No, no #11
You should watch it
It's all you have to
look forward to.
I'll take the kids to the
hospital, go back
to Tsukiji to do the books,
and come back here..
That would be about 2:30,
and I'll take over for
Ume, and watch the store
Just what you'd expect
from Yujiro.
Give Yujiro a hand
Thank you.. Thank
you, everybody
Did you three finish your
homework for today?
Not yet
Go and finish that first
Okay.. let's go upstairs
I give them credit... They
must be feeling lonely
Without their dad
The adults have to
do their best, too
This is tough... We're
only up to 2:30
It'll be exhausting to do
this for the whole summer
That's right
Hitomi!
What happened to Dad?
Momoko! Haven't you
gone to the hospital?
Of course not! I heard the
message and rushed
right over here
Why? I left a message
for you to come to the
hospital, didn't I?
I thought I'd come here
first to find out what
was going on. I figured
someone would be here.
How is he? You said he
broke his bone
Where? Was it his back?
His ribs? His skull?
Tell me!
His left knee.
His knee?
It's just his knee..
Everything else is fine
Will he be able to
walk again?
What about physical therapy?
Will it take about three years?
He'll be fine after a
month in the hospital
One month...?
There won't be any
after effects, and
he'll be able to return
to his normal routine.
It wasn't as bad
as I feared
jia iJi» ii) iji j iJjjylaia
ery is io n r
That's right
At home, too
He broke his bone at home?
That's right. He fell down
What is he doing? Getting
hurt inside the house
It happens often to
old people
Because their
muscles are weak
He was feeiing under the
weather from the heat
Right, Ume?
He seemed tired when
he climbed the stairs,
and I heard this loud
clattering sound...
I yelled, "Katsu" as
he came tumbling down
That's right, when I heard
that, I came running over
He was at the bottom of
the stairs groaning
so loud and his face looked
he Itfiis ace
That's how he
always looks.
This is ridiculous!
I got worried
for nothing.
Don't say that, let's
go to the hospital.
The hospital?
What are you saying?
You're his daughter!
If I go, he ll just say
something sarcastic like
"Oh, y tic fo^^now I feel worse"
I think definitely,
he will be happy.
in that case...
Come, and help out
over here then.
We were just discussing
who can do what, and
when they can come
to help out.
Actually, it's not easy..
We were just saying how
exhausting it would be
to do it for a whole summer
It really will help if
you pitch in
I'm really busy at work.
Can't you do something?
Your office is early, so
you could op on
your way o o es
calls, or something
Just do what you can..
Keiko and I are
both busy, too
isihj i
/ jl 3 -hlLLJj
If I do , t'il o ike
I'm orried b t
him, wa r ing
o!he him o
Is this any time to be
so small-minded?
I am not! Do you know
what that old man
put me through all
these years
I'm disowning you! You're
not my daughter! ^And. "
Ail ri^fit.Guilder land.
Too eing
small mindedrbut if
you could just look
at the big picture..
What^o youTnealjy th T?
Look at it this way
You're not coming to help
Grandpa out.. You're
he n becau
y dan n
i o ried to keep
busework,
he. a ing at the sam§
ime I ollapse again
Especially since
it's summer...
And it's so hot
she's sure to collapse.
All right, if it's for
Hitomi's sake, I will.
That's right.
It's not for Dad's sake,
but for Hitomi and
the children's sake
All right. I'll do it
That's that then.
Give her a hand
I'm hungry
Ume made omeman sushi.
I'm exhausted.
I think this might be the
chance for those two
to make up.
I think so, too
If he learns that Momoko's
helping at home,
I know he'll be happy,
deep down in his heart
Find the right timing, and
take her to see him
in the hospital.
I'll find the right timing,
and give it a try
Everyone was going to
work together to get
through the one month that
Katsutaro would be gone
The summer had
just begun