Trying too hard to find happiness
Episode 58
Thanks for the food
Let's play cards, Akira
Okay, but just one game
Be sure you finish your homework
So you ran into Keiko at the orphanage
She was there to tell them she was getting married.
I'll bet everyone was
As you'd expect, everyone there is warm-hearted, aren't they?
It made me realize that I have to try harder.
It was a good training for you then
And.
I have something to tell you
What is it?
What did you want to tell me?
You know when I went to Atami to dance for a
part-time job
And ?
And I ran into the most unexpected person.
Who?
Mr. Katsumata
What a coincidence!
Did you go up and talk to him?
No I didn't.
Why didn't you? He's going to be like a member of
our family soon
He was with a woman.
A woman?
They were wearing cotton kimono and they were
arm-in-arm.. Like this
Who was it?
Probably...his lover...
Hitomi. What are you saying?
Katsumata is getting married to Keiko
That's right
That's why I want YOU to tell Keiko
to reconsider this marriage.
Wait a minute! What are you saying. Hitomi?
When was it you went to Atami for that part-time job?
This past Saturday..
Keiko said that Mr. Katsumata was on a business trip to
the Kansai area this past Saturday.
That's what he told Keiko
Are you saying..
that Katsumata is deceiving Keiko?
That's right. He is.
You're mistaken.
It wasnt him
You're mistaken. Hitomi.
When you saw Katsumata in Atami, were you
close, or far away?
It was far away..
If it was far away it maybe just looked like him
so you could have easily been mistaken.
Those things happen all the time
No... I'm sure it was Mr. Katsumata
! saw him with my own eyes
He was just here and he promised me that
he would give Keiko a home filled with warmth
You heard him, didn't you?
I did. I heard, but he was there!
Listen to me.
That man's face wasn't the fate of a man
who was lying
I looked right into his eyes.
That's why I believed him!
I thought it was unfortunate that he didn't look like
he could carry a portable shrine, but I believed
that he could make Keiko happy
And now you're trying to tell me that he
was arm-and-arm with another woman in Atami...?
Don't be ridiculous!
If Katsumata said he went on a business trip, then
that's where he was.
Is this what you wanted to tell me?
It's too absurd!
I'm going to take a bath
Wash the dishes, and while you're at it,
wash your suspicious nature, too
Hitomi. Order is ready.
Miso mackerel, right?
Here's your miso mackerel.
I ordered the deep fried horse mackerel
not the miso mackerel.
That was a medium bowl large serving with an egg.
pickled vegetables...?
I ordered a large bowl medium serving with
extra, extra pickles
It's totally different
Is something wrong?
I'll exchange it right away
I'm sorry
What's wrong, Hitomi?
This is the third time today
I'm sorry.. I'll fix it
No. I'll do that.
Take care of the counter
I'm sorry
Here's your salted mackerel
If you're troubled about something, you can talk
to me about it
Bu you're the last person I would talk to, Yuzo.
Just a minute!
What do you mean by that?
She has no faith in you.
What are you saying?
An honest man like me?
Right guys?
Why're you looking away?
You all trust me, don't you?
Look at that! No one trusts you
Hitomi
You're not focusing at all today
Go, sit down.
You're bothering the other students
so go, and sit down
I'm sorry
I'm sorry, once more everyone
You mean what you told us about in Atami?
That's right
Did you tell Keiko?
I did. I even told Grandpa.
But both of them told me that I was wrong, and they
won't believe me
But it's not something for you to worry so much about, is it?
That's right, it's not
That might have been a parting trip for him.
A "parting trip"?
I've heard of that
"I'm marrying someone else, so let's
end our relationship."
That's no good!
That means he's betraying Keiko, doesn't it?
Well either way, you told her about Atami so you
already fulfilled your responsibility
After that, it's a problem for the two of them.
We have to go to our part-time job.
See you!
Keiko and your Grandpa just don't want to believe.
Since she's finally going to happy.
But I don't think she can be if she
marries a guy like that.
It's my mom.
Hello?
Hitomi? I think I can get home early tonight.
Do you want to come to my place and have dinner?
You can help me set up my bookshelves too
But I have to prepare dinner
Can't you do something?
Ask that stubborn old man
All right, I'll ask him
It's okay
If Momoko's asking you, then go and help her
She doesn't have any friends to help her move
Yuria... Hitomi said she'll be late, so
can you help me prepare dinner?
Sure!
Yuria said she'll help me
So you don't have to worry about us.
Okay, got it. I'm hanging up.
We got a lot done didn't we?
You worked hard.
Hard enough to get paid for it
Here's your pay.
It's a pretty good wine
My former boss gave it to me to celebrate promotion
Being the assistant branch manager is*|Uit 'fetoig
promotional!-titf?
Well, I guess.
Are you happy?
Actually being the assistant manager
isn't what I thought
It's a heavy responsibility
Trying to sell cosmetics that we only sold in
Hokkaido here in Tokyo isn't that easy
I go around to the department stores
everyday, but I haven't had any good responses yet
I just have to stick to it, keep trying to sell them.
Since the company pays for half of the rent
for a nice place like this, I feel pressure
to work even harder!
It's not easy, is it?
But I feel a sense of satisfaction
starting in sales, and moving this far up...
But I had to leave you alone a lot to do it
Shall we eat?
Cheers
I need your advice
About what?
About Mr. Katsumata, Keiko's fiance
Do you fee! like the father of the bride?
Feeling happy and lonely all at the same time
It's hard to relax.
Something like that
But aren't you glad that he seems like a
nice person, even if he doesn't look like
he can carry a portable shrine? That's what Yujiro said.
He definitely doesn't look like he can carry
a portable shrine
but I never had any hope that he would
to begin with
As long as he takes good care of Keiko
and makes her happy
Have another drink
"Happy sake"
"Happy sake" (the song playing in the background)
It's exactly what you think it is
He was wearing a cotton kimono, and walking
arm-in-arm with a woman in Atami, wasn't he?
Both Dad and Keiko say that you're mistaken?
I guess they just don't want to believe it
They were both so happy about it
They've convinced themselves that Mr. Katsumata
isn't that type of man
He is that type...
After all, you saw him
Let's go and check it out.
Take me there
Where?
Mr. Katsumata's apartment.
If Dad and Keiko are going to be like that,
then we have to do something about it!
What are we going to do?
I'll think about it when the time comes.
Mom!
I can't leave it like that
After all, she's Dad's precious daughter
I'm going to get ready.
Wait for me
Are you really going?
Right here
But there's no light. Maybe he's not home yet.
Let's wait for him to come home
She's really going for it...