CHAPTER 20
The Next Step
Episode 120
Written by
SUZUKI Satoshi
Music by
YAMASHITA Kosuke
English Subtitle by
Nippon Golden Network
Good Morning
Thank you for
the other day.
Be sure to call me if you
have anything else
j :<-1
What is it?
Did something happen?
You could say that.
Mom and Grandpa were
drinking together
At Mari's place?
They sure were..
They parted talking about
who you took after, and
whether you had leadership
qualities or not.
Katsu said you took
after him sintt*
he's thele Iter fit
the ftfTis
Momo said you took
after her nee
she's the "FOkUs Ishach '
(assistant branch manager)
Katsu said, "tgko
fuku (clothing) everyday '
ty/hat'^hat?
But they weren't fighting.
It's just an argument
about how much they
care about you.
They were showing their
feelings of gratitude.
Katsu feels grateful to her
for giving him such
a good granddaughter...
And Momo's grateful to
him for orr ingthat
They went home
after that, didn't they?
What did they ta1k
to you about?
They both told me to
give anything a try
It felt kind of strange.
It's so unusual for them
to agree on anything
So what did you tell them7
I told them that I was going
to continue dancing
You're going to
continue
by yourself?
fcut t akfs e happy
rijfii hey wef^
drinking together.
Thank you.
I just set it up so
they'd be together
They had you to talk
about, so they at
^rvjoqei ler to drink.
Your son's sure been a good
son lately, hasn't he?
With that new hairstyle.
Can I brag a little?
He's really doing
well lately
He gets up n ho rlie
than me, and co fc^WS
When I was going to
make the rounds of our
customers, Mold e ey
uaaJOjai • u\Mu *
o he'll go in e
He's reading books on
business management.
becoming more aware of
his position, o
esident $et.
The next thing is
to find a wife.
Don't you know
anyone?
Good idea
I'll come back again
Thank you
I'll see you again
Hello... Are you making the
rounds of your customers?
I see you're taking
your role seriously
I guess... What did
you expect?
I'm Yuzo from Tsukiji
e o qoingto
or. rorr;nov\^
m hfelate Trt.
ork
You, too, Yuzo
IJfraye hotter
6to o/na
e.ko1
What wao omg today?
I don't know
See you!
I'm home!
Welcome home.
Mis Hitomi
We have the same
hairstyle
I thought I'd copy yours
Do we have a guest?
Yuria's friend,
Ms. Sakaino
She did something
about that
Excuse me!
A customer
I'll take it.
Will you?
\e s o *t drop it
Yuria, I brought
you a snack
Welcome
This is Hitomi.
She's a really
good dancer.
I'm Sakaino Ryoko
Nice to meet you
Where's Akira?
Reading a quiz book
So you like quizzes?
Ask me something
Ask something.
Who wote the "The Brothers
Karamazov"?
Karamazov?
I'm sorry...
I don't know
Dostoevsky
You're really knowledgeable,
aren't you?
She knows a lot
of things
Do you live nearby?
Then come and
visit again.
If you want more,
just call me
Thanks
Enjoy your stay.
Be careful on
your way home
See you
Goodbye
See you again
See you tomorrow!
She's really quiet,
isn't she?
She's shy
She doesn't raise her
hand in class, and
if the teacher calls on
her she looks like
she'll start crying
How did you get to be
friends with her?
When we were changing for
phys ed class,
she was the last one
to change.
Everyone else left, but I
waited in the hallway
waited in the hallway.
She must have been happy
I'm glad that you made
friends so easily with
someone who'd come over
to the house and play
I'm home!
I'm hungry!
Out of all the new students,
you're the worst tennis player?
Some of them were playing
since middle school
There's one guy named
Komshi who has a
really strong serve
I can't even hit it
But you're going to try
your best, aren't you?
I'll still be
the worst player
But it's better
this way.
All you can do is
get better at it
Have you decided which club
you're going to join?
Don't they have
a cake club?
You love baking cakes
There's no such thing.
That's right
Thank you for
the meal
Me, too. Thank you
for the meal
She's really grown
Yuria.
Remember what she was saying
about Ms Sakaino
That's how she was when
she first came here
Maybe that's why she's
so nice to her
She remembers how
she used to be
I'm going to do
my homework
Me, too.
I'd better grow, too.
You don't have to
grow anymore
You'll hit the roof
This way?
That's not what I was
talking about
Hello.
Just a minute.
After I'm doing cleaning up,
can I go out for a bit?
Sure, OK
Mayuge Neko at a
nursery school?
The principal there
happened to see our
last performance and
called Mr Ishn..
They want us to teach
all of the children.
Is that it?
That's the one you put
on the cat's face, and
dance, isn't it?
I always wanted
to see that.
Really?
Just a minute.
You have it
It looks like this.
It's Ken and Ray!
That's right..
Look at this
She's so cute
Send that to her
cell phone
You can't do that!
You have to get
permission before
you do that.
I'll get it later
She'll hate you.
She will?
Of course!
We'll have to call Ken
and Ray, too
The budget is
small this time
so he wants just the
two of us to do it.
Is that it?
He can't bring
costumes either
He's not providing
transportation.
S ^ie$entl 1s..
Just the face?
Here you go. Bring this,
and we'll meet there
Take care of yourself.
Take care of
myself?
m^^mm
4tohbemi Nursery School
It's the first time
I've done this.
ritf make some money
and it'll help me
in the future
popular
and ei\1\a e more people
at our next event
If he was coming anyway
he could have brought
costumes with him...
Hello
I'm sorry in
to come at the last
minute like this
Not at all
THKoga, th in i ai.
I'm Mi2un
in charge.
I'm Kijima.
These are our artists..
Ippongi Hitomi and
Tanaka Moe
Pleased to meet you
Please sit down
Jfpurs age^) performance
was really wonderful
o thought I'd really
like you to teach
the children here
how to do it
You can proceed
any way you want
Concentrate on
the dancing.
We'll do our best.
Gather around,
You're the first!
Come over here
^T fta e broil Tft some
jjiM oijm a^tj spi au^
teach you to dance
Mayuge
G t»d a te noon/Moon Gro
an IStars Group .
Good afternoon
We're going to do
a dance called the
Mayuge Neko dance
We'll have all of you
dance later, so
watch carefully OK?
y.nj
Don't play yet
everybody
Watch the cats...
Watch, everybody!
Everybody
Watch us!
The Mayuge Neko were
at a total loss