CHAPTER 13
The Birth of ROSE M iRY"
Episode 74
□—X7J—IL£J (
ng "Manual Recording'
ng "Manual Recording"
ng Manual Recording"
ng ' Manual Recording"
ng "Manual Rtcording"
ng "Manual Recording'
ng ' Manual Recording''
ng Manual Recording"
ng "Manual Rtcording"
ng "Manual Recording"
ng Manual Recording"
g Manual Recording"
ng "Manual Recording"
ng Manual Recording"
ng "Manual Recording"'
Enough Sp
ng "Manual Recording"
g Manual Recording"
ng "Manual Recording"'
ng Manual Recording"
ng "Manual Recording"
g Manual Recording"
rig Manual Recording'
ng "Manual Recording"
ng Manual Recording"
ng Manual Rtcordlng"
ng ' Manual Recording"
g Manual Recording"
ng "Manual Recording!1
ng "Manual Recording"
ng "Manual Recording"'
g Manual Recording"
Enough Sp
ng "Manual Recording"
g Manual Recording"
ng Manual Recording"
ng "Manual Recording"
ng "Manual Recording"'
g Manual Recording"
ng Manual Recording"
ng "Manual Recording"
ng "Manual Recording"'
ng Manual Recording"
Enough Sp
ng "Manual Recording"'
g Manual Recording"
Enough Sp
ng "Manual Recording"
ng Manual Recording"
rig "Manual Recording"'
g Manual Recording"
ng "Manual Recording"
ng Manual Recording"
g Manual Recording"
ng "Manual Recording"
ng "Manual Recording"'
g Manual Recording"
ng Manual Recording"
ng "Manual Recording"
ng Manual Recording'
§o^pu£hou ike
} >1)1/1, or
(frag^yer on on
fo n ithyou
You c£n do it. >Aftef all, 4
^ypu're myjgrand&aughter.
You're right.
im o a e
he . ^ es /ith h
i^tv 1 Viujm
t with on m and
"tegij- 3j/v/ib
b mp s .. ont
ilJit lrt> liii^ii) U li ' >
ultlj U)J (SJiHa 1
e el , ill t?
iitui vtmiOi!
iz an '
See how popular I am.
It'$ not you
heiimizu yoka '
You're very blunt, ar
ourMs Miura.
pu'fe very blunt, aren t
you, Ms. Miura?
Rose.. 7
liiave our name..
Ouf name.
pur startin p Ini as
Rose's u io.
Man's matsuri mambo."
So ej\ c II ourselves
t)SE MARY
e I
I like it.. It's
very feminine
What about you, Vuka
£0 a ithme
If i £ okay with
all of you
I don't wa 1 to forge
that feeting
ancing mindlessly, afid
oming together as o e.
he in ividual aw Yd is
ood, we^should aim
for inning he contest.
L « im for "both
jiunifr A
Together, that makes
r "0,000 yen
I ^Ofor
hat then?
RO MARY*
They started their
afternoon practice
in a cheerful mood.
They put whatever ideas
J' Villi)
togeu'er-to/cre te
ROSE 1ARY's jda e
That's good
You were ail great
came ith a move
b felbu b
IJU JSj«
te> s art
unko 9
Wh r you usin ahce
mo esilike those idols
r long ag 9
thou Tit it would
tj6 VergrebU
That's not the point*
ts silly!
t's not silly!
really worked h<ard
to come up with that
vjNow... now.
You mean you liked
what she did?
No, but
though! it ftas
pretty good
You ju it hSvfe
bad taste
Your moves are I just
the same pattern
TUKd... JUIiKU
We just decided on
our name, so let's
try to get along.
Good work for the first da/
13>ur training camp.
We worked hard,
i n't we.
We got the first
aif done already.
I guess..
I'm hungry
Shall we eat?
Good Idea.
ant to eat "gyoza"
Sounds good to me!
Shall we have
gyoza" then?
Let's eat "gyoza/' and do
our best again tomorrow
Let's eat!
What d070uthink of
Otsunomiya "gyoza"*
it's delicious
It 1s, Sritit?
Just reme./bef\
Reldy?
to n..
utsunomiya'
Gyoza" own...
Utsiino
Very good
YoQ're forcinglh In
to say that.
Therrwhat'slhe rariten
noodle town...9
Monja" toftn.
Tsukis .imal
Remember
It's ^elifiSbs.
Eat up!*Eat<ots.
Instead of a training
camp, this is more
like spending the night 1 a
relative s house isn't it?
It is, isn't it?
Since there are
children here
Have you lived in Tokyo
all your life?
Since I was born
I gu Iss someone like !you
wou
Idn't understand how
much someone like ine would
long to come to Tokyo
Like attaining success
in the world?
I guess it's iike that.
I To me, Tokyo is a stage.
Everyone is competing
for the spotlight
to shine on them
Once/ou gel up Vi the
stage, you t go
backstage Util you create
a moment of excitement
! think! understand
it's so like you.
jfou don't feel that way,
do you,+litomi?
Even though you're one of us
who came to Tokyo
didnt think
that far
I like when everyone is
working hard together
If the girls I was dancing
with didn't quit, think
would still be
in Sapporo
Why did they quit?
They found full-time jobs
If they looked at reality,
it was better to find
something normal rather
than hip hop
They wer^n'i^yrpna.
tried that my s If
But the difference was that
couldn'£<gtve t*ip
That's why I'm going
to do my best
What is it?
A iSincloth...
Loincloth.
What do you think
you r Tl ing*
What's wrong?
What happened?
Why are you hanging up
loincloths dressed
in your loincloth?
There are girls here.
I wasn't thinking
This is my summer
casuaiweaf.
Do 1 forget about tomorrow's
co-ed party.
Wear some ciothes before
Vpti say that
I'm softy
Please calm down.
I'm counting on
all of you
Good night
We have to get dp early
tomorrow, so hurry,
and hang these up
Moe'
Harig in there
a i ri %re Mop
Jt sieigh days until
the ^summer contest.
ft looks like ROSE MARY is
star irig to get on tra£k