CHAPTER 13
The Birth of ROSE MARY
Episode 75
They held a dance class
for the children.
That was great,
wasn't it?
OK.. that's enough of
eing the audience.
JMe. your
turn to dance
c nt o t
lfy$S T-actice
yHe n.
Ju§f4§arnjt
step by- tep,
lanSjf^GtfjJI
be fin
nTecitejhfe u.tiplication
i* 1e. can't yo i. Sh la?
Two times two is four
Two times three is six.
Two times four is eight
Two times five is ten...
That's right... Even if
you couldn't do that
ir 1 you\verp gradually
a e o re a e ejwsoe
1 d e; Weren't ^ou?
It's the $am
ithWiting.
You leariTe*a~li o'e
one 1, time, n
praclice it ofe?
hen eventua ly. or dy
vill ju ImbvelrTunlly.
Shall e<give it a try?
Let's try it
Let's do it.
Yourh s aveio emore
/ol
Ready?
That's very good, Yuria!
p
Are you okay?
Shota. What's wrong?
TDid 6u i It your leg?
I can't do it,
after all.
You can do it. ol
practice,! promise
youjl be
Let's give it a try.
Right..Left
^Tur 1
One...Two...Right!
Left! Turn!
That was close!
One..Two..Right!
Left! Turn!
You almost got it!
I asked Akira..
What did you ask?
Wh 1 hfe pntecl ob
^henhe^rewu ...
What did he say?
He hasn {decideS r
profes ion yet,
> wants to be a man who
can be proud of himself
That's so cool.
When he'd tided w iVth t
he was going^o ry
to get into high sth
he WorkaJ in Tsnkiji
for a while with zo
That's when he got
that idea
Yuria had a jot...
r e or a baker
dancer
So dancing is
one of them...
She really seems
to love it
She learns fast, too
Hitomi and the thers
practiced itti assion.
C ryone's e me
one, giving birf
-ttra lo\ frDfi^r
ance es
Its r lly oodun until
his point. Isn tiP
Next, we just nee o
lit in the climax
What about the mo es
id earlier?
teheed somethin §
Ti<&e £ool than th
That'll bring what we did
up to now to life.
That's right.
Do you think we can win?
We can. .. If we can come
up with the finale
Just a little more..
Let's do our best!
Hello
Mom
How are you ail doing?
Working hard?
3 an^uL
Pleased to eB! ou
Komi's indebted
tip
o ht hi
ill Jl 1 jl
ill ou serve
this % i ?
Okay
U « ±
ci brincr ake!f
Here you go
Thank you.
IITiave some, o
We're going to eat!
Go ahead.
Thank you!
Looks delicious
Are you in between
sales calls?
I'm on my way back from
a department store.
As usual, it didn't
go very well, so
I'm not too anxious to go
back to the office
That's why I made
a little detour
You're having a hard
time, aren't you?
What about you?
Is it going smoothly?
I can't say it's going
jjiojtll*
1 think we're
getting there.
You think so? if you win
the 500.000 yen. -reaX me
you're going to split
the prize, aren't you?
Which means, you'll each
get 125,000 yen.
Don't say that..
I'm trying not to
think about that
You're such a wimp.
I went to visit your grandpa
at the hospital
You did?
He was flirting with the nurse
even while I was there.
I didn't want to start
fighting with him, so
I left right away.
He was just embarrassed
great r r s,
isn't if
suppose...
"What if we combi Vthis
md this together?
After Momoko left they
were narrowing their
ide o n o ley could
ccrne Vip^With itclimax
How about Jf we olo
hat witl^his.
Even if they didn't come
up with an answer, they
felt like they were
tiling closer
Cheers!
Th Yik i\> II for
ommg o ay
It stiof exactly a
co-ed pany bQt
*we don$ qeilnhch o a
chance to aothis
Kind o thin
{L. J
Will you please listen?
Don't get upset.
After working up a sWfcat.
he b'lfcr is d 1ici«lis.
tlay^ ~uest . onbr
^^Makoto here.
Iter all.. «e s till
1ngl jiis age!
jfe giv(Hi jp
tgetunj married
ould think-so
You don't have to
be so blunt
I still have hope.
That's good
h on is it?
I introduced im eartie
but this isflpn-chan...
He's my classmate
Honda Mutsuo.
Hello..
He's single too
I run a fishing
guest house.
Fishing guest house?
You can c c. q i e -bit
of fish in tlie okyo Bay.
Horse<Tiackerv1. mackerel«
scor Ion is >and
even$lac dr*5 y
Then, do ■ ou have*4) 'at?
i/Vho wants to Tide
he boat?
Jj Jake out
ext time
II to tit!
Will ou ealh t
lariKyou
Let's all go when you
have Ihtftime
What's going on?
didn't expect a fishing
h obesopo ular
What are you saying?
Where does that leave me?
Don't worry!
From here on, it'll be
all about you, Makoto
I gua "fcntee ifc so*
|Joni worry*
Are you sure?
It's going to be
Mako's night.
Welcome..
So this is Tokyo's
okonomi-ya
It's not okonomi,
its monja
If you've n h
itfcJfore ^h o
outryIt'f e.ic o's.
What do you want
to do.' azu?
na I j^e try it then/3
^You ma'ke'a^vell
like this.
Then pour it inside
ache well...
Put in whatever you
want to eat, and
mix it up like this.
Will you look at that?
It's really good
Okonomiyaki is good, too.
But I prefer monja
It has depth when
you bite into it
Okonomiyaki is a little
too simple
tao'i hi "pliLJ t >
Th * Jook angry
o y'te ""bt
ook eir ates.
re
t ngr lall
That's just the way
they look.
Hiro! Isn't XU'\ enough?
It's ready, isn't it?
I guess it is
Go ahead and eat it.
Use the spatula
It's still raw..
Go tieacl.1.. t'sreatiy^
D^ilMii
Tr 1C
I don't feel like
eating it
We're leaving
We'll leave the
money
What is this "monja"
anyway?
It's ridiculous
It's something
you eat
Who are you?
Hitomi
You're being rude to the
people who run this place
How arp you come to a
monja restaurant,
insult monja, and leave
without even eating it!
It's up to the customer,
isn't it?
That's not the problem
You're insulting the
people who make it.
Haven't you heard the
saying. "When in Rome,
do as the Romans do."
You should learn to
keep your month shut!
How dare you come to
Tsukishima, and
insult "monja."
I wouldn't go to Osaka and
insult "okonomiyaki"
They'r^ll related
oeac i o i er
Whether it's "monja" or
"okonomiyaki" you
should just sit down
and enjoy it.
Shut up!
Hitomi
WhaiSlo ou think
youYed incj?
Calm down!
Just sit down!
3 fly #
It'<5 6 flyer or
a^conte
Are you going to
watch this.
We're going to enter
that contest
That's interesting
33 313
Her name's Kazu...
and she's quite well
known in Osaka.
We're called the
Blue Shoes
What's our name?
ROSE MARY
It's a nice name.
Then show us
How you dance
here in Tokyo
We'll show you
what we can do
Let's go outside!
^Outside? This is
T likishima
Sounds good to me
A dTifce' ^ttle onYfloo
!slarrtJ.(Tsukiss!ma)
Are you scared?
I'll show you
Shall we start?
I'm ready!
Clap your hands!
^f me, Kazu!
Hitomi.. I'll go
A dance battle has begun
here in Tsukishima