cfb^R^J
HAPJER 16
Goodbye Shota"
Episode 94
Written by.
SUZUKI Satoshi
JVIusic By.
YAMASHITA Kosuke
o
"Hngli Ti Subtitle By
fiippbN gqIden Network
Soc i a jo ' c ling
tem orary measures)9
i r itt^ /tjiA
S ma ill eli ingwithtiis
^rothei Saito Mikie now
I right. Than o
or Jetting us n
-Several daysiater.
Yes9
hey're here
Come in.
I'm Mikies father...
Mizus ima Toshio
I'm Ippo i &atsutaro.
Pleased o meet you
This is J^itomi.
She s helping Katsutaro
to raise Shota..
I've heard about yoif
from my daughter.
Thank you so much
for your help
Please-have a seat
If you don't mind, we ll
it in-white you talk.
Excuse the way I'm dressed...
Like someone in a cowboy
western drama
Not at all
I was going to dressin
something more normal,
but I thou Tit you shou
see me as I usually am
I feel the same way.
You've raised S ota n il
now with suth I Ihng^are,
but well be raisin
him from here pn.
So I wanted you to
see me aslVri.
Mr Mizushima. 9
Yes9
raised Shota as if he
were my real son
I thinks know Sh ta better
than anyone nlhis orld
I'm sure you do
He really lovels "natto'
(fermented so eans).
We eat "natto'
every morn n .
He doesn't ike
bell pe s.
But Hitomi Jrie er r§ 1
bell peppers rateg Vi
him, and he smarting
jeat bell e ers now
If you slice thepi\\ peppers
really thin, he'll eat it.
And, I've told him tie er
nything else, but he
Inus n't lie.
I'll do the same... If he
lies, I II scold him.
There are a lot of things
I probably overlooked,
so 1 don't kno o
well I've one
No... You've raised
him well.
I could tell when I mei
him the other day.
Thisis'srshirt that
I sell at my store..
I asked 5hota if s ra a
had a big stomach like me
^arid lie .said you iOnf o
I thought4his g oo
good on you
h nk you... I'll wear it.
almost forgot...
This is dried flying ish
that we make our elves.
I don't know if you'll
ikeit or not...
It's one of my
avoritetoods
It s a fish!
Of course! He^aid
1 was fl irr fish.
That's right.
Thank you
Katsutaro.
Hitorru...
Thank you so much for t
you ve done u« til now...
You've cared for Shota in
place of Mikie and myself
ed for Shota fn
place f Mikie and myself.
eW^a e over from here,
and raise him.
We'll raise him to be someone
you can be proud of.
Please watch over us.
I BeSse take
re of S ^bta
a you
Shota's grandpa was a
nice man, wasn't he?
m relieved
Whafsh II we do? - Je have
bne m>e month.
What do you mean9
I wanted t leave Shota
Wi n the b Nt memories
before We senfl him off
I want Akira and Yuria to
spend a lot of time with
Shota during this last month,
so they'll have lots of
memories or Shota.
JWhat shall we do9
have something to say
You probably already
knowjthis, but...
Shota will be ivmg
with his mother
He'U beliving in
Izu Oshima where
hismother's father, in
other words, Shota's
grandfather lives
itomi arid 1 went to meet
is grandfather 'oday..
His name is Toshio, and
he's a really nice m'n
So I think he'll give
Shota lots of love
ota will be movin^ it
this o te
eco tl term . s
December 26tr .
That's about a mo th
from now, isn't it?
i iidi b nyni... we n iidvt?
ori s "month before She .a
a es this ho&se nt
to m
th li
the best mc
hat jie pen
in hisliouSe i
o a e to hear your i eas
about fiat we should do
hat do you
-want to do?
h t about going to
the amusement park
Or shall we *ake a
trip somewhere
That's a good idea
Let's go to Hawa i
We can t go to Hav a i
over the wee e
If we're going, we t»o
go somewhere closer. /
he ow about going
o he hot springs7
e n try out the
different hot springs,
eat lots of
gobd food .
lA?e don't have to
gb anywh re...
ont have
to hold back
-et's go wherever
you want to go
It s "Va ... AA/e don't
have to50 anywhere
Sbota.. Are you si rt
Do you just wa t Jto o
what we always do?
I see... You re ight
After all, we aire oy
e ing togethe , a <n
0 ether, Tig tin i ch
r and do n I in s
f tun things ro h
h wo Id ma i
most memorable
wouldn't \V>
Okay... we II hono
Shota's wish
we won do an- th n
special, and s o
what we alwa s o
We ll treasure each a ,
and trea ure th s a
month we have togeu er
with Shota
That's all ^ve to say.
Shall we play cards?
Let's play Sevens'1
Okay
Let's go upstairs.
He's right.. We don't
have to do anything
special, Ho we?
"hall we piSt the
aundry away9
Sounds good to me.
Like we always do...
Like we always do.
li's the last month that they 41
ce living ogemerwi i .nora.
December, 2007
2007fiM2B
£007f£12B
Aki ! Shota*
It's orning
Wake up'
Stop that1
C ud morning
I'm leaving
Wailor me'
fhey Ye so full
of energy
The miso mackerel is ready
Here s your miso
mackerel..
I'll have motsu-ni" (stewed
pork inte Vines) large bowl.
r^edium serein ...
Ill have the same .
Two ers
*fhe ^st memories they co Id
ave as pending he tlays
like they al a's do
Like learning (h ^ance
steps one by one,
hapomess^jn ie ittle
litlk S JllJ jp
JIJU J Jil^
^We re home1
What's for dinner?
Bellj>eppers...?
When you come home, a *h
your Imds, and gargle
Norma ly, she didn't th nk
about it, but when she
h \ightih IJhey would
soon Be parti ith
Shota, each day became
extremely^ftecious
a uge
I hih
IT osuke
^tzh'MtbJXK '
9> ?J- ai Together
ztj^Jl
s y y
astt^o'^-is'a^iBic.'...
(FEBO tz^h
m±i:rc w<P as
*z?jt±z>T UTjh =];Oh *..
wfc—fC-HHappv!)
37>4=—fC * (Lucky! J *:
Oancing!)
2 3 Oancing!)
Sjfio Cancing'!*)
Cfcj to.,
iiXjjyu X.
) r<- hz?^ a- Together /
y^ Kk na
]
HAVE FUNI!