CHAPTER 18
Season 6f Love"
Episode 106
nsoi^BI d06)
Written by.
SUZUKI Satoshi
JVIusic By.
YAMASHITA Kosuke
^Engli li£iAitle By
MPPbN GQ ^ENtJEYWORK
I thought you went to
your part-time jbb
We met up with BLUE SHOES'
Why did you come here?
Becaus lhav t eard that
your mentors are going :o
e.ler Dance Beat yet.
We were headed for the
monja" shop to give
them a little incentive when
we ran irffo these Mo
! heard you have a
studio here
Can we use it?
Beautiful madame..
Sui
They're good.
Yhfe^'vejotten even t iter
since t e last time
Thank you, be tiful
madame
You're el come1
What do you think?
You can see for yourselves that
you cant even compete
with us, can't you9
! have a dynamite body1
eil KEN and RA *iot to run
away and compete with us
hall e go?
ait inute1
wrat is it?
ant to talk
toy'V 1
one.
What is it?
.Why %do you keep harassing
-KEN and RAY like that?
It's obvious, isn't it?
m avengingtnyrf)rpther
Those two killed
my brpther.
I heard it was
an accident
A dtorcycle acc de 1
it was no accident*
They killed my
brother's heart
That's why tie took
his own ife1
Whit do you mean "they
killed his heart"?
My brother artfi RAY were
seeing eachjpther, but
KEN stole^er away
My >pther<was betrayed £y
this rus e Iriend and
his sweetheart
p m sure it's just a
misunderstanding.
jRAY,and KEN aren t
Mike that.
Are you sure you're not
overestimating them9
Have you ever heard the
phrase dance is life ?
When a person dances,
it expresses his life
If that's how you feel,
don t think you'll
liow how good ^ dancer
you really are
It looks to me like you're
using your dancing as a
way to vent your
bitter feelings.
I don t think you
should do hat
That's not Wh 1
dancing is..
It's somethin tfi Vfteople
can enjoy watching,
where you can mak "friends
with the people you dance
With, and something
that has drea ^
You have no right to lecture
me about aancing
1 kezu*
You should just
let her be
I don't care for
people like that
Isshe|hinking
-about KEN?
Do yo hm they'rg
dating**
o, I'm TW
^ftou hear 5?
It's not eas etting your feelings
cr SS to peo e^sit?
You e n|elKENJiow
Ufeel ab "tttihim?
No'
TheritYuzo9
efinitely not1
I'm just talking ab lit
PEOPLE IN GENER V
see pebple
fin ge ^rai
S eaking about getting our
feelings acrtfss, the son
f the people behind i\ew
is iina going o marry
the girl next Woor
isn't Tie?
He's been trying
/or 10 years
en years9
4feMe's been trying to get
his feelings across
or ten years, and
^y'/e finally g ^ina
married now
it really is difficu t
getting ^our feeling
^ TosS to others.
It is, isn't it9
It doesn't go the way
you want it, does it9
Thank you for all
the memories
T^ayrwe are graduating
from HigashlTsuklshima
Grade 6ehoo|"
Dad's really in a good
mood, isn't he9
He's probably relieved
because you passed
your entrance exams'
How are things going
with your lovelife?
I told you., t's
not like tha 1
Th t's because you're
a late bloomer
That's probably it
I don t want to heartthat from
someone in grade school.
Are you home, Katsu?
He s ri the bath
right now
Your grandpa doesn't need
a karaoke room, does he?
Are you going to
Mari's place?
I've fully recovered
from my cold
Katsu 9
After you get out of the bath,
let s go to "Matsuri"
tVfter you get out of the bath,
let s go to "Matsuri."
I'JI be out of the
bath soon.
Thank you for the
invitation"
Here*sH6$our
recovery, Yu
Thank you
Are you fully
recovered?
| actually stretched jt
$o t Idnger so I could
leave Yuzo in char e
of the shop.
riot ready yet
No-good, huh7
J Know fie« trying, but
Jiejdst runs around
in circles... Once he gets
^n idea in his head, he
paiVj $ee anything else
j> He^ets on the phone to
Jake orders, but he
^puts too ifauch of a burden
^nlhe employees.
-When you're in a position
(o jfTiciitage others, you
o Jjaye to ^bie to see
h t's going on all
•around you, don't you7
That's ju hit
He cant do it
He's not ready to be In a
management position yet.
0! oes "hat make
yo ' n a way9
BdUrtiighype even happier
-jfony son was a full-fledged
dftult, aftd could tell me
toleave the business
his hands, so I can
a.ne it easy
i don't sek what's wrong
with nfnning around in
Ire es... nit's a lot
etter Jnan riot moving
at all isn't it7
Eventually, the c6gs in
the wheel might catch,
and^tart ftvingfhe
$fav it's supposed t6.
I guess I'll just
have to wait then
As the saying goes
If winter comes, then spring
cant be that far behind "
CSme ^hmkofit,
heri rnrt xomes
it'll be a^fear since
itomi am W
That's right... A lot
happened, but she's
part of the family now
She s adorable
isn't she?
I'll bet you feel that
on don't wantlogiv iier
away to any mannow.
that might b£trQe, but
it^Joesri't^volrk^ut
that way, dcfek it?
^fterall, lie'llbe21 soon,
and<a*ull-grbton lady
I heard she found
a Doy rien
; ho?
ii 6JjH ' X
eard bo t t, too
1ako ojd ife
e god -looking ancer
ihiJird he was really cool
Yuzo was really^jpset
fou re talking about
See? You knewabout him.
i asked her if KEN
wa % ^-boyfriend
^Sand Ihe told me,
absotuteiynot.'
She won t admit it
to you, Katsu
S i usi mbarrassed
don't believe that.
He's ncft her boyfriend
We^e talking
£bout Hitomi...
She's still a child
you just said she's a
^ull grown lady
lOidnt he9
he's ot o ular
/ith IT s
What are o aying9
Storm's ery c e
Thatright.
•No, she s<not.
Yes,^heis!
Her^amily migll think
She's cute, u 1
others woulcJnt
4h11< so
He's getting all
worked up
How ador \\e
She doesn't feve tiy
<jim
appeal at alf.
\
i^ne... iwu ini^tf
' f v : \ ' o
I thin Tiris all...
Thank you for always
thinking of us
Don t worry about it.
Next time I make something,
I'll bring somexwer
Tha kyou
Good night
What are you doing7
Returning her dishes
What's wrong>
Why are you sighing7
I Jdn't know what to do.
Have some tea.
Thanks
rrm fquite full-fledged
when it comes to work
I'm not good at it
Ldl! I IIIIU
wife either
don t1<nbw what
} "Qojinymore.
VI ill's 0setwith
rr^all the time.
m nlyca Sihg trouble
^drNish and =he
others at work.
It Ink'I'm doing
the «lst I can,
bTtt§ust urns
out "hat way
If this^ee sup, then
I won t |jiappv at all
Excuse me.
Hitomi9 mat BLOCKS
rig 1 now..
There s trouble
over here
All right. I'll be
rig
hi ovelr
Wait fpr te
Who Is that7
Was that c \jy
KE ^gain?
How rude1
That wasn t KEN..
And besides, he s
not liki that1
I'll see you1
"Wait...
Akira! m going
out for a while
Okay1
He/»
Are youjUst^joing to
leave me^ikr this?
Mole
Hitomi! Overthere'
Kazu's trying to pick a
light with RAY
H]told you..! 5n t run away
^ahd compete against us.
We're not funning aWay
It's no use talking
toy fl1
Ca I * EN otfer
Wait a mlntfte
What do vou want?
Hitomi 7
you .harassing
RAv again9
Vontiry to make me
look like the villain.
i'mju tilling her that
averi e'my
broth Ts death by settling
it Tit \ dan e loor