HAPTER 12
J Can't Go to the Festival"
t pisode 70
My mom ^ tsic i n
So I thought rtow would be
a good chance to onvince
her to come.^rid
live with 5.
So I need your help to
get my mom to lean
towards living with us
Me?
If possible, Hitomi, too
Hitomi. too?
n ou greed to it?
Of course!
Don'tide th \
on your own!
hat's^ighF fibe
I don't think it's
ecess^y!? Tr Onfe o
to someplace she can *
get used to atlier ag
I don't thin h land Is
wife will get alon ther
! heara'shesa
very good wife
And she's agreedlo i in
with Tetsuo's mothe .
I don't thin \hk 'Smadam
is a good wife a J1I.
Are youbgainst t?
Of course I am.
I'm not tbo sure
\oOtit
hy?
I think it's tiard for.
h V at her age to do
the cooking, cleaning
and laundry by
e selfeTer day
It was okay because she
got over her illness
—Tight away but itstjoing
to h**en mtfte and /nore
o ten fromtiowon.
Even if it's a little
hard to ^t ujed to
Iriritfg jn a strange la
and it's a little Ird
to ge long with^i r
daught«r- nlatff
on t
bin n
.43
es ein
a ilia sftr y| in
her i e an easier life?
Very go d,Hiroshi.
n ike our IderJjro i e
you un er^tand. don't y V?
AreyofffjoiA§1o
betray me?
I'm not betraying anyone.
Let's no fight
Stop it
Can s ^ou something.
ha
hat?
Is it art of your
*sa!es work?
j o • • lil|u
thought so'
What4sthis« tout
a shopping mSlP
etsuo's om an as pahs
to build a shopping mall.
And Tetsuo p n harge
of getting tena sfor
the shopping mall
So since MoiTT aving ay
Jiard time a vprk.
she's after af>pot in
the shopping mall.
Is that it, Momo?
old your soul for
hat's n't it... Although t oes
have a littlest to do with it.
But basically, we should think
about Ume's happiness.
Isn't h itfor*.
Ume o eci
«ie?
I'm forthem living
toget fl
What's witfi$!) *
I s ould ask you
the samefT^n .
is it because you feel
inf riortof f? o?
What?^
Your classmate jssuccessful,'
so you're jeaiouSwen't you?
Say tha ti^m!
Stopfffl
I'm not iro ing.
Are you opln?
Yes, we^Trf!
Come inr
They're pplh
*We have a ii 1e variety
of "monja" ere.
o re ou going tola k
o m bout Sunday?
In a way, I think
Tetsuo is right.
Jn a way.! think
etsuo s/ight.
ven f theire areafe
pro lems, t's bestfor
a amily to We toge her
B lore it's too late.
Yokoyama
So i can under tand
how Tetsuo feels...
i thinkJieca t pbut
worry bout you...
^Especia I te
^h^t pbened.
even if you've is reed
up uniilfiow, how about
ifyoujilst-si o n, an
eailogether once?
He dsaid V o der a'super
deluxe order of sushi.
iHe tre Is rne like
a stranger.
Ordering take out
susm fortnivery.
The^hat o ldydulike?
thejfVecomm o my
ho ^ ^hey should pat
/"hat I eat
Jfihey/e ^oming for
1unch? Jean fix it.
A e this coming Sunday?
3lf ihey waiit Jolcome
they canlfome.
That's or
enough, Ume
"Thank^ou!
l'lfta I etsuo.
It's Sunday
Hello.
Hello!
Keiko! Did you come
to help out?
It's a nice da^ to
do the lau Adry
What's Xh£
Tetsuo and his family
are ommg pver to
me s place
You meaVi the "madam"?
Th I s right
(Jme said she ll fix them
so herself, so
that's why I'm bringing
these over there
tting aside the question
of hether it's better
for her to live with them,
I ju*! Ihink that it's a
good thing for them to
eat a m lal together.
Fo , no rtiatter what
kin of relationship
th ent and £h!ld has
it's more than enough
that they can just
live together
Keiko.. ?
is you'
mfe to do the laundry
o you want to help mb?
It feels good,
During the summer
best thing is doing
the laundry isn t
During the summer, 4h
best thing is doin
the laundry, isn't it
Hey! It's cold
&hat are you doing?
hat'6 Great.
efs ay, Akira
can t. 'm reading.
carft^'m reading.
jgke hte oTning
pretty soon
me's grandson
You met him at N W
ear's, didn't you?
You met him a Ne
Year's, didn i yo
I don't remem e
Play with him.
Are you sure it's okay
forUs to join you?
Ofc lirSe
"hat'^Vhy I made
all that food.
Wh.lls that?
u«p
What is it?
"He Wasip \>d at writing.
Isn't his wrjting
-beliliful*
■^pfi tB Sg*1
Let me see that.
It's your treasure,
isn'i jtHJme?
That's right.
Um looks like she s
enjoying it,doesn't she.
They're here!
They're coming!
rue "madam'fs here.
Madar*? <She'« ^Te.
It's been a while
Doy to Know what
)his is?
Its pickletl daikon
r clish..
It's ho herein
£ukishima.
I really hate it
{She looks like the
epitome of societ
I didn't know you knew
hard words like tfia
Really?
Thank you for making
ur th, Mother
1 don * have much to
offer, but please
help yourself
I was going to order
sushi, but Mom said
she d fix iunch.
t thought this would
be totter ioo
It's the basics
or iving.
a in<j1i home iikelhis,
add "flavor, doesn't it?
ere's a restaura ^ like
Is inAzabu.
I've b^en there witfim/
fqeritis on ourjway
back Tfdm an exhibition
Shall we eat?
My^cjame, Mom
Wait a minute...
*fcan't he do without it
for a little while?
Why should he? It keeps
him quiet
What kind of iffiso oup
do you like, Takeshi?
Takeshi! Grandma's
talking loypu
Xe doesn't like anything
in particular
I put "nameko" mushrooms
in 'he miso soup today..
Takeshi.
it should be okay.
Don't play with
^our^jame
Hitomi!
hat fire you doing?
^me^ a King im.
«4f yo re his mother,
iet^iim answer
H'm sorry.
e Jias great
concentration
Takeshi.. .*YoU
-like games...
I'm going to
day utside
t) kay.
But e're going lb
t rom now,
He just^/vants
16 explore
He's lull of
turiosity
Is it okay, Mother?
Surfe..
ComeifeckVi litawa^v
Shall we eat
I heard sorrtething break.
I'll go, and check it out.
e did it
id you bre *k
this, Shota?
No, I didnt
u houldpla pal
in a wider space...
Isn't that right,.dear
That's right.
Let's go inside.
^t's eat first, t in
clean it up
You really didn't
break th 1?
No, it wasn't me
Dad always told you,
didn't he?
You must never
tell a lie
It wasn't you,
was it?
it wasn't me
Okay It wasn't you.
J m sorry It wasn't you.
It was that boy
e from here.
-it yvasn't Shota
This is good, after all
it's be a long iime.
It's thela to of #our
cooking,^M In
Jhe flavor really 4s
vso in this clried
Stripsdaikon radish.
I had this at j delic lessen
in Kyoto
This "inari" sushi
s the be&t
It's my mom's specialty
She used to make it for
my school excursions and
athletic meets, but what
it reminds me of is
the festival
It's really popular,^a fT
all the people'wh ^afry
{he portable $hrines want
to eat this, so WWd
to make tons ^4t.
Everyone praises it
Dfear. ^
It a t brings$ac»<
so manymemories
i£n I eat foo
like this.
{Unfinished
I'm finished.
Are you iinished
already?
But you hardly ate
anything, Takeshi.
I'm hungry
What are you saying?
We have a whole
feast here
It's hot a |east
e isn't n thing
/antlo eat here.
on t-say things
like that
Your grandma put er
heart and soul into
making this for us
Stop it, dear..
You're scaring Takeshi.
I'm sorry
What tlo you
want to eat?
Hamburger.
s here a family
restaurant nearby?
flow can you say tiat?
You're being
ude to Mom
It can't be helped!
Takeshi ays he
w nts hamburg Y
i hen how about "monja
That's ^hat Tsukishima
lsJmown 'or
i guess tfi It'll do.
Excuse me, Mother
We'll be right back
^ThaQkjou fortfie
meal, Ume.
Mltlen it up!1§r
I'll lake you iherfe.
I'll e Tit all