CHAPTER 11
Summer Without Grandpa
Episode 64
Here
What is it?
For your Grandpa
I forgot to give it him
Give it to him yourself
I don't have time
Here... Take it.
I'll leave the
rest to you
Did Momoko leave?
What a com lie 1 air.
A towel? It's a towel.
Momoko ended up fighting
with Katsutaro again
when she came to visit him
in the hospital.
II
said, the surgery
didn't take that long.
Don't scare me like that.
o o worried that
e t in . e middle of
ing, ant)
an ver here.
You keep saying "moo, moo.'
Are you a cow?
Go on back to work
You're busy aren't you?
Dad
What?
Maybe you should take
this chance to lose
some weight.. From this
angle, you look like
a raccoon dog . nament
Mom!
Why that little
You're back
I'm sorry I left in the
middle of the meeting.
How did it go
after I left?
We didn't make any
progress at all
Everything's the
same as as before
Without you, we can't
make any decisions
%idth branch manager
ke if we really had
any motivation at all.
He did? I'm sorry.
Shall we continue the
fc ingtSia^ then?
Can you stay overtime?
Tomorrow will be
soon enough...
You can't ask the employees
to work overtime for your
own convenience
u see ; to be busy with
other things, but
I expect you to
do your best
I will.
I'm going back
to Sapporo
Good night.
It's okay with us
Let's do it
Let's do it.
Let's do it tomorrow
You can all go home
All right.
Good night
Hitomi!
Shall I give you a hand?
No. it's okay. I'm sorry
dinner's so late.
Go, and finish
your homework
Good evening!
Mom?
I thought I'd help
you with dinner
I bought croquettes.
Thanks
Were you drinking?
Just a little
I had two beers
It's hot
Do something.
But what?
About your attitude
toward Grandpa.
1 Vnowjtivas my fault
, \itjcoldn t
you have been a little nicer to
him when you were there?
I was going to, but that
old man started calling
eggin eon
He was just embarrassed
I'd better say "hello"
to Mom first.
Mom.. Dad's in the
hospital. Please
watch over Hitomi and
the children.
I'll do my best, too
don't care what
happens to Dad
Where are the
children?
They're upstairs
Get them to help you
prepare dinner
It's okay
They're working on their
summer vacation homework
They can do that
after dinner
Don't spoil them
I don't remember spoiling you
when you were growing up.
I'm not spoiling them.
I'm going to call them
Don't force them
They can help when they
finish their homework
Good evening.
It's Hitomi's mom.
I'm coming in
Hitomi's mom.
Why are you playing
instead of helping out?
We're not playing..
We were helping Shota
with his project
This runs with
rubberbands
How nice.. But you're already
done with it, aren't you?
More or less.
Then come downstairs
and help out.
While Dad is away, you
have to look after
the house, don't you?
Get your act together
*eV& o*
urr
I don't-like ^rattitude
Ignore her
Letedlt again
Is there something that has
to be done after this?
I'm going to wash
the dishes.
Shall I do the ironing?
OK thanks.
Is the laundry upstairs?
OK, children... after we're
finished lied e ling, we're going
to do the ironing.
Hurry, and eat.
It's stiil wrinkled
over there.
You have to stretch
this out like this
Aunty. Aunty
Put some strength in
your shoulder Tj^fid..
Aunty!
Are you talking
to me?
Shota's still
learning...
That's why I'm having
him do this.
it's going to burn
Dad said he can just
do it gradually
Dad does it
his way
I ad t my way
I don't understand
what you're saying.
Just do it properly!
Stretch it out first ...
Not like that
Aunty!
Hitomi!
Shota's going to cry
Can't you do something
about her?
I'm not trying to
pick on them.
Sin they're summer
vacation Jm n
trying to make sure they
don't etJa y.
I'm only doing it for
their own
] jun e s an , but It's
e icSte problem...
It's difficult until you
can win their trust.
Trust?
I remember when I first
came to live here...
If I said one thing even
a little harsh, they
wouldn el gainst me
On o .at, you and
Grandpa don't get along
What does that have
to do with it?
Thos i s eally
|o e randpa
aybeth o ant to
getalonq i i someone
whos a s ighting
it randpa
All right
I'm leaving. You can tell
them Aunty's leaving.
un y wait a minute.
I agree with you.
What did I expect? They've
already seen the way
I fight with Dad... I'll be more
careful from now on.
If I want to be of help
to you, I'll have to
get along with
those kids.
Maybe I'll stop somewhere
and have a drink before
I go home
See you.
Thanks for everything.
Good night.
Hitomi!
Come with me
It's not easy
for me.
Things aren't going well
at work, and the branch
manager is always
on my case
It must be rough
It sure is!
It's not easy trying to
sel cosmetics that we
sold only in Hokkaido,
out here in Tokyo
Things like that take
time, don't they?
To to ifTJff, I skipped out
in the middle of an
important meeting to solve
that problem, to go to
the hospital!
And what does that old man
He asked me if I
was a cow
What's this about a cow?
Mom kept saying, moo.
irf&t " So Grandpa
asked her if she
was a cow
get ft!
It's not funny!
I'm sorry
He made it sound like he
didn't want me to come
anymore, and when I got
back to the office,
the branch manager got
on my case again
And when I went to the
house, the children
didn't like me either
It makes me so sad
to drink tonight
You already had
enough, Mom!
Stop
Why are you such a
good little girl?
What do you mean
by that?
You take care of the
house, look after
the children, and your
grandpa, too
What about your dancing?
Isn't that why you
came to Tokyo?
I'm dancing!
I'm going to school
School is chtstfl
What about the future?
What's your goal?
e.1.4
Decide on your goal
If you don't have a goal, you
can't go full speed ahead.
Just do what you
want to do
Just throw everything
else away
I threw everything away when
I ran off with your dad
Thanks to that, I'm still having
a big fight with Dad
I told you... you had
too much to drink
But... I don't have
any regrets.
I did what I wanted to do
And I had you
Hitomi..
It's your life
Decide what you want to do
with your dancing
She's hopeless
Trying to pick a fight
with her daughter
Let her stay at your place
She can't go home
in that condition
Momoko's words pierced
Hitomi's heart.
She still hasn't found what
she a e If fn dancing
Jqw she had another
new Yk for summer