CHAPTER 17
Dance is Life
Episode 101
Written by
SUZUKI Satoshi
Music by
YAMASHITA Kosuke
English Subtitle by
NIPPON GOLDEN NETWORK
We're not going to
enter Dance Beat.
Let's disband
ROSE MARY
I'll do my best on my
entrance exams, so
don't give up, Hitomi!
"Keppare" (Do your
best), Hitomi!
Keppare!
Shall I try my best?
February
This s a*
PI ^. |eav& "m* sa e.
Hello! This is Hitomi!
I thought about what you
said last night, but..
I'm ROSE MARY's leader.
In other words, unless
at ROSE MARY
e is Of nded,
feoSE
to be disbanded
I'm not giving up until
the deadline, so
I'm counting on you!
See you!
That was great, Leader!
e - to be positive,
e? Positive!
Are you okay?
I Should tick to being
-the nanag y..
There's too much of a
Sdiffer ncefcet e n
ybY/iancing, an ine
Doft't stop... It's on&y
darteing dlofte, soft
s a
great h 1 having
oil a te with me
Really?
Hitomi
It looks like you
need me here
I'll practice
with you
You will?
That dance move you were just
doing was pretty good.
Teach me how to do that
The move I just did?
Got it
Like this.
That's CoSsa V
Come on...Do it
with me
There you go
That's it
Hang in there
"My Memories of the
School Year" by
Oka Yuria, sixth grade,
Group one
Everyone was doing their best
at what they had to do
Junko, Yuka.
Did you get the message
from Hitomi saying that
ROSE MARY won't be disbanded
until she says so?
We heard it.
It's up to her
That's really cool
Mj I'vr) )
tji injhAa) vmiiai tUijiM
Me, too
We were all going in
different directions.
But Hitomi got us all
to come together
I said I was going io
do it alone, but
Before I knew it, the three of
us were dancing together
She knew how to get us
together, didn't she?
Hitomi's great
That's what I like about
lit:;... ntrt fjtri bi^i^iii.tr.
When the three of us
dance together
I feel like dancing
is so much fun
It makes me happy
It's really a waste
sffttt
You were great at the
Summer Contest
But I don't know how
to convince them
Then let's practice
Think of me as Junko,
and Daisuke m a
And tr o-come p ifi
what you wa> 1 to say.
That's a go lea.
I can't think
of anything.
Shall we try changing
roles then?
Maybe we're standing in
the wrong position.
That's not the problem
Daisuke's Junko, and
^suke's Yuka
That's not it
Hello..
4/V Icom^1
Ken!
What are you having today?
Miso mackerel..
One miso mackerel!
Coming right up!
He's a dancer
is
ffewHiim at the
5 iibuya lub
He's e end dancer
Here you go.
Thanks
He makes me so mad.
He's too cool
Don't worry
Thank you for waiting.
Here's your miso mackerel.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
You came here before,
didn't you?
It was delicious, so I
came again today
Thank you.
By any chance...
What is it?
It's KEN
This is the ie a
He was KEN's really good
friend, but he died in
ore clea(cide
three years ago
EIJI was riding the motorcycle
when it went right
into the ocean.
wnt
KEN ft If comes
Ifiereb liims If
It's been three years
since EIJI died, but
it seems like time has
stopped for KEN
By any chance, did you
go to Harumi Pier?
I'm sorry
t'«6*> Tiy
■MOBpJold staboutCHEAPASS
Hetlid9
When I have something to
think about, I go to
Harumi Pier to look
at the ocean
When I p e here that
time, I was on my way
back from there.
And I'm thinking of going
there again today
A number of my friends
quit dancing because
of money problems and
family circumstances
1 wasV TinyJ) 7:k1hen, too.
So 1 ^asfeckless, d
\edih In jf that's
all dancing means to them.
But I wouldn't say
those are the ones who
can be good dancers.
Why is that?
You don't just dance
up on the stage.
You're not showing your
technique, but yourself
Technique is only the
method you use to
express yourself.
Someone who doesn't run away,
who comes face-to-face with
having doubts and
suffering hardships..
If you still want to
dance after all that,
You're sure to dance
your very best
Dance is life.
Saturday
Hitomi... The deadline
is tomorrow.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to convince them
Hitomi!
Yuka! Junko!
Are you home?
Oh, it's you
Keiichi?
I'm here on business, so
I thought I'd stop
and convince Junko to
give up dancing.