chapter 18
Season of Love"
Episode 107
DSO^BJ (107)
Written by.
SUZUKI Satoshi
JVlusic By.
YAMASHITA Kosuke
"Engli Ti Su title By
ktippidn go idem network
Moe
Hitomi' Over there'
Kazus trying to pick a
fight with RAY
Hlold you... 8n't run away,
^and compete against us.
We're not running away
It's no use talking
toy T*
GallkENo\fer ere
Wait a mm le
What do vou want9
Hitomi. ?
Jkre you harassing
RAY again7
pon t try to mdke me
ook like the villain
mjusttelling h that
I wanftt>
aven e
brother's death by settling
it mtv% danc? floor
HI show these guys that
1 better alicer
Mhan the
Kazu...
KEN *
You're just in time
Why don t yo ^iell JhB truth
in front of ^er body? /
Listen, ever
Let's ve your
atte 1i6n here.
You all know who th€5e
wo are, ^on you.
"They're KEN and RAY from the
legendary unit, cfiE iPASS.
My brother was a part
of that unit
Do you all know why
CHEAPASS broke up9
These two were dating
each other, and my
brother got in their way,
so they drove him to
commit suicide
That cant be true1
fiat's not true,
sit. KEN9
RAY?
See9 They cant
say anything.
All the dancers in Osaka
Who were frienOs with
my brother, all said..
That there's no way that
someone who loved dancing
much as EIJI w iiid quit
dancing, and die
They said it's all KEN
nd RAY s fault.
My poor brother was^betrayed
jy.iis es men , an ie
W man he loved, and died a
lonely death, all alone.
Pon t run away, and
compete with me.
iKEN!
ken'
That's not what
happened, is it9
No matter what
Kazu says..
Its not at ail like
that, is it9
KEN 9
Say something
Leave me alone*
You dont know
anything'
Then..
Is It true what
Kazu said9
I'm disappointed
-Be raying your best fnen
4>ver something like that.
I'm
vm
disappointed in you
and in CHEAPASS
JLto'i sjjjia
to wor o a
Did ^clchfBur
old^ttijiro?
hen walJeavin§,Tie-asked
if ^ould4ake£ff4oday.
He said he a ted o
reflect on s life
U ul kuM
lot happ Yfetl wh fi he was
^thB^cting president
Ma ;be^ie^ostconfidence
yVhen ai ;e wants o
e lect ri Is ife,
itmade me in that maybe
s grown up ^littfe.
Up until now; he's ever
reflected cn his life
jDe e ecovers is
pint #after 11<ing
Ilia1 1
iTiope so.
Bytheyvay doesn* itomi
seem depressed o a 9
fs ^fceetf iikith T
I morning
a e s trouble about
hing o o ith
er dancing..
e c e
Y»
I had the urge to have the
miso mackerel here again
I'll have the iunch set.
n s ckerel with extra
(Sic ^ Vegetables
coming right up
Thank you.
Can I sit herfe?
Sure
i ruxjj \
I should explain to you
I don't want you to
misunderstand KEN.
And i don't want to lo
the trust of my students
Can 1 talk to
you later9
ay..
KEN and EIJI were
close friends
Close enough that it
made me jealous
There was never a love
triangle iike Kazu said
ou mean Ihere were no
feelings of love at all7
Why?
ecause.. You're wonderful,
and it woUldn t be strange
for KEN and EIJI to feel
Ifrli Y/aJ l
m happy that you
would say that
_J)utth re weren t
any at all
-Nottft all9
<6f coursi!|Riey both really
cared about me...
ut*is adancer
CHEAP ASS was..
enuin ly three dancers
ho came together
We respected each other,
and the unit that came
J about was like a miracle.
It made me fefel as if i
would never encounter
anything <ike it again
Then wh^ id EIJL.?
I think h6' Is jealous
of me and KEtf
But it had nothing to
do with love, did it7
t was jeaiousy
as a dancer
It was more painful to
iJI than being
je lous of a lover
&5ecause>da tifigVal
every lung to him.
^He convinced himself
fi l^iiad/io talent*
£#henjhe compared himself
Oine nd KEN
eiold lm it wasn't true,
u Iq IJI t sounded
llUie IKtT dfLdbli!
e-star ed to drink
duall , ur danctrfi) on
tage^is lit of svnch.
JJEyehtdally, he started
e!ling,#Y£ry£odv that
EN nd were in lotfe
vith^a n other.
I Jl t 1a us that we were
taking him for a fool,
pnd^hreatened
40 quit dancing
KE abbed hold of him,
^mflola Jiim many times
o say things like
h' f<tarid that he
Yited EIJI to keep
Slicing with us
But he couldn't get
through to EIJI
He ran out, and drove his
motorcycle into the ocean.
That's when KEN
sto ped dancing
ecause e thought it vtas his
fault hat EIJI was hurt
Why ?
Why/von t you and KE f\l tell
eVeryon e*|ruth?
Because KEN told me
not o say anything
ven when the rumors came
out at the reason for
his suicide was a
love triangle
KEN aid we shouldn't
make excuses.
Hethougllltw ^t) 1t-1r
than pebple no ing haf EIJI
comltted suicide becau etie had
i/en up ho,^ !as a dancer
e as trying to uphold
Mi's honor
fte wan ed people to believe
t El I loved dancing
u lil the 1 end
he reason he
KEN ants her to have the
hig es espect for her
? the s a dancer
It's been more th Yi three
years since
Efl
has
danced onstage...
4Je hasn't been able to free
himself from the past.
tven ! think that KEN is
p tting too much blame
on himself
But the truth js that KEN
and ! continue to suffer
In order to overcome th^C
i want the two of us to
dance together again.
i want to appe r on Dancfe
Beat as CMEAPASS
Dancing is our friend
e didn't do anything
o betray pur friend
wanted you to
understand that.
T % iso mackerel
was delicious
lan 'you ior .. .e mea .
Thank you firkin the
time to talkio me.
I'll see you.