CHAPTER 12
I Can't Go to the Festival
Episode 67
The usual town
August, 2007
turned into a
festival town
festival town.
It's a minor festival the year
before the real Tsukuda Festival.
During this time, Ume's "inari"
sushi is in great demand
Will you hurry up?
Everyone's waiting.
Stop nagging
Just hold your horses
Are you all waiting for
the "inari" sushi?
I'm going to take some
to Mari's place
I'm going to pass it out
to all of my customers
I'm going to take some to the
neighborhood association
They look forward
to it every year
Come on in and have
some, Hitomi.
Is it OK?
All right!
This year is just a minor
festival, isn't it?
The real festival is once
every three years, so
since the last real festival
was in 2005, we had
minor festivals in 2006
and 2007. The next real
festival will be in 2008.
This year is already
Next year is the
real festival
You should see the
real festival...
It's something else!
When you see me carrying
the portable shrine,
you'll fall in love with
me all over again
She's not in
love with you yet!
Then she'll fall for
the first time
Pretty sure that's not
happening
The Tsukuda Festival is
the Sumiyoshi Shrine's
1977 Tsukuda Festival
festival that takes place
every three years
1977 (Showa 52)
The Miyamoto f portable
shrine, the right-sided
portable shrine tid many
ot^Wepffera
chance for the e pkyo
to show their do spirit
Many tourists attend
this festival, too.
In the years in between, a
'kage matsuri" (shadow festival)
is held in place
of the real festival.
As Yujiro and the rest
keep saying,
the next real festival will
be held in August 2008
Folks around here
love the festival, so
A lot of my classmates
are coming to town for
the festival even if
it's just a minor one
They can't wait for next year
Come to think of it, Ume
is Tetsuo coming
for the festival?
Of course not, he's too lame
to come home, that guy.
Who's Tetsuo?
Ume's son. He's my
classmate, too
Does he call you?
About once a month
He asks if I'm healthy,
and I say, yes I'm fine
Then, he just hangs up
Stop: Let's not
talk about that
Talking about her son
puts Ume in a bad mood
It's ready! Take as
much as you want.
I'll take 20
Me, too
I'll take the rest
You don't need that many.
There was some situation between
Ume and her son, Tetsuo
that Hitomi didn't know about
Hitomi!
What a surprise, Moe!
Yuka! Junko!
Hey Hitomi!
You came to visit!
Yuka insisted.
I wanted a taste of the
downtown atmosphere.
It's not that we've made
up with each other...
But she pays half the
rent, so even if I
wanted to, I couldn't
kick her out
We put up a curtain, and
try to ignore each other.
Like this..
But today, let's just enjoy
the festival together
Right?
Yeah, you're right
Will you look at that!
It's awesome! It's too
dazzling. I'm blinded.
I can't believe they're
the same living beings
as Ume.. Can you?
Are these your friends,
Hitomi?
From dance school.
This is Keiko.
Nice to meet you.
Good evening
Keiko! Go over there,
and stand with them
What for?
Never mind! Just go!
Why?
Just go!
I don't want to
Wow!
It's blinding!
Stop it already!
It's embarrassing.
Don't do that!
Go ahead and play
I'll watch the kids.
Really?
Maybe I will. Thank you.
Yuka..
Stop it! Enough!
Quit it
Come and have monja.
This is a large serving of
spicy, salted cod roe
it's an extra, extra
large serving
What are you doing here?
We always come here to help
out during the festival.
Why didn't you tell me?
This is Daisuke and Shosuke
from my part-time job.
Good evening.
I'm the older brother.
I'm the younger brother.
I'm the older brother
I'm the younger brother
Good evening.
During the real festival,
when the portable shrines
come through, the spectators
throw water on the carriers
with buckets and hoses
We get soaking wet!
We get soaking
wet, don't we?
We sure do!
Mari, it's all ready.
OK, let's all go over
to Rose's place!
Let's go!
What are you doing?
We're all going over
to Rose's place!
Come on, Moe
Thank you all for
visiting.
You can't go home from
the festival without
hearing this..
Here's Festival Mari singing
the "Matsuri Samba"
After the festival,
the sun is setting.
In the evening, while a
chill wind blows
The old man whose house
burned down and
the old woman whose secret
savings were stolen...
keep sighing with
terrible sadness.
No matter how much they
cry, they won't go home..
No matter how much
they cry
All that's left is the
matsuri (festival)
Go on and dance!
What are you doing?
Dancing is the starting
point of life!
That was fun!
The people in Tsukishima
are awesome, aren't they?
It's been a long time since
I enjoyed dancing this much
I had forgotten
this feeling...
That's true.. Lately, all
I thought about was
getting better at dancing
or getting chosen in
the audition
What are you doing?
They're asking
for an encore!
Encore! Encore!
Come on!
Shall we go? Let's go!
Shota
And Yuria
She looks so good in
her cotton kimono
Excuse me..
I'm sorry! Is it too loud?
No, just the opposite
Can you turn it up
a little?
We can't go to the
festival either
We want to get into the
mood of the festival
Okay... I'll turn it up just
enough so we don't
get scolded
How's this?
That's good
Great
It's light out,
isn't it?
Get back to bed!
Which button is it?
Thank you very much.
Ms Miura.
It was the three of them
who asked me to turn
up the volume.
Lights out!
I'm home...
Mom!
I came to help out
I got off early
You don't have to do that
I'll do it. Go and
enjoy the festival.
It's okay. I don't
want to go
Why not?
You haven't been to one
since you went to
Sapporo, have you?
It's been 17 years!
Go out and enjoy it
It's too overwhelming
I've told you about it, right?
The first time your dad
came here with me
your Grandpa asked him to carry
the portable shrine
You mean when he said,
how can I give Momoko
to a man who can't even
carry a portable shrine?
That was the beginning
of our big fight...
And when I brought you
here when you were
three years old, it was
during the festival too
That's why I can't
really enjoy the festival.
I feel like a stranger,
even hearing the
Tsukuda festival music
Hitomi felt as though
she could feel a little
bit of the pain in
Momoko's heart.
The "shadow festival" was over.
Good morning, Ume!
It's over isn't it?
I feel a bit sad that
the festival is over.
We can't do anything about that...
But when I think how
grand it'll be,
I can't wait for
next year.
Ume?
What happened?
Ume!
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
I'm okay...
No, you're not
You have a fever!
What should I do?
Hang on, Ume
Are you OK?
This time it's a
crisis for Ume