CHAPTER 14
Mother Shows Up
Episode 82
Do you remember
your mother?
Not much.
Do you want
to see her?
Your mother called
and wants to see you.
She's sorry she didn't
call before now
What shall we do?
Do you want
to see her?
What did Shota say?
He wouldn't answer...
When it came to his mother,
he wouldn't say anything.
It's a mild case
of shock
It's quite common in
cases like this.
A lot of different
feelings are getting
entangled with each other..
He's holding back because he
doesn't want to hurt
his foster father and
his attachment to
his foster home...
After all it's? n living
at the Ippongi home
He probably loves his
life in Tsukishima.
Of course, part of it
could be that he can't
believe in his mother's
love since he hasn't
seen her for years.
It's only natural
But I don't think he's
refusing to see her
since his reaction
wasn't that strong.
He's probably having
conflicting feelings
about this right now
Iri e like this, what do
you think I should d0?
Do you think you could
see how Shota feels
while you go about
your everyday life?
We've already told him that
she contacted us.
you could see if
he's agreeable
It might be best to have
Katsutaro see how he
feels since Katsutaro is the
person he trusts most
Do you think you
could do that?
All right. I'll try
Thank you.
Is this you, Shota?
This Akira...this is
Yuria... s s ito
t's s
71& & j on? JiU?
J 3013 1
His o. i sure is
tic ing o it-a lot.
s s t le&all...
s is his
toma
I ma e s orr&ch the
Wefce o je Slking
now liota
Dad!
Hey Shota!
yj JiJl.hliA
Ih jaJ*
wa n t
take this home
with you
We can a gain.
rftonii la
ev Tythmg.
Thank you for coming.
See you again, Shota.
Goodbye
Yuria... Sorry to interrupt
while you're reading, but
it's almost ready, so
c lle^rybUy
How did it go today?
Did Shota say he wants
to see his mother?
He wouldn't say anything.
I knew it! He doesn't
want to see her
We don't know that.
Being told something like
that all of a sudden.
He might have been
so surprised that
he didn't know
what to say
So what are you
going to do?
I'm going to ask
Shota myself
It won't make any
difference...
He doesn't want to talk
about his mother
I want you to eat dinner
like you normally do
I'm acting normal.
No, you're not!
When you laughed yesterday
your face was all scrunched
up like this
You're kidding!
No, I'm not.
I'm not good at this...
It shows in my face
right away
I'm not good at it either
but I don't want Akira
and Yuria to worry.
At least until everything
is straightened out
Shota's been through
a lot today, so
I want you to try
to cheer him up
Do goodjT)..
Smile!
That's it.
How did you lose that
smile so fast?
Keep it in place
After dinner..
Shota
Can you come down
for a minute?
Okay
Akira
Shota went to the child care
counseling center today
h o
yi?i Sldj
What did you talk about
when you went to the
child care counseling
center today?
They kept me company
while I drew pictures.
Is that T! Hit?
Did you talk about
your mother
We did.
They told me your mother
contacted the child care
counseling center and said
she wants to see you.
What are you going to do?
Will you see her?
You don't have to
answer right now
Its OK then
If you have homework
and finish it
It's just as I thought
He doesn't want to see her
Why not?
As soon as you mentioned
his mother, I could
see him distance
himself from you.
You sound like a
psychologist.
That's what you call...
What are you talking about?
There's a proverb
that fits that...
You know which
one, don't you?
No, I don't.
Are you home, Katsu?
What was that
saying...
You know the one..
What are you
talking about?
You know... when an
amateur acts like
he knows everything, and
sticks his nose in all
kinds of things, and
ends up getting hurt.
I know which one!
"Bystanders see more
than the players"
That's not it...
It's the opposite.
That saying means that
when you're playing
chess or "no" the audience
can see what's going to
happen before the player
actually sees it.
That's right.
It says that it's better
to be a bystander.
I'm talking about
just the opposite.
You're right
It's the opposite
I got it...
"A little knowledge is
a dangerous thing"
That's right!
That's it.
That's what you were
doing just now
I don't understand,
but it's OK
Are you going
to Matsuri?
It's empty
right now
Maybe I'll go
with you
I need a change of pace.
Let's go
We're going then.
See you
Shota... What did you
talk to Dad about?
Nothing
What happened at
the center..?
You went there today,
didn't you?
Nothing.
Is something wrong
with Hitomi?
No... Why?
She was acting strange
at work today
She seemed to be riled up
about something.
She kept making mistakes
with the orders.
Eventually, the f^ss
scolded her and
told her to go
home early
Is she worried
about something?
They just won the dance
contest, so it doesn't
have anything to with
that, but maybe there's
something at home that
she's worried about
That's what I think.
You're absolutely right.
Aren't I?
Actually
Promise you won't talk
about this with anyone.
You know I won't...
t'inlmown forkee ing
my mouttrshtft
You poor man
Okay
Shota's mother called the
counseling center and
told them that she wants
to take Shota back.
foufneari the mother that
I^lia nt heard frdrnV
She disappeared and they
couldn't contact her
all this time
And did you tell
Shota about that?
I took him to the counseling
center today and the people
there explained what happened,
and asked him if he wants
to see her.
And?
He wouldn't say anything.
;ftntl I jsked him *t)out
mys 1f earlier.
Ht vas4h~^ame thing...
He wouldn't say anything.
He doesn't want
to see her
The way she abandoned him
for all these years...
What did you expect?
She's a terrible mother
Leaving him for someone
else to raise, and when
she wants to see him, she's
suddenly his mother..
You must be kidding.
You're saying the same
thing Hitomi said
Hitomi's only 20, so
I can understand how
lie cantiatfe^n opinion
ike that out
Yoti'rgjan&lint, so don't you
have a more mature opinion?
It doesn't matter whether
you're 20 or an adult...
When you what happened
Nlrn&ke ^ou^ngry.
That's called human
compassion
It may not be
that simple
That's right.
I agree with you
His mother may have had
her reasons for what
she did, and as for Shota,
she is his mother.
I'm pretty sure he
wants to see her
But it's hard for him to
deal with his feelings
after hearing about it
from you all of
a sudden like this.
(iViave iotianfi A*
to you, Man..
Just what I'd expect
from you
I agree with you.
jSo just going to wait
until Shota can put his
feelings into words.
You're wasting
your time
Why?
Shota hates his mother
You're so simple-minded
I said you're
simple-minded
Promise that you won't
tell anyone else
about this, okay?
Not a word!
I won't say
anything.
Hitomi began to realize
that what Shota was
feeling wasn't as simple
as she thought