CHAPTER 12
Can't Go to the Festival
Episode 69
I'm worried about you.
I don't want anything to
happen to you while
you're living all alone.
It's a given this kind
of thing will happen...
Bothering our
neighbors like this.
We have a room for you
It'll be a lot easier
for you than living
here in the tenement
I don't want to
No matter what anyone
says, I love it here
in the tenement
Just go home already
You'll raise my fever
I'll leave for today
But I'm coming back
I'll leave this here - a melon.
I don't want your melon.
It cost $100, you know!
It looks like Ume's son Tetsuo
came to talk
Ume into coming to
live with him
Don't you have more
to say to her?
I better go home, given
what she said
I'm sorry you had
to hear that
It's okay
Since you're here, can't we
talk some more before
you go home?
I want to hear more about
that shopping mall, too
How about going over
to Makoto's place?
We can have beer
and monja
Monja? Sounds good
Shall we go?
Let's go
Mom! I'm going home!
Hitomi! Take care
of Ume
Okay
Let's go.
Hitomi
Let the children
eat the melon
Is that OK?
It's ready,
isn't it?
Here goes
Yum
It's really good
Monja is the best
Of course, it's
Tsukishima's specialty
Tetsuo...when was that,
the New Year's when you
brought your wife and
kid over here?
When we ran into each other
The time when I wanted to
eat monja, and my wife
said "We're going to a
restaurant in Ginza."
That's right, that was it.
Why didn't you push a little
more to get your wife
to stay and have monja
I was waiting for you to
tell her that you were
a Tsukishima man, and
want to eat "monja"
And she should eat
it too!
There's no way around it
My wife just doesn't have
any understanding of
what common
people eat.
It's not like it's
substandard!
What do you eat at home --
French and Italian cuisine?
Something like that.
My wife loves to cook,
so I promised to come
home to eat dinner at
home every night
She's going to make me
eat dinner when I get
home today, too.
If she finds out that
I ate something like
this, there'll be
a big fuss
I wonder if she'll
smell it on me!
I guess it's OK.
She's the. daughter of a
company director, isn't she?
He was, but now he's
retired, so he's not
connected with the company
anymore.
When we built our house, he
paid the deposit
without hesitation. So I try
to keep him happy
You've changed, Tetsuo...
You were never like
this before
What was I like?
We used to play pranks
together all the time
On Katsu, too.
Like what?
That was before we got
to middle school
While Katsu was in the
bathroom, we changed
the prices on the
shirts in the store
That's right. I remember
We changed them to $1000
or $10,000.
What a thing to do.
When he found out,
he got really mad
He sure did
Katsu's really scary
when he's angry.
You really see steam
rising from his head
He lectured us until
we cried
He really lit into us.
He said, "What would
happen if customers
really paid $10,000?"
If I got a $10,000
for a $30 shirt,
that would be fraud!
Do you want people
to call me a fraud?
Did you hear me?
Makoto!
Tetsuo!
We're sorry
But that's the kind of
friends we used to be.
You used to love festivals
when you were a kid.
You promised that we would
carry the portable shrine
when we grew up..
But you don't even manage
to watch the festivals
**If you're drunk,
maybe you'll do it?**
You had too much
to drink, Makoto.
I'm sorry, Tetsuo
That's just the way it is
What is?
That's the path I chose
Unlike you, I wanted to
get out of Tsukishima
I wanted to become a
success in something
in the big world
outside of Tsukishima
I thought my mom would
be happy if I did
But the plan
didn't work that way
No matter how much
success or how
big a house I have, it
doesn't please my mom
That's the source
of my troubles.
He wasn't a bad kid
to from the start.
He studied hard, so
he could make me happy
He got into a good company
and married a young lady
from a rich family.
But from about that time
we couldn't agree
on anything...
I don't think being rich
makes you important.
And I don't just because
you have a grand house,
you'll be happy.
But that's how he came
to think.
Maybe he had a hard time when
he went out into the world.
I just don't know
Maybe there's also
some good parts.
Hitomi
I'm going to sleep now
Thank you.
Are you sure it's OK
for me to take this?
You eat it for me.
Well then, thank you
Good night.
It wasn't that they truly
hated each other
Not being able to agree on
things, and different ways
of thinking create a chasm
between parent and child
A few days later
Ume had recovered.
Good morning, Hitomi
Ume! Are you okay?
Thanks to you. I'm even
better than before.
I'm so glad!
How did it go?
No good, huh?
I want to go back
to Sapporo.
Don't say things
like that!
Face forward,
face forward!
I'm back
Welcome bacK
Ms. Ippongi...
Yes
I'm getting an earful from
the head office
They want to know what
is going on in
the Tokyo office!
You have to do something
to get closer
to your sales goal!
Don't you get it? We
have to get more stores
to carry our products!
I'll make every effort.
It's making my
stomach hurt.
Are you alright?
I wish he wouldn't blame
his stomachache on me.
All he has to do is take
stomach medicine for it
Suzuran Cosmetics..
This is Ippongi.
Tetsuo..
Momo..
Tetsuo!
I'm sorry to be late when
I'm the one who called you
No worries, I was
happy you called
A coffee please.
Getting right to it, about
that new shopping center
I thought I'd tell you
about our products...
That's not what I came to
talk with you about today
Then what did you
want to talk about?
My mom got sick, didn't she?
So I thought now would be
a good time to convince
her to come and live
with us
her spirits are
weak right now, too
Maybe so, but...
So I need your help to
get my mom to lean
towards living with us.
Me?
If possible, Hitomi, too
Hitomi, too?
I'll think about space
in the shopping center
One Sunday soon, I think
I'll bring my wife and son
to Tsukishima
I'll use the excuse of
celebrating her recovery
from her illness..
I'll order a super deluxe
portion of chirashi sushi
from a sushi shop and
we can eat together
in harmony
That sounds good.
Why don't you do that right away?
It won't be that smooth!
My mom hasn't ever
even let my wife
come into her house.
SO it's going to be really
hard just to get her to
agree to this arrangement.
Just to get her
to eat sushi?
That's right
So I want you to
help make it work
I guess I could do that
The main point is to
spend time in harmony
We've never eaten a meal
together before, so
we probably won't
have much to talk about
That's where you come in
Me and Hitomi?
Then I'll look for the
right timing to bring
up the subject of coming
to live with us.
Then I need you
to back me up
I'll think about the
tenant space
Mom, you agreed to it?
Of course..isn't it
a good thing?
For a mother and son
to live together.
Don't decide that
on your own!
VVhy are you siding with
Tetsuo anyway?