TEr!5
Tearstained Towel Blanket"
"Episode 88
)ltr j Kl (88)
Shota's tow 1 blanket?
What's wrong?
Shotas towel l^nket
is missing, nd
Shota s rra. ing a big fuss
You mean the towel blanket that
Shota treasured because
it held memories
of his moti^r..?
That's right
Hurry, and go. Don't
worry "bout us
Ym sorry.
I d better go.
Thank ^oujor the meal
I'm sorry
Be careful
She's booking after the f "Ster
children, too, isn't she
That's right.
It ust be rough Jiel ing
Po/aise children ^ d
training tobe a dancer
Drink up!
And eat o s, too
I'm home!
It's fsally terrible.
^h 1a scrying.
4A/hat rey lidoin 9
I thought it might be mixed
in with the laundry.
But! thought Shota had
put it away tn alDox
He did,;but
You're right! It's gone.
We looked everywhere
in this foom.
Betwe 7i the bedding, and
underlhe bed,-too.
Did he take it out
fromtiere?
He^aid lie did
After that time, he put it away
i Ihe box^nd o 1y looked
at it once in a while.
Then why is jt .gone?
Don't cry, Shota
Just wait. I'll find
it for yod
What are you doing?
I'm looking for Shota's
towel blanket.
I don't think it's here
When I hung out the laundry,
i didn't see it
It might have fallen out
here by mistake
Like the last time
Yuria..
on'Mnow
w ^re it is
Thenwh id you Suldn'tyou
look meln the eye just now?
N Ireaso
it's over here,
isn't it?
It's not there
Then let me look
I found it
What's this?
I don't know
Why did you hide it?
Because
you don't need
it anymore
You nave o r others w
Yuria
Look after im. Akira
Yuria...
Cornfe downstairs, and
talk to me
Yuria
Think really hard about
your feelings
Aren't you feeling lonely
because Shota might be
leaving this house?
If tha's true, th Vi what
^BlTf e doing is the
opposite of what
ou're feeling.
What you're doing is
jus ormenting him
You kno//^ou:shouldnt
do that,<fon't you?
You s "buld get along with
S^a while he's herfc.
Think abodtjt really
carefully ^andif you
feel bad about what you
did to Shota, t
apologize to him
That's all.
Her feelings are so mixed
up right jio ~tHS!>she
doing stran effitn s
What?
jn sorry £both
what! did.
I won't do jt fiymore
_Jt*s Sunfaay, YidTObmi
aftdfheoth ts are
aboutto gouptih stagfe
iillic fjcpai unciii c
ftltfij
If the children see you
itJIget c "Sbtic,
Gobd morning
I'll check the a dierice,
and give you he cue
from the other side.
If tfi&t's thefca e, h
s 'ould have made this
a little bigger,
don't yo hink9
I e ul! if
yj i UJ
It's ret y heav^
ilL^i lUf
Wa t mute
Hitomi.
"Mom!
e!lo»
ou came?
I was here on busin .ss
anyway.
That' ""Shoia
t "ac:
Shota s mother
Which means the guy
next to her is...
Iter fiance
He as playing with
Shota the oth rday.
rfe's the
Imaza o.
It's a restauran
in AVasaka
He sells ento IGnr >S
in the b^serne.i
this department's o?e
It's time..
go
While m da n , ill
^lttJ^ JJliIJ Jitf
rmv/Offte«J -]«3o»ii v/ii-ii
if tjMnj
It's fo hoia s saKe.
Hitomi!
yia iajjiiliij jii yj JJ
Wait a minSlel
e.lo, verybody'
Vpu don't sound to6
enthusiastic.
Onte retime'
Hello'
Thatwa e I bod.
eday
a'lJ'
Jj) «j) 3 iij :3»u' >
lease a c nd
enjoy notlhe "Maneki Neko,''
but the "Mayug ~Neko '
I reall^jfeel bad'
about it, but..
My tnomis...
h idn't gu say
something sooner?
You knew about Shota
from the beginning.
1 lid. but...
I'm really sorry
In \i
y case..
It's going to be a little hard
for us to get married now..
I'm sorry... Really sorry
What? They're not ,
getting married?
That' "Hflhat he said.
Why?
mother s against
the marriage
^e never old his mother
about Shota
She must ha\/e said some
harsh thingfe onsi e in
she's the owner of an old,
traditional restaur n
Wait a minute..
If they're no etting
marrie T^her what's
going to happen to hoia?
It doesn't have anything
to do with Shota, does it?
Even if his mother doesn't
get married she can
still take him back,
can't she?
I suppose, but..
Hitomi.. Encore'
o on, Hitomi!
Thanks.
Even after she went home,
Hitomi didn't mention
what had happened.
Shota. what are
you rriaking?
A house
What hSuse?
T "ft house
This house?
The ippongi house.
is is the%itting?oom, and
when you go upstairs,
his is my room
Right here
This room.
Shfe was hoping that her
do "hts would end
as just doubts
a ug
IT osuke