CHAPTER 12
Can't Go to the Festival
Episode 68
Ume!
Ume. What's wrong?
Are you okay?
I'm OK.
No, you're not
You have a fever.
What am I going to do?
Hang on, Ume!
The morning after the festival,
Ume collapsed
Ume
Ume?
What about Ume?
She has a fever
and collapsed
W VeliiVe* ver here
stay there and take
care of her
Wait a minute. I'll e
you talk to Yujiro
Hello... How is she?
What am I going to do?
I put her to bed
MOlf 10|
You'd better call a doctor
Ume might say she's okay,
but that's how she is
We don't want to take chances,
especially at her age.
How is she?
It's probably just a
summer cold...
Once her fever goes down,
she'll be fine.
It's ri Iseriodsie. ough o
pOt lir in the s 1 a
Make sure she drinks
lots of liquid, and
give her something nutritious and
easy to digest
All right.
The fatigue must
be catching up with you
With helping Katsutaro,
and all the work you
did for the festival
re you going to
a ecareo
neig T)ors are for
Don't you have enough
to do already?
Taking care of the children,
and with Katsutaro in
the hospital... If you
overdo it, you'll
collapse again.
I know.
Why don't you call
your son, Ume?
Let him take care of you.
Never mind. I don't need
a son like him
You mean you still
don't get along?
That's not good at
a time like this.
You know what they say,
When you grow old,
Ii len to your
children
Why don't you use this
as a chance to have
him look after you?
He and I don't get along
It's easier being alone.
You should at least
give him a call.
Even if you don't get
along, family is family.
This is a summer greeting
card he sent to me
There's his cell
phone number
Give him a call!
But won't Ume be upset
if we do that?
It doesn't matter if
she gets upset
At a time like this, you
need to notify the family
Isn't that right? Then give
him a call, Makoto
You want me to?
Of course! You're his
classmate aren't you ?
It would better if you
do it instead of Ume.
You think so?
But he's the department head
at some big company now.
I haven't talked
to him recently
Do you think I should
use polite language?
That's not necessary.
Just start off with "Hey,
it's been a while"
Something like that
I see. Ail right.
Do you have the number?
That's right..
Gi eme a Teak.
Can you do it?
Wrong number
Department Head Yokoyama..
It's time for the
department meeting
Let me take a short
break first
I've been in a meeting with the
vice president all morning
Yokoyama Tetsuo
I've been in a meeting with the
vice president all morning
Yokoyama Tetsuo
Give me five minutes.
This is Yokoyama
Hey! It's been a while.
It's me.
It's me... It's me...
He hung up
You have to give
your name first..
Didn't I tell him
my name?
You just kept saying
It's me, it's me.'
I thought I told
him my name.
Hello!
I'm sorry, but I don't
know any Makoto..
Makoto?
It's you! It's been
a while
My mom?
I just thought I should
let you know..
No, not at all...
Excuse me. I'm sorry to
bother you at work.
OK, goodbye
What did he say
All he said was "I see.
Thank you very much."
Did he say anything about...
He didn't mention
anything like that
He said something
about being busy
I needfc rin i /a er
We have barley tea.
His wife is the daughter
of a company director?
ha's after that
they started favoring him,
and he moving
up the company ladder
his father-in-law put down
the deposit on their
big mansion, too.
Do you think he
^len^etk d?
That's possible. I think
it's very visible
Orice~beforerTetsuoi)roug t
t S.Yijf} Jjl» 0 1
1 n ew ear a
I ran into them on
their way home
I told him that our shop
was open, so to stop by
and have monja
Tetsuo looked like he
wanted to, but..
His wife didn't
want to?
That's right.
She said, "We have an
engagement to have
dinner in Ginza today"
and she pulled Tetsuo
by the arm.
He brushed her arm off,
and told her, "I'm a
Tsukishima man, and
I want to eat monja
and I'm going to eat it
And so will our son"
He said that?
No, he didn't
He just gave in to his
wife, and told me
"We're going to
Ginza today"
He had his nose in the air
and went off to Ginza.
He's definitely
hen-pecked
I wonder if that's what Ume's
upset with Tetsuo about
He's turned his back on
Tsukishima, and let
his wife run the roost
Do you mean the typical
frpu 1 between the
bride and the mother-in-law?
That, too
You can tell that his wife
and Ume won't get along.
That's true..
Hey there Yurie!
Did you go to the pool?
I swam 27 yards.
That's great.
We're going to see a
play, aren't we?
Want to, but.
Go ahead. I'll keep
an eye on Ume
I'll watch the store
Are you sure?
Shall we go after
lunch then?
Aren't you glad?
Tha \ id
Both Ume and her son
don't get along
me i n jseem to want
^o Hk "bdtit irso ..
^oltiidtf sk.
Has it always
been like that?
No... when he was little, he
was a good son to them
When he was in middle
school, and his dad
^itl, p eally started
£tudyirv ^ird...
e a nedjiistiiitio "by
ell ennglhe newspaper
h ,1i6sa ed w tking, she told
uU Vrib'U ail t> 1
ffobukiza^eatfer^hen he
Is fir t paycheck.
I think he started acting
pd toward her after
^he go!jnarnecl.
o atrer^h lihe
irU Stances,
re tja TJ TiildWe
oirylo ^t«along.
You should talk, Grandpa!
Shota... Did you finish
your drawing
I'm almost done
/Jltf JfOjUdJUJ
He' UVrr ralTdChild...
my on.
My son and my daughter
This is my granddaughter
Good evening!
Hello, Momoko.
Where's Hitomi? tho g .
tifcome-fMd he.p o
She's over at
Ume's place.
as a lever soHitomi
we.. loja^e careof^er.
3><fJ5m in charge of
the children tonight.
Is that right?
Let's eat
I e ... So they o
e nere
Thank you for the meal
You've gotten your
appetite back
And^our feyer'^o n, o
It must be the median
Here you go.
Th Tifs
MW wash these.
M feel bad letting
tielp out, too,Tvlor~b
What are you saying, what
are neighbors for?
It's probably Dad's fault
that you got sick.
Making you work because he
had to stay in the hospital
Why couldn't he get hurt without
dragging everybody else into it?
That's not true
It's just the 'demon
illness"
Good evening
I'll get it.
Who are you?
Ume's son... This is
my home
Ume
Your son
It's been a while, Mom
Makoto told me
Tetsuo!
Momoko!
It's been a while
This is my daughter
Is that right?
Pleased to meet you
I'm Hitomi
I'm Yokoyama.
rji ggftt
Here you go.
Thank you... It should be
the other way around.
Why didn't you
tell me you were coming?
Why should I tell you?
I'm your son
¥out:ou!dtiavec"1l U before
one of the neighbors
She didn't want
you to worry
It really has been a
long time, hasn't it?
When did you come here?
months ... I have
choffic .enow
What about you?
I'm still working for the
real estate company
You're an important man
now, aren't you?
I'm working on a shopping
development in Tama
that will in snt-cf
Ijzui firmiu
I'm in charge of getting
tenants for the shopping
center, so I spend
everyday talking
to people all the time
Hitomi...
t eb
Will you take the
tea away?
He'll be leaving soon.
What are you saying?
You've hardly talked yet
I don't have anything
to say to you
I know what you're
going to say already
I'm worried about you
I don't want anything to
happen to you.
you're living all alone.
It's already happened..
You have to bother our
neighbors like this
We have a room for you
It'll be a lot easier
for you than living
here in the tenement.
I don't want to
No matter what anyone
says, I love it here
in the tenement.
Just go home already
You'll make me worse
4% leave o 68a
But I'm coming back.
I'll leave theYnel~"*tiere.
don't want v^r .
it costs 11boo ^n!
Excuse me.
Goodbye.