CHAPTER 17
Dance is Life
Episode 98
Written by
SUZUKI Satoshi
Music by
YAMASHITA Kosuke
English Subtitle By
NIPPON GOLDEN NETWORK
Yuka's father's company went
bankrupt last month
Didn't he have a number
of famous restaurants
Why didn't my dad or
my mom let me know?
They said your dad's
restaurants were
behind the times
A lot of fashionable
restaurants geared
for young people have
been opening up
Is that why the company
went out of business?
Your dad was so determined
to overcome it that he
opened more new
restaurants
He said he would show them
that he had what it took
But it was a mistake
I didn't know about
it until today
He told me not
to tell you.
He was ashamed to have
you see him like this
so he even told me not to
tell you about this place
A long time ago, your dad
said that there were
stairs in this world, and
he was going up
those stairs. Climbing
higher and higher up
those stairs made him
so happy, and when he
let me work in the
restaurant, it made
me happy, too
I felt like I was climbing up
those stairs along with him.
While we doing that, neither
of us knew how we should
deal with you, so we just let
you do what you wanted.
When you said you were
going to quit ballet,
and try street dancing.
And when you said you wanted
money to rent a studio
We let you do what
you wanted
We cant do anything
for you anymore.
That's not what I
wanted to hear
Yuka...
I'm home.
Dad.
Yuka!
Hibino ol me
This is Hitomi. One of
her dance friends
Pleased to meet you.
Here
Dad
Let's talk, Dad
It's been a while since
we've seen each other...
Let's talk about what
you're going to do now
It has nothing to
do with you
Of course it does!
I'm your daughter!
What are you going
to do now?
Don't you have a
lot of debts7
Your mom and I will work,
and repay the debts.
How?
My friend is opening
a restaurant..
We'll work for him
We'll manage somehow.
That's how I got started
when I was young
Then I'll work,
and help out
Why would you?
I want to help!
Never mind. This is
our problem
What do vou mean
by "our" problem?
Aren't I a part of
this family, too?
You just do what
you want to do!
That's what we've let
you do all this time
She's such a troublesome
daughter
She started rebelling
against us since she
got into high school
On top of that, she
ran away from home
We let her do whatever
she wanted to
We let her dance
We gave her as much money
as she asked ior
That's not what I wanted.
Then what did you want?
Yuka!
He got what he deserves
All he t Blight about
is making money
So when the money is gone,
he has nothing left
Nothing at all
It was fun when
I was little...
Before my father started
his own business
He was a hired manager
for a restaurant.
We lived in a condo about
the same size as the
one we saw today.
But on his days off, we used
to watch television together.
I used to like
Amuro Namie
So when I used to imitate
her and dance, he'd
laugh, and clap his hands
He told me how
good I was
He'd praise me
Mom used to smile a lot
It was fun back then.
But somewhere along the line,
something went wrong.
We turned into a family who
wouldn't even tell their
own daughter that something
this terrible happened.
YUka!
I'm sorry..
I need to be alone
for a while
Let's talk about practice.
We're going to turn in
our entry tomorrow
You have it, don't
you, Hitomi7
Can you hold off for
a little while?
I can't think about
dancing right now
Don't say strange
things like that
I don't have time
to be dancing
That has nothing to do
with this, does it?
I just can't think about
dancing right now.
Listen here..
Why are you acting like
the spoiled little
rich girl now?
Didn't you say farewell
to that spoiled little
rich girl when you left that
mansion, and came here?
When I saw that,
I saw you in a new light..
I thought you had
a lot of spunk
jjij nv
3 M.
iHng e sailed
little rich girl again?
No matter what you say now,
you don't have a mansion
to go back to anymore
After living here with
you for 10 months and
dancing with you,
I had to admire you
We've urged each other on.
I thought we were friends
who would aim for the
o together
e anl do it
without you
igh *
e a e ROSE MARY unless
three i s are together
Then why don't you
change your name?
To ROSE TEA or
ROSE GARDEN ?
Get out
Hello..
Dad?
I'm fine
Why are you calling all
of a sudden?
What? Mom?
Okay.. I'll be
right there
What's wrong?
My mom got into an
auto accident
She was hit by a car
Utsunomiya...Are you
going there now?
I'm worried, so I thought
I'd go with her
I m sorry, but can
you make dinner?
All right,
I'll tell Dad
Thanks
Let's go, Hitomi.
Be sure to tell
Grandpa
Talk to you later.
Be careful
The two of them headed for
the hospital in Utsunomiya
Junko's parents run a small
gyoza restaurant here
in Utsunomiya
Junko
How's Mom?
They're treating her now
It's not life-threatening
It's not?
Who's this?
My name is Hitomi.
I'm a friend of Junko's
from dance school.
She was worried, so
she came with me
You were
I'm Junko's father
What happened?
The car hit her on
the right side
Your mom came out from
the street suddenly
He hit his brakes, but he
couldn't avoid her
The driver is at the
police station now
So it was due to Mom's
carelessness7
So it seems.
She's used to walking
along that street
and it seems her mind
was on something else
She was thinking
about you
Oh, it's you
Mom was worried
about you
It's been almost a year
since you went to Tokyo,
but you haven't come out
on television yet
Keiichi.. Never mind
that. Say "hello"
to Hitomi, Junko's
friend from dance school
Pleased to meet you
I'm Junko's older
brother Keiichi
He works at a bank.
He's the eldest son, but
he's not going to take
over the restaurant
You sound so old-fashioned.
Rather than selling 300-yen
gyoza, I'm more suited
to moving 30 million yen
from right to left.
Are you a dancer too?
I'm surprised you want
to do something like that
You cant make
any money that way
Junko riled to or e s
but she quit, and went to
Tokyo to chase a dream
It will never come true
It's beyond her
Was Mom that worried
about me?
A iittle
It's not just that
With just your mom and me,
it's hard to increase our sales
And I can't push myself
like I did before
So if she got hurt because
she was thinking about
that, and not paying
attention, then
it's my fault that
she got hurt
Mr Hashimoto
We finished treating
her, but the doctor
wants to explain her
condition to you
i sctr
If you'll excuse us..
Will you wait here
for a while/
It looks like Junko has
family problems, too!