CHAPTER 16
Goodbye Shota
Episode 92
Written by
SUZUKI Satoshi
Music by
YAMASHITA Kosuke
English Subtitle by
NIPPON GOLDEN NETWORK
Mikie?
What's wrong?
This song.
It's Miyako Harumi's "Anko
Tsubaki wa Koi no Hana."
When I was little my father
used to sing it ail the time
Anko Tsubaki..
What do you want to hear?
You were waiting for him,
weren't you7
Do you know the s fig
' ftkoTsublci..."?
Sure, Anko Tsubaki
wa Koi no Hana"
That's the one.
It's a nice song
It's a famous song
from the Showa era
In answer to your
request..
You don't have to sing it
What's the song about?
What does the "anko" in
Anko Tsubaki" mean?
It's the sweet bean paste
The honey from the "tsubaki"
(camellia) is so sweet it's
like anko. That's what
the song is about
You're wrong
Don't teach he*
the wrong thing.
Then what is it about?
Anko is the name of
the girl who picks
the tsubaki (camellia)
Tsubaki abura (camellia
oil) is the specialty of
Izu Oshima, isn't it?
it's an Izu Oshima song
It's an Island, so
even the mail came by boat
That's why part of the
song is "carrying the
letter three days late."
Don't sing
You'll disturb
the neighbors
I want to sing
You'd better not sing
If you do, Ume will
fall down
Good night!
Don't pinch my ear!
Ouch! That hurts!
Several days later, Hitomi
went to the child care
counseling center
They told her that Mikie had
something to tell her
We talked about my father
tiia JUrfi
That he was alive and
living in his home town.
By chance, is it
Izu Oshima
That's right,
How did you know?
Anko Tsubaki...
I learned that it's an
Izu Oshima song.
You told me, didn't you...
That you thought
I should see him.
When I heard that song in the
coffee shop, I realized
that I missed my father
I tried calling him
You did? And?
He was surprised, but it
sounded like he was happy
He's a fisherman
on the island
When I told him about
me and Shota, he said
he'll come to Tokyo
and meet us.
Isn't it great?
We Jho would
be a good idea.
I'm sorry to worry you
I'm a little nervous, but
I'm going to meet him.
Thank you, Hitomi
Thanks to you, I
made up my mind
So Mikie's going to
meet her father?
He's coming all the way
here from Izu Oshima
Mikie said that she felt
her father deserted her
when she wa little
So if she meets with him,
and they can make up,
she might settle down
a little bit
But will it be that easy?
You don't think
it will work out?
It's hard when it comes to
a father and daughter
Once the relationship
falls apart, it's hard
to mend the relationship
You're talking about
you and Mom
I hope he's a nice man
That "Anko Tsubaki" father.
•s t
I'm leaving!
It's a g tSfhhin
It'll be a relief for
Shota's mother if
sees her father after all
this time and they can
clear the air
between them
No matter what you say,
you can rely most
on your parents,
isn't it so?
But Grandpa's worried that
if they meet, they'll
just start fighting
He's talking
about himself
Don't worry, Hitomi...
A father and daughter
like those two don't
come along too often.
That's true
a ing o zu t)sh m .
The fish from here is
delicious, isn't it?
They tna e "kusa^a" salted,
sun-dried fish here
That's right.
Yout: n "tch n obster,
snapper, <1 ing and
bro /n-stripe tk Y 1
HttS treasure house
of fish, sn I
And 'a tiitab '
her al greens
t delicious when you
eeo ry it, isn't it
It's a nice place..
if he's a fisherman mg
ni e place like that
I'm sure he's a nice man.
The way your parents raise
you has a lot to do with
the way you raise your
own child, doesn't it?
A child's problem is
the parent's problem,
and it all comes back to the
parent, doesn't it?
Shota's mother, and her
fisherman father
You mean the "Anko Tsubaki" dad?
That's right
If things work out between
those two, then it'll
help Shota and his mother
to feel more secure
I hope "Anko Tsubaki" helps
to work things out.
We don't need a musical
accompaniment
Doesn't that song get
stuck in your head?
It does
The part after that...
That's it
Sending a letter to the
one you love, but no
answer comes back
A one-way letter.
That's pretty fanciful...
I sent Mari a
one-way letter
Mari, it's time for an
answer to come back.
Just kidding.
Don't get swept up in
the moment and say
something strange
You figured it out?
dl .
I'm embarrassed
He's turning red...and
it's not the sake.
Mikie asmffeting
<fa o ay
Mikie.
You've grown up
You're a grown
woman now
Of course, after you left,
I grew up, and had a child
of my own
I can't say anything when you
say something like that
Why did you leave me?
Why did you leave us behind
and go to the island7
Didn't your mother
say anything?
She said you hated Tokyo,
so you left us and ran back
to the island
V h st9 eres
some. Ing now,
efTtell me.
About the time their land
3 iwvliy ) iin;^
Mt. Mihara ruled..
Mt Mihara
In 1986, when you
were seven
My siblings and relatives were
fishermen on the island
Their houses and boats
were all destroyed
No matter ov m mil y
they had, it wasn't enough
So they "fere was
some way I could helpi m
& r JbLii
back to the island
I wa 1idinig\}Urom
Tiy low salary, so
your mom and I were
always fighting
li j) uvfoi-
two years.
We  ti m toward
ime of it, too, but
I couldn't stop
and turn my
back on them
So we in I t a divorce,
Ill J I v^jtf >i
ihjiJ iy m sofiff
So if you and your mother
thought I abandoned
you, then I guess it
can't be helped
Ui
Gi forgot about
pjfctf 1 3
Out of all the pictures
I have, this one is the
one where you can see
your face clearly
he BStJta e it with
me,#Tiflloo . it while
ftd Jj) iiia }
a .
I'm really sorry, Mikie
I'm sorry you had
to suffer
If you can forgive me,
will you come and
live with me on
the island?
Let's put an end to this
loneliness already
Will the two of you come,
and live with me ..?
Bring Shota with you.