CHAPTER 20
The Next Step
Episode 115
Written by
SUZUKI Satoshi
MuSic by
YAMASHITA Kosuke
When we finished dancing
I really felt great
because I gave it everything
I had, and it felt like
we had become one
April, 2008
Outlays after Dance Beat,
Hitomi's ankle had
completely healed
For now, Hitomi was going
to do her best with
the housework.
This is for Akira..
And this is for Yuria
Congratulations to you both
on entering new schools
Thank you
Open it
it's a pen case
It's a handkerchief set
Do your best in middle
school and high school
Thank you
Also, I brought cake
Let's eat it together.
Thank you, Keiko
They're my dear little
brother and little sister
I have an announcement
to make today.
What is it?
I changed hospitals
I'm going to be working
in Tsukiji now
You mean the hospital I
was in when I broke my leg?
So I'll be able to stop by
here from time to time
Is that right?
In that case
--din r w We i o orks
our way to or from work
I pi Jiappy to «se you
Speaking of Hitomi
Where is she?
She's taking in
the laundry
But it sure is taking
her a long time
Hitomi...?
Hitomi
Keiko
What were you daydreaming
about?
You were taking in the
la n fy w r4 1 o 9
I was just thinking
about something
About what?
There was a big dance
competition called
Dance Beat,4>i]t4t'£over 1m
I heard about it...
You didn't make it through
the preliminaries
It's too bad,
isn't it?
I see.. So you were thinking
about your frustration
No, not that.
I did all that
I could do.
the y d n't you lobk more like
ypu compli Tied something7
But I feel a little sad..
Like it's spring, but the
autumn winds are blowing
In other words, it's the
sadness you feel after
the festival is over
After the festival
fbu lit arkT all
that energy yoy built
up inside on the stage
that day, and burned out.
After a festival, I feel
like an empty shell
with all my spirit gone
You may be right.
Listen to this
Ull J y
Th dness after
the festival ends
It comes eve
Are you depressed?
-mum? .
Thank you!
What did you want
to talk about?
Do you want a beer?
I'm sorry... We'll have
a drink after we talk
I want to talk before
we get drunk.
YUZO
I told you once before
job was to make you ay
fDIIHetiggtimanrsO
ou take over
Ishida Shoten.
Listen carefully...
At the end of this year,
I'm going to retire as
the president of
Ishida Shoten
So starting next year, you'll
be the president
One day, you me hotae
drunk, and told me...
Dad, I love dried
bonify, and I'm going
oTSioi. I'm going to show
you I can do it!
So watch me."
It made me happy to
hear you say that
I feel like I've been
waiting years for
Ishida Shoten has a lot of
customers who say that
it has to ep r ne bonito
or they won t • y any
it means you have to treasure
those /eg 0 a s omfers
But from n // on, t has
to&ejnore i lan thai
We havfe to ke g 1ting mo e
and morgue u omers
Ypu JI have o do ~ofh.
Do out 1h u
do a
I'll do it
initiojt... I'll treasure wh 1
ou've do ie>anti fi ~tl
new ways to make Ishida
Shoten bigger
You'll have look after Nishi and
the other employees, too
I'll listen to what
they have to say
and do what I can
to help them.
Thanks for waiting
We'll have beer
Coming up!
Starting next year, you'll be
the president, so I'm
counting on you to take
care of Ishida Shoten
I'll do my best.
Yuzo! Congratulations!
Thank you
Good evening
Hey, Yuzo! Yujiro!
Sorry, Katsu
What is it, Yuzo?
Are you crying?
Did your dad give you
a lecture again?
No he didn't
So what are you
going to do?
You can't be on spring
break forever, can you?
What about school?
The class I was taking
is finished already
And the teacher
quit too
Then will you form a
new unit, and try
again next year?
I haven't thought
that far yet
Yuria... Can you
take this?
Sure
But you're not going fo
quit dancing, are you?
Of course not!
I'm glad
I'm happy A lit-y m'W have
more finite to look after
the children, but
But you're more energetic
when you're putting your
efforts to dancing
I'm surprised you
made the decision.
I always thought I would
have to do it someday
Although it applies
to you, too
I was talking about your
dad, Ishida Yujiro
What is it?
That was a big
decision
Didn't you tell me that you
knew Yuzo was doing
his best, but you were
still a little bit
worried about him?
I'm still worried, but
with things like this,
you have to draw the
line somewhere
Don't worry...I'm going to
work hard from now on,
so don't worry
The president is
dried bonito
j* Some Tie who Work TTVd
without recognition
Without good dried bonito,
you can't make good food
But once the soup is made,
you can't see the
dried bonito
That's true
You have to suffer where
the employees and the
customers can't see
! understand
That's really
good soup e
Yujiro... You're talking
about dried bonito
Y Xi'je really aweso.i.e
That's true..
It may sound nice being
the president, but
it's going to be
hard isn't it
You should find a wife
to give you support
I guess
Next, you'll have to
fin a wife.
That's if he an find someone
who will marry him
Thank you, everyone.
Ishida Yuzo, will work
until I turn into the
dregs or the soup base
countma on
• I III*
Do your best!
So, Yuzo's finally going
to be the president
It won't be until next
year, but I tiUrd he'
really gung ho about it.
Welcome
What happened
to your hair?
I thought it was i e
too wild sirTte ' n
to be the president
next year
The second-generation
president's hairstyle
That's it
J. jji'V • jJj pXF
o, it oes..
It seems a little
incompatibie
right now, but once we
get used to it...
Once we get used
to it. Right
That's right.
Once we get used to it.
O e Tiere..
it Ire
Hello
Ken!
%pu ImefffEN
a e%£eat
»«ooooo
leno ed or a ce
•4he*other^Jay
BUM
I enjoyed your dance
the other day
You were good, too.
He's going to work for
us starting today
Ken's going to work
at your store?
After the dance competiton
we ran into each other
MOOOOQtt •
After the dance competiton
we ran into each other
at the exit and we went
drinking from there
And we talked about it
told that I w n fed to
r ome hing new^ince
I £\o Id a chapter
n ancintj
So a "ketl him if &
io dM
lJii- * • iv T;jiU
never expect H
KENlt ^ofhe e.
I've never done anything
other than dance so
I want to expand
my horizons
I wanted to do something
that was entirely
different from dancing
We don't only pse bonito
flakes but
mackerel, too
You mix different things
together, and put it
into soup base, \)U^e
a totally different ta le
1 5CC
Is he. w?
He's starting today
His name is Ken
I'm working here
starting today
He's a nice guy...
^He wo . s
Do you want
your usual9
Ken is selling
dried bonito?
He said he closed a chapter
in his dancing, so now he
wants to try something new.
And that's dried bonito?
I guess he'll be good since
i ht on his feet
t o^ks ike e II
started o mg eN.
Yuzo n €N...
venlhe nl ren re
It's Moe.
Here you go, Hitomi.
Thank you
I'm sorry to call you out
at short notice
It's OK...I finished
cleaning up already
What did you want
to tell me?
At the Dance Beat preliminaries,
there was a producer from
a record company
He was looking for
dancers that he might
be able to pickup
f
Don't tell me...
By any chance
What is it?
Were they scouted?
Really
You did it!
So ROSE MARY is going
to make their debut
We did it!
You did it
Congratulations!
Thank you
Thank you!
Can this really
be happening?
Yes, it can
It looks like something
new has happened to
Hitomi, too