CHAPTER 19
Showdown
Episode 109
Written by
SUZUKI Satoshi
Music by
YAMASHITA Kosuke
English Subtitle By
NIPPON GOLDEN NETWORK
Wow!
Amazing
We're going to
dance here
The Tokyo preliminaries
will start
the day after tomorrow, so
Hitomi and the others
came to check out
the competition venue
Good morning!
So those two are really going
to dance in the preliminaries.
That's right
It's the return of the
legendary Cheapass
Hey Ken
I'm glad you're going
to compete with me
Kazu
You said it, right?
That only Eiji knows
what's in his heart
What about it?
You're right about that
That's why Ray
and I suffered
By dancing, we're going
to put and end to it
and move forward.
So watch us
Say what you want.
Let's go
March 2008
The preliminaries are already
the day after tomorrow!
Shall we do it?
For the few days before the
preliminaries, Hitomi and
the others used Rose's
studio to practice as
much as they could
This year, I'll definitely be
There since I couldn't
make it last year
I'm rooting for you
So do your best.
Do your best!
Here you go..
Something to share.
Thank you!
Here's dried bonito
(katsuobushi for good luck
has "katsu" - the word for "win.")
This is a pre-celebration,
fresh Tsukiji sashimi
That's really extravagant.
Dinner turned into a send
off party for ROSE MARY
Wait a minute!
Akira's not here.
Is it OK to start?
He went over to play
with his friend and hasn't
made even one call home.
He passed his entrance exam
so he's relieved and letting
loose a bit
That's good
You're put aside a plate
for Akira right?
Of course
In that case, we'll go
ahead without waiting for him.
Come to think of it, when I
first came here,
everyone came and brought
food to eat like this.
tciidn tlhe *
That's right.
Time flies, doesn't it?
It's already been a year
You made a play for her,
didn't you?
I did?
When you heard Hitomi
was twenty, you told her,
I'm 33. I'm available
for you anytime
Let's just eat!
Don't bring up boring stuff...
Wait a minute
I made that!
Thank you
Anyway just do your best
We'll be rooting
for you
We will!
Everyone eat up!
Coming to this house
is really relaxing
It really is - I wonder why
Everyone's boisterous
and cheerful
Like one big family
It really is,
isn't it?
I'm stuffed
I want to just go
right to sleep
You can't do that
We're going back to the
studio to practice.
Okay.. I'm ready
Yuka...?
Do you think your father
will come to watch?
Just do what you
a to do
That's what we've let
you do until now
Yuka!
I want him to see me
the way I am now
If he does, I feel like we
can be a family again
I wonder if he'll come...
My brother's definitely
going to come
He wants to be there
to see me lose
Dad definitely wants you to
succeed him at the restaurant.
There's only you
You want to make the effort
to achieve your dream
It's just chasing a lie
That's right, you promised
him you'd quit dancing
if you lose, didn't you?
I want to win!
I want to get
into the finals
I don't want to
see his gloating face
I don't want
to see it
What's wrong, Moe?
Just thinking about it
made me mad
Everyone, let's definitely
win, OK?
The part with three of you...
The angle seems o
a oil 3 JjjUjUVIcu
Ve're ndhn^yn
One more time!
You have to come down
lower, Hitomi.
A little more
Lower, lower...
How was that?
Perfect!
I think so.
I think so, too
What about you, Yuka
It's the best we
can do now.
If we don't give our best
performance tomorrow,
we won't win.
I know...
Tomorrow is the
preliminaries.
Let's get a good night's
rest tonight so we'll
be in excellent condition
tomorrow
Hard wokers - this is my treat
Hello...What is it,
Grandpa?
Akira isn't home yet
Akira's not home yet?
It's 10:30!
So can you keep an eye out
for him on your way home?
I'll stop by the park on
the way home, too.
Overlook it just
this once.
He's at an age when he
wants to play around
But it's already 10:30
What is he doing anyway?
I'm so glad I made
it here in time
Mari!
The preliminaries are
tomorrow, right?
I wanted to give
you this
What is it?
It's rosemary
aroma oil
I gave you some the
last time too
I wanted to give you
some new
Like they suggest at the store,
just spritz a little in the air
Thank you!
Don't think about how well
you have to dance
Just listen closely to
the music, and
believe in the beat of
life that's bubbling
up deep within your body.
Let's all say the
words of love
You all know it,
don't you?
I know it
Say it really loud..
Dance is the
spark of life
I see... Akira's finally
liberated from studying
It's the most fun
time for him
That's right. So I think
he's changed modes
Dance school will be ending
soon, too, won't it?
Isn't that Akira?
Akira.
Hey!
Come back here!
That hurts!
Hitomi!
Did you hit something?
Are you OK?
I think I twisted
my ankle
It's okay... See?
Nothing's wrong
Don't overdo it
I'm sorry
I'm okay. I'm fine
Never mind that
Worry about Grandpa
He's really angry
I know
When they got home
Katsutaro was waiting
for them with his
arms crossed!
Go on inside
Let's hear what you
have to say, Akira
Why were you so late?
And why didn't you even
call once to say you were
going to be late?
I think you know
this by now,
but you mustn't lie, so
just tell me the truth.
I have a friend named
Shimatani from the
basketball team
So you were playing with
this friend, Shimatani?
He wanted to see a movie,
and he said we could get
in the 7PM showing
It's no good for middle
school students to go
to see a movie at night!
I'm sorry.
What did you see7
An action movie...
Shimatani wanted something
to relieve his stress.
Why?
He failed the entrance
exam for the same
school as me.
So he's going to his
second choice.
We said we'd go to the
same school. But only
I passed the exam.
He was depressed, so wanted
to cheer him up.
To let him know that even if we're
going to different schools,
we'll always be friends.
Got it.
I understand the
circumstances
circumstances...
You were late because you
were talking to him about it?
That's right.
OK Akira.
I think you did
a good thing.
But out of consideration for
the people waiting at home
for you, you should
have called.
If this happens again, be
sure you call home
I'm sorry
You're going to cheer
Hitomi on tomorrow,
aren't you? We have to
get up early in the
morning, so go on
up to bed already
Good night.
What was that?
There was just a little
bit of discomfort
Don't fail me now, ankle