CHAPTER 17
Dance is Life
Episode 97
Written by
SUZUKI Satoshi
Music by
YAMASHITA Kosuke
English Subtitle By
NIPPON GOLDEN NETWORK
At the start of the new year
The Ippongi family began their
life without Shota..
Saito la
di nlfuiowyou
Were~ail here...
osena e-(chicken-and
seafood hot pot) is
>9
lie uc^is 1^11 i ii
It's good, isn't it?
All the fl vprslrpmthe
different ingredients in
the pot He 1 together
so that makes it good
it's a collaboration,
isn't it?
That's exactly
what it is.
The family of five is now
a family of four
Once in a while, they
felt lonely, but they
didn't have much
time for that.
Entrance exam day!
Life went on for
the family
February 2008
It's February..
February, 2008
This month is the anniversary
of Mom's..Setsuko's death.
Then that means that it's
been a year since I came
to live here, doesn't it?
That's right.
We were so surprised when
we first met you.
You were so big.
That's right.
Wait a minute!
On my way home from
the funeral, I was
r~Yis£d hen! a were
dancing like this...
It was just about the time
that they were iSing the
preliminaries Dance
Beat in Sapporo...
I was supposed to be in
it, but I couldn't...
We're going to
quit dancing.
Wait a minute!
The preliminaries are the
day after tomorrow!
If you look at it realistically,
being normal is be m
I was supposed to dance
with two other girls,
but when they thought
about the future
they decided to look for
full-time jobs instead
But I couldn't give it up
I'm glad your group
broke up
Why?
Because, if they
hadn't broken up, Hitomi
wouldn't have come to
live here, would she?
That's right.
Last year, around this time,
I never imagined I would
be sitting here eating dinner
with the two of you
But now, we can't imagine
not having you here with
us, can we?
That's true.
Dance Beat is drawing near.
Everyone... Gather around..
2008 53H20H
This is what you've all
been waiting for...
The preliminaries for Dance
Beat will start soon
It's a big event that will
determine the top street
dancers in Japan
Dance Beat
Every year, talented street
dancers from all over Japan
participate in
this event.
ft ^KLB?
The preliminaries are held in
various areas during March,
and 3 fierce battle ensue to
get to the finals in April.
/ /*
The Tokyo preliminaries will
be held on March 20th
Ih re tiline
s ary 20th
eM \ accepting applications
starting from tomorrow
Please turn them
in to me.
I submit them to the
head office all at once
As you all know, the level
in this competition is
not to be taken lightly
Those teams who will be
entering, raise your hands
Consider this the culmination
of this whole year, and
do your best
II fesseQtthe
e \r. pplications.
Thank you
Ready?
Smile!
One more
How do you want
us to pose?
That's it!
Tell us what you're
determined to do.
I'll show my best
dancing yet..
I hope we make it
to the finals
I want to turn this into
a chance for a debut
1it) ewerrakeit
to the finals
It's my revenge for the
Sapporo preliminaries
That's what I work so hard
for this whole year
I hope we make it
to the finals.
As your manager, I'll give
my support to all of you.
I hope you make it
to the finals
Go ahead and
fill it out
Fill it out
I'm going to
fill it out
Let's turn this into
MOBO
What about a leader?
Leader?
It should be Yuka
M * Y do it, ufikt)
Because... you like to
stan lit, don't you?
When we do interviews, you
can do all the talking.
I don't really like to talk.
Really?
What does the leader
do anyway?
To put it simply, someone who
keeps everything together.
Then it should be Hitomi.
Hitomi!
Why me?
Because
You're the one who holds everything
together, aren't you?
That's right.
When Junko and I start
fighting, you can
keep things together.
Really?
I vote for you
too, Hitomi
OK, I'll do it
That's it then.
Can I have this picture
of the four of us?
That one's out
of focus
It's OK.
The leader treats everyone
once in a while, right?
That's right
You can treat us
to monja
OK! We're counting
on you, Leader
You're going to be
the leader?
That's awesome, Hitomi
What's wrong7
She cracked
What's wrong?
I'm just happy that they
have faith in me.
jiial JOii-il n \
It's almost time for
your entrance exams.
How is it going?
Are you confident?
It's not that I don't
have any confidence
He's confident
I didn't say that
You scored Tu~h on the
mock exams, didn't you?
Eat lots to keep
your strength up
Do your best!
Hitomi... I'll have
seconds
! have to keep up
my strength.
Akira?
/o 9
Do your best
That hurt!
Stop!
Help! Hitomi, help me!
Hitomi!
Do your best!
They're starting to accept the
entries for Dance Beat today
February
Tuesday
februjrv
1 ^ 3J^lfliii
e rie , e urn
Feb
Tuesday
lfemin
them in no
here s no ru
We ll be accepting Irie
until the 20 i
Do your best..
Do your bes ..
Re y?
Who was that anyway?
I've seen him
somewhere?...
I'll be right back
Do you know him Yuka?
That's Mr Hibino.
Don't you remember? The guy
who used to drive Yuka
to school
That's right
It's Mr Hibino...
I didn't know
JJi >ji
Is it rt«ep
hmji/jl I'll
blj
V "1itev.ro .
Yuka's father's company
went bankrupt last month.
idnl he ve a mb
f famous restaurants? .I
Why didn't my dad or
my mom let me know?
I thought your parents
had told you about it
So I came to say
goodbye today
hi o ng ^me
IVIiss!
ISS
I'm going with her
What a shock!
tis isn't iP
h bout oure try9
We'll turn it
in tomorrow
Hitomi and Yuka were headed
for the place where Yuka's
parents had moved
Jjhisjsjhfe* la I
idn't even be
compared to the
& lion
itomi
1a i/isi e be ore
Yuka
Mom!
How did this "happen?
It used to be popular
before but for the
past two or three years.
They said your dad's
restaurants were
behind the times
A lot of fashionable
restaurants geared
for young people have
been opening up
Is that why the company
went out of business?
It wasn't only that
Your dad was so determined
to overcome it that he
opened more new
restaurants
He said he would show them
that he had what it took
But it was a mistake
I didn't know about
it until today
If Hibino hadnt toid me,
I wouldn't have ever
known about it.
He told me not
to tell you
He was ashamed to have
you see him like this
so he even told me not to
tell you about this place