CHAPTER 8
"Two Kinds of Love"
Episode 44
Akira's classmate, Naoko
came to the house.
Hitomi was so curious about
what their relationship was,
she couldn't contain herself.
rig "Manual Recording"
ng "Manual Recording"
g Manual Recording"
Enough Sp
ng "Manual Recording"
g Manual Recording"
rig "Manual Recording!1
ng "Manual Recording"
g Manual Recording"
ng "Manual Rtcording"
g Manual Rtcording"
ng "Manual Recording"
ng Manual Recording"
ng "Manual Recording!1
ng "Manual Recording"
g Manual Recording"
ng Manual Recording'
ng "Manual Recording"
ng Manual Recording"
g Manual Recording"
ng "Manual Recording"
ng Manual Recording"
ng "Manual Rtcording"
ng "Manual Recording"
g Manual Recording"
Enough Sp
ng "Manual Recording"
ng "Manual Rtcording"
g Manual Rtcording"
Enough Sp
ng "Manual Recording"
ng "Manual Rtcording"
g Manual Recording"
ng "Manual Recording"
ng "Manual Rtcording"
ng Manual Recording"
ng "Manual Recording"
ng "Manual Rtcording"
g Manual Rtcording"
ng "Manual Recording"
Tell me what happened
before I go in
I want *o share toy
shock with you
If I tell you, you cari't
share it, can you?
What's going on
anyway?
Let's just go iri
Come on in
What a cute place.
There s n thing
unusuaPhe«e
Yuka?
Hey, Hitomi!
ere'you two
ose?
f cojrseyiot!
hai s hy I'm shocked.
D ou elie e Is? She
an s e to etjier
a e e ofiigtit
Don't jUSt sa;
or*onight..
ei e$a ere or
o r h ee days..
t ou ev*
be for a week
L sten here., wor*
art-time t ub
four nightsc>/ve~k
-*You were ucky ! wasn t
at .work* Uayyfcut
sometimes I get home in
the middle T hejiight.
Don't AvcTry^bout me...
Jl e nere to watch
the lace or ou
ere /ou icKe^ out
of^eur ?>use?
No... J Jeft home.
>j! l)W
with/nyxiad
thought of going to
o nave children here
i>) BUJjfti li Yf J
be too much o. an
impositi- Y»,
o why don't you^tay
J J J iD tei?
Youjratfewcre it
I made up my mm
not \o u&e it.
s pai ut of m
ad's account, o
on't you think tha
would be vexing?
6o what are you
going to do
1 me stayjiere until
things cooltfJown
YouJoiow* hat?
te a in
^kpiiungry
^Joavhat?
"Voi/re rem tsuhomiya,
gyoza" potstickers)7
course o,r liaf'-s
our/amil Lusiness
They won* . on e ^ enny,
buttheyjl-send me all
the^gypza! want
Lei« ave ,ome
a ia
Make .some jor me
Why don't you just
make some for her?
She says she doesn t
Ihave any money.
You sure are spoiled.
u s ake yourself at hofrie
omeone else's place.
t's good
It's ea ly elicious
Thanks.
Try to get along..
Justt nk of
4t as fate
A would be childish to
kick her out. so I'll
et her stay, tjfjj'irt not
going to talk to her
asthuch as p ^sible
don? want to come home,
and fight too
Would you likelbiore.
Thanks.
The soup is}re
Howth u$htfuf*
Is It ood?
tfejreallv g ¥>d
mglad
I'm home!
ISSSS3I
iinnt
lltomi. Y uridinner s
in he refrigerator
Sorry... ad "gyoza"
^a bunko's plafce
^'11 eat tomorrow
morning. "Thanks.
What was Junkos
emergency?
You won't believe this.
it seems Yuka had a fight
with her father and
She asked Junko to put
her Qp at her place.
She said it's just for a
fe "tJays, so I'm sure
it's okay, but.
Junko didn't knoft what
to do, so she wanted me
to come-over, and listen
to Yuka's story.
What about Naoko?
"""She erutiome
before dinner
It was Iready dark.
Akira saw her home
Way to go, Akira
But the funny thing is.
? hen Momoko and Keiko
J i^uldi
felt as though those
boyfrien s ere aking
them from me, \ felt like
they were hv rivals
But it's different
with a boy
! just think has he grown
tip that much already?
I feel like he accomplished
something, tid it makes
me happy
You're a male parent
after all
Shall I do that?
Are vou orne, atsu?
I'm home
What is it?
Will you^jo with me
to M Isuri.. ?
Just for i tie hile
Notagaifl? Goby
urself
I'll ust be in the
way won' 9
hat are you saying?
Tffto Kamakura with
art on Sunday, and
we talked the whole
day long.
^So I don't have anything
ore to talk about
I don't have anything
o talk about either.
ou ust have something..
11aybe about shirt designs
r something.
ust'talk about anything
Please! You're my
friend, aren't you?
I want to see her, but
the vorst thing is not
having Anything to
talk about
I do feel like
having a drink
Hitomi... s It okay if
! go out for a while?
o igfl head
Tferiks, itorni.
J/nvv lUivb
I'm not an umbrella you can
borrow or ^UTJQen .shower
a-3 j>»
I ^arjghtfcack.
Man dewdrops are popular
in shirt designs these days.
ewdrops?
i They think it's retro, so
it's quite popular with
the young crowd
Dewdrops are £ute,
aren't ihey?
^es, they are
jieyVe really cute.
Also, speaking of
yshirts..
^Checkered shirts are as
opular as-ever...
Checkered s irts, huh?
That's standard.
isn't it?
Tha bright... t $
standard, isn't it?
Do ou Want some
rolled £ggs?
oun sgood
11 ~dveone
I'll make some
for you now
Sheknows what my
a?5nte-foods are
_:She even kfiows what order
ik no Btlhern
m~gratefal
eel like a ido!!
Wh talking about jiewdrops
an'u cnecKerec smrts-fof
your sa anyway?
ave a urink
II orinK my own
Is he thinking about the
girl who came over today?
It's possible
We're leaving now!
So. Akiratias a
girlfriend.
He's ail grown up?
I'm leaving. Graiante!
Be sure to tell^uka that
the "tstikudam" s V$ave
me was so delicious,
i ate it ail up.
I will*
Be-ca eTlf
How nice it stobe
young, isn't fa K
I feel like singing the
song of Jbuth ho®
Go ri Tit hhe \l.
Sano'
Good jnornmg
I won't interrupt
Actual! , >i couldn't
sleep las night
Why not?
When you > /alked me home
yesterday, yo did me
about your re father,
didn't o 9
I was thinking about
that all night long
About how it was.
It's okay.. org St
about wh
dyou
I can* o ge
it's sadder tha h addest
stones tha ' ead
up un i o
Hrtomi had no idea that
at that moment. Akira
was feeling a ripple of
uneasiness in his heart