CHAPTER 10
"Trying too hard to find happiness"
Episode 55
Does that mean...
...you're getting married?
Please allow me to marry Keiko.
To Keiko, marriage means a family.
Can you give her the warmth of a family?
Yes... I will.
This time it's a business trip.
To Atami.
Atami?
It's Mr. Katsumata.
What a coincidence!
itomi saw Mr. atsuma a
together with a om n
other th&h Keiko
I bought tea
Here you go
Thanks
Were you putting on
make-up again?
Hitomi?
Thank you.
What's wr tig? Y u've been
kind of q let
What?
Just as an example..
For example, if you saw a
man and woman walking
down the "SllWay at an inn
wearing cotton kimono,
what wo "Id y to think their
relationship was?
I'd thinkthey were
lovers, of course.
Or a married couple
If they 're not a
married couple
Parent ahd child
Mnp to show gratitude
to a Vent
^■what jf they were walking
arm itrarm like this?
Then^hey would have
t lie jov Ys
what jf the re dy
hadjs fia ?
Then
It's an illicit affair!
He betrayed his fiancee
afid went on a trip with
another woman!
Is it someone $ou know?
What?
) was just giving
an example
That's all
We're leaving
Get in the car.
Hitomi felt her feet dragging as
she returned to Tsukishima
She didn't know if she
should tell Katsutaro
about what she saw in Atami
I'm home!
Jou're just in time
llor dinner, Hiiomi!
With everybody s help,
we have some re lly
Swesometastmg curry
T is is for you, Hitomi
Thank you!
I'm .hungry'
Okay Let's eat
J-fitomi! How was Atami?
You went there to
dance, didn't you?
It was fun! Our dancing
didn't go over too well,
but we got to use
the hot springs
Hurry Hitomif
I'm sorry
It Jooks delicious!
We madelEi dressing, too
Try the salad
I will!
Let's eat
This is
It's delicious
Of bolirse. t e ilwo 1(e
hard to ma e it
Try the salad, too
Nice 1or
Hitomi y/as afraifllhat she
vAild bl?t.it out
li wouic a.su aro an
Ikolhlnk ey
found utwhat
hap eried today?
Keiko call a today
What did shfe wantf>
She was complain n that
they were £oth too busy
o they didn't ha /e time
iO «J0 Old Oj) •
Mr. Katsuma a went on a
busin %s|rip. Hes
wor ing a home... whatever
ouc
hi it... f T a company
in Tie J<an5ai area
ome page?
That's it Home p^ge.
h to nd Yuria jnade
something nice
Thisls great
Its reallyjiice
he ildrermre
he$Kno 1iow muc
ft
e ns/orK 1ko o
^fje married, and ha /e
a amily of her own.
They a I no o
happ she is
hat's vr Yig?
1Mb . ri
Wha Were you thinking?
Gai o vertofto e s
p ace fora^while?
i ot , sojtsjok y
if I g ov t, and have
a dri X.isn't it?
ure, it'-sokay
I'm going to
get my wallet
Are^ou home, Kats
I'm jiere!
Do you want to go
to "Matsuri'J?
Mart was getting ready
to open up earlier,
and she told me to
come over tofiight
id that n omfortable
fee!inTjf)fetwe/>i the
two f you go away?
i suppressed my
eari \ y esires
Did you suppress
themt&mpletely?
I (lid my best
Good eventn
Are you going so ^ /here?
f Jl AO 6lU06 UJ.I
Rose's plac
ifill outa eYuzo
vith you?
e nte found out
Keiko's getting
%
a ne , e's been
ittie 'depressed.
He is? Buti'm sorry...
He is? tButVm sorry...
He is? u\ I'm sorry
I want to^alk to Rose
about so 'filing toda
i J
ImVng
over
to > ose s place
s uzo feeling
depressed?
a e's feeling like
big br ther watching
his^itile ister going off to
come ome mans wife
en ugh they used
o fi "h all the time,
Keiko were
^retty close.
He d \kn'i too* t. Vs
sensitive, s e?
f He takes te
his da
Hey! Keep it down!
I'm sorry!
I'm so happy
-for eiko
After tjoing to an
orphanage to live
away from her parents,
she came to live
with you -and Setsuko
She's okay now, but when
she<first came to live
with us, it was
•really rough.
"he had a rebellious
streak that was
stronger -than most people
If I scolded her for
anything, she would
tear all the paper off
our "Tioji" doors
* And she'd turn over all
the planters in the
whole iieighborhood
All along the
-alleyway
But you and S u Ttacc te
the vay^h as, yoxir
pi iiujtf^iji^?
he said she anted £0 be
jj o j
she e
cam ii jr
And the result is the
happiness she found
With everybody s effort,
Keiko has finall reached
the point he «s ell ha ethe
\^rmth I Hfown ^fiily
Congratif 1ions?¥Catsu..
Dolft sa ha
I'm gingery.
rlf SfetsGko was alive, she d
be so hajpjjy, wouldn't she?
You'r 1<irig m ry
Go ah 'ad, and cry
ry I yo ant
Keiko's finally
found happiness
But you sure do
cry easily.
Did you tell anyone
about it yet?
No, 1 haven't.
Whatever you do
don't tell Yuzo
That fool is very
fond of Keiko,
so you don't want him
to go crazy, do you?
What should do?
Should I teil Grandpa?
Or should go directly
to Keiko, and tell her?
Or maybe I shouldn't
teil anybody about it
! have a feeling it'll
all blow over if
I just don't say
anything about it
And! won't be destroying
everybody's happiness.
(don't know
what to do
Not saying an/thing is
one way 7 handling it.
This is an adult's way
of thinking, but
They're not married yet, so
we could jclose our eyes
to a little affair and
not make waves.
But would Keiko be happy
mam Mo a man like that?
That's right... She won't.
She won't be happy at all
But it's between
the two of them
So I thin < it's best
if they res 1ve this
between themselves
The b ay idbe
if Keiko was suspicious
about 1 s usinesS trip
or just some woman's
intuitio t would make
Keiko realize wt Hf was
going
dif lie would
talk to him ab tJF it
Andifsh a ts tcrfofrgive him,
that would be okay
You know w at they say about
overcotn!ngV)b tacies
making a person stronger
Hitomi
Let's just wait and see
what happens for now
If it t Tkes too long for
Keiko to* e lize W's
going on, on 'bu
can talk to her.
All right. I'll do that
Thank you
YouVfe welcome
Go ahead, and drink
I'm home
I was so happy.
1 linted Dad to i
s iiis blessing^
Aren' you glad
he approved?
Will Keiko be okay?
Just as Rose said, Hitorhi
was just going to walfch,
and see what happens, but
she couldn't help but
worry about Keiko.