Tear-stained Towel Blanket"
Episode 87
rte(D#7t)\J>7 J M (87)
ScrShStaVs . eeting
with his mot ^fer?
hey re .meeting about
now somewhere
-it must ejgoing
smobthiy..
In the^nd, hota/nus Jiayg
ongedfor Is another
J^o matter how much Uncle
Katsu c Ted lor him
he an't cbmpete
against his mother.
I don't know what s
going to happen...
Why? Is there
something wrong?
They haven't seen ach
other for years, so
once they s.art lining
together, I think that's
'When the p oblem
will start
Especially since Shoe's
gotten used o ife
at our house.
Ila 6 r .. h as
ru is moibe. ajs ill
And t Say, h?'s suppose o
meet his mother s fian
But Shota already knows I
about that, doesn't he?
That* true, but.
But you haven't de i
your own feelings, e o
"Riat'-s right.
30st as Grandpa Til
(flr WaVayama^ys,
it's II for Shotae
sake,i)Lt I still...
I understand how you e
The more .inqs y/ork out o*
Sb «a rr Isrrothe...
V7i:di ib iHib«dnywdv
It'sjbifWti -only
one who doesn
wh Ts going *>n
<Jn order to strengthen
th ^ond^etweenmeth
and Child, Shota and his
mother have me. t umber
^iUjfilU ^iub -UiJ Ma
Ji« i^i^J 3dJjili^
ime ^rtrea
Anfl t aay, the/re supposed to v
-meet Mikie's fiance, Mitsuru.
eilrneet ^in. -n
it'stime o lunch.
All right. JIV:all you
Mikie!
ihoi
his is Urtt.e itUru ..
He's one f ry
best rie Is.
Hello..
He wants to
to know you.
Is it okay if he
plays with us?
Oka .. What shall
\te lay then?
I e ver here?
Let's go over there.
I'll call you I ler.
Wait for me'
I thought I'd make a
preliminary inspection
as their manager.
Kin jh« • J
so enthusiastic.
It looks like it'll
be easy to dance..
This time it'll be perf tt
t as the department
store that insisted
n g limg you to o
Mayuge Neko.'
That was great, Sho a.
r h-.rf} iftoji
Sh il we go to e
Tie re ^ing foo'm.
Okay
n the rooftop
department sto
h Tl i saw him,
as-surprised
Vas his-mother.
e lis that guy rnuSt
er,fian£e..
tt Jnan who's going io
Ti^hota'ssfather.
hm was heMe
e so .med ice.
nd t loo ed like he was
je>=ing a ong with him
He was?
So I guess it'll be
good for Shota
h 1 t>kfed|ike h
j^ifljy iljjijx
n. ere a amily
If you $aw them, yo
think they were a family.
p to feeling lo el
aren't ;ou?
trig about o a
e incj Tsukishima
A Jittle
n erstan
Iu\J j) j &&
t'«?he b Is?
lilliLj tJi jlJhL
Yoi n t'6 etter or m
bUV^Y/lhil liiUfta
m home'
come home
jJ'uu JUywj
The eoar m . «t to e
/njgb/1 • ^ J
mil J,)) «n«Jj> 1 Jul
Didj/ou have fun?
They ought pilots
f s ft ice c earn.
Tnat's greSt.s
^J «jO»ljili iil^ ijili
Bltfeks.
Th t£ great. <&o, aift put
the Lfoc!^ up in your room.
1 nfeed tojtalk
to s jfroue
h Ji ji ml
But (hink"it's great that
he seems to g \ along with
his mother s fiance
Moe saidlhey looked
like a real family.
It might work out better
Ihan I thought...
Are you still unhappy
about it?
No matter what happened
in the past, this is
protfobly the best for
ShotasJiappintess
"That's right..
if we think about
~>iota s future..
it's Mom!
Momoko 9
Hello..
I'm bringin he people
I work i o Mako's
place oday..
hat's nghP e inally
ot into one of thelGinza
department stores.
So we* inij
to ceiebrate
Do you wa o join us?
When I told them my daughter
was a dancer hey all
wan ed jo meet you.
1 want to go, but.
I have stuff |o
do at home..
If it's iter dinner,
you can go.
It ll^ea nice
diversion.
Me said it's okay
So you're going?
u ' sojglad... It looks like
II get along with you, too.
It's because we re
both men...
__But Shota -eally
is adorable.
He's so open,
and sweet.
The problem is my cooking
I'd better work on it
What are you going
to make today?
Meat and pot toes.
Be sure yourook the
potatoes propely
i know! >What are
u saying?
We should bring him to
meet your mother, too.
I've only met her at the
restaurant th tftielime
on't really feel Jike
e been introduced to
her as the woman you're
^going to n")arry
We'll do it one day ..
When will }hat be?
Actu lly..
Whatls it?
J told myTnom..
that you work h
office in Ma.unou lii
I'm not an Ifice c erk
I know.
I've never worked in
ft office before!
I know!
y mom's really
strait-laced, so
old her about what
ou really did
Okay then... All I have
to clo is retend that
I'm an b fice clerk
whe
n rn
eet her.
I'm goinq to quit
soon anyway..
just ont
tell her
There s ofie more thing..
Wha ?
ut our marriage
o d her that I was
n in of getting married
Tell her that we're
qetting mairied..
Not that you're just
thinking about jt.
If I did, she'll get upset,
and thin s vnTTTSII «part
So for now, I just haven't
mad it c ear yet.
You h letoTlllier..
Otherwise, I can't bring
Shot To meet her
There's o e more thing..
heres ore?
I haven't toid her that
you have a child.
pu're kidding!
If ant tell her'
ve never been mafried
and l'n^her only son...
My mom woulfl'heverlthink of
my marrying a girl like that.
1 • 1 OUm
eally havearv n ention
marrying me
I love you.
Then tell your rromer
We won't g ere
if you dori |
Why did ol
with Sho a o a
Why ami cooKina
meat ^and potatoes?
Where are you going?
I'd bette o today...
You're lea ing.
telliil/ii
c 0
o db e? ait a minute!
It canW.
^So you're all
from Sapporo?
That'STight... Th M
came oOHiereM/itn me,
o ked reall hard,-and
ere-finatl e£ing
ome£esUlftfTb w
/e re "n fhara'1
really) liappy
Namarp'
Mormko s Mn<. cool
1 work,^oo
Really
Namar^.."
It's because sne doesn't
put on irs
ofry! Let te
concen ra » .
It's ready now! Fat!
So this s "monja"
It's "namara" delicious.
I'm "namara' happy
Namara' cheers!
i i.at's not how
/ou use it
It's no *
Mever mind, and
get back to work
It's delicious
pu dance hip h p,
*ton't * ou?
That's sojcooI.
Ddyo dance ate ents
and things like that?
I do...
sgpeakmgpf events
you all imagine
hip ho 8 here's
this darce ca led
Mayuge leko^lhat we do
ou mean mayugt" as
in eyebrows?
Neko (cat)7
ewe
mes,
arid /lance
tamusenesi . hs and
places likeihat
It's e 11 t e, nd
popular with children
really want to see it.
^"and see41s.
I •
Don'i Icea^i&y
o jriy daughter
Tijiotjftlcin ^a
lay former
xcuse me..
t' randpa
Hello?
hotas o e
blafike*9
It looks like something
has hippfened ^ev een
the children£ga.n.