CHAPTER 15
Tear-stained Towel Blanket"
Episodfc 86
©^TNl/^Vkl (
Shot a
How's Shota?
He's iying down,
-and crying
Yuria*
Why did /feu do something
like this? You're his
older sister "tent you?
Because Shota was mean
What do you mean?
He wouldn't tell me
about his mother
And he wouldn't tell me what
he talked !o her about
It's been along time
since Shota's seen
his mother, 5nd he haT
a lot to think about
And he s having a nard time
putting it into words
i know you want to hear
what happened, but give
him a little more time
He's not trying
to be mean
You have to make
up with him
Yuria thought you were
trying to be mean
because you wouldn't tell
her about your mother
ut it's not that, is it?
Then will you two
make up9
If the two of yotf arjfe4'
fighting, Akira won f
be able to study
Make up with
each other
Shall we shake hands,
and make up9
Shake hands..
Jo: I //or»'f
shake hands.
Yuria*
Why 9
Why did it turn
out like this?
'ji*I /»i
tarted fighting?
They haveri t made up...
No matter how hard Grandpa
tries, he couldn't
resolve the fight.
This is the first time
hardly anyone talked
during dinner, too
Ma be Yuria's feeling
a little jealous.
Because Shota went
to see his mother
Yuria s pr T>ably
fe ling lonely
This is wh 11 you
should step in.
Even If everyone else
is tense, you have
to stay che Trful, and
brighten up the house
That's true...
That's what I think, too,
but I just don't know
what to do
Shota really is adorable
Having seen fm^gain.
I realize ttf^J
really do love him.
Did e)a k$o ou?
At firsts was a little
shy tarted
op radually
I reafl a a fool o
leaving u an adorable
bby^lone, and
e in onely
t a e me cry
e o bad
Pretty soon, we'll be able to
meet oihside^omewhere.
When we*do,-shall we
all go somewhere?
I want you fftdlotjet along,
since we'll all be living
together next year
That's true..
Maybe I should meet him.
Promise?^'!! tell Shota
at our next meeting.
Do you want seconds?
Eat lots! i ha ^o learn
how to^took for Shota
Than* you.
sftard^sn't it?
Wh ther o e sho 19
e th
parent
an real ents nt ftct
lib acn Iher or not
*Pe s all , Ihmk f
th \ nteract with
But wheh e tr hfte s
trouble, t!|h n s just
don > ork
Mr. //akayama s feriinceS
cas ^like t
t\>ugh I
un e
stoCd
what Mr. aka a ma was
sat incj, b .
his s h irst ime
e expe lenced a case
fTete e eas Vent
m
orTie. child.
ru) si 3 t^
I Wade t,ch£
careless remark
I'm still a ounqster
In .islin ork,
everyone s..
There s riot:o ve* lent rule
that ni\\as ure us that
things will wo V out
e real ays tfst
ee mg ur ay
We haveto ;front the
liv^ftihe ea parent,
fos erpa enffcnd
i ec.ai ea on
E ery tas s irst
time jexpenence
In ft atWnTe. r. Jaka/a~a^
n I are on siers, too
Ypti can be'firoud thaf
ou're a youngster
Thank /tfufor
the c 1fee.
MayugeN l<o" (again?
Th s time,Mt,!l"bei>ff
he r ftop of
UteparfiVient ftorf
h to e id it at&he
amus fnent ^ iTthe
last time, someon4 at the
{3epartmentastorei/vas there.
^Kfna really iiked it, sofhe
asked us to do it for Afi m
The fee is pr
good, too
I think it's go
it'll be a good arm p
for ROSE MAR oo
WhaTdoyou hink, Yuka?
It's 1<ay with me don't
have any/rrdney left.
You spent all t ri
money alread
When Tf§ ^s mof^y, she j ^
pendsi i htawa
She' ystdarice DVDs^nd
things like hat..
he can'* etoOtof the
little rich irlmo e.
What abo^fV^u? "bought jcrab,t$
i
and ate it a I yours f>
Don OgrumbleM gave
you a e , idn' 7
It was 1 ne eg.
■* MO I! "MOM
So we're going to do
it, aren't we?
That's right
e ou!
let's ha* e tea
4o ether
So.ry...* ITiave
Like what?
A making up party
for the children
See o '
Eat lots today
You don't have
to ho a back
Mako-.^ell ha
another curry "monja"
It's Shota's favorite.
TSr oTThad a fight.
t§ etter if you '
r ogetjalong.
th nk«o too
make up with
a.^cant you?
No... trota^on't tell
me a Txut-his "SVher
I told you... Shota's
hot trying to be mean
He just saw his mother,
and there's still a
lot he doesn't know
Right?
ria... try to understand
iow Shota feels.
(F flon' understand
o e so stubborn
n?wa/,just eat a lot
today... Lei's have
fun, an * eat.
It's feryone's
favorite "rrionja."
This part is d licious
It must i)e rough...
Burdened with such
compTi ^ated feelings
fit sue ^atyoungage
I want to say something,
til I can't do it
The only thing we can
dcrts o ervethem
d liBoifs "monja."
your carry
muisjd, OMUld.
You'/egood atltrYuria
Make itjor ith
I don't tyrant *o.
M iVit-for im.
Why do J Jiave to jmake
monja' forborne fie
who's joing to be
leaving^sobn?
furia.. Wait'
Shota..
Hitomi... after tier
Go after her!
I'm sorry!
Yuria s an lot
She's to 1 ft idiot.
anuria
Wait J
Yuria.
Yuria. i
Yuria
Why did you
You'll ma e
Shota sSb
You wouldn't nderstand.
Yuria.
5h'4 follow me.
Yuria...1
^ave me alone'
Just leave me alone
I'm just going home
Hitomi. 9
Mr. Takayanagi!
nas n my way
to your house
wondere- how
Shota was doing
I see... Shota's situation
caused quite a stir.
Everyone in the house
seems to be on edge
even Grandpa seems
to be at a loss
This is a first-time
experience lor
KatsGtaro, too,
isn • i
-For the child's parent
to come, and take
he child back
o think of it,
It is, isn't it?
For Akira, Yuria arid
Shota, too...
it can! JLe helped
if their feelings
get ptit of hand.
t out of hand
What should we do t
a time like this?
Just accept thfcir f flings
I'm so r ... r just
repeaiin what the
section c lef laid.
There isn't c » e en
rule to e us how
to^do this.
We just have to feel
our way around..
And confront each f&rsdn's
life head on...
That's what I was told
He said I liould be proud
that I'm still a youngster
Le s think about
it together
We'll t Ink about Ond
find a good soluti n
Okay
Hitomi feit that she tiad
tb laccfejtt the confusion
thfe childreh were f \ling