CHAPTER 15
Tear-stained Towel Blanket
Episode 85
September, 2007
It's the day when Shota
will see his mother for
the first time in years.
Yes?
Excuse me
Their meeting
has started.
How was Shota,
Mr. Takayanagi?
He looked up
at his mother
How have you been?
Saito Mikie
Fine
I brought you a
present, Shota
I wasn't sure what
to get you
What do you think it is?
Open it and see
Video game
Do you have it?
Play with it
Thank you
What's his mother like?
She's about 30
She works at night
Will I be able
to meet her?
Just for a little while
on her way out...
Hitomi
I want to see her
i in buny... n ustrieociiiv
trouble between the
real parent and the foster
parent, the child gets
caught in the middle, and
the child will hurt
That's why we try not to
have the two of you
come face to face
There's a reason for this...
Please don't make it
hard on Mr. Wakayama
I'm sorry
What about your house?
What kind of home is it?
He's lis shirts
A clothing store
What about your dad?
s our su is ima
ad kind?
He is?
and s ster on't you?
What do you play?
jOJ
0JJ3? \ j jj ITLlXJ Jj £}|j
ames do you play?
"Shichi narabe" (sevens)
So you play "shichi narabe"?
Jir it mis next time.
Do you enjoy school?
You do?
What are you good at?
) p] 3 turnip j 3j
a h est
7MF3 I
h t ind f or s
aseba I
I see. What television
shows do you like
Comedy
What do you like to eat?
Natto (fermented
soy beans).
What else?
Meat and potatoes
I'm sorry
I don't know anything
about you, Shota
I'm sorry... I couldn't
look after you properly
I won't let you be
lonely anymore.
At first, Shota didn't
say anything, but
eventually, he started
answering his mother's
questions one by one
I guess his mother's feelings
got across to him
Along with spending the
night with her, we want
them to restore their ties as
mother and child gradually
This meeting today is
a big event in Shota's
life, so he might be a
little emotionally
unstable after this
I hope you'll both help
him to deal with it
Here he is.
Shota
Did you meet
your mom?
Did you talk a lot?
Shall we go home
for today?
Thank you
Thank you for your
patience
I'll see you out.
Shota
What's wrong, Ms. Saito?
I thought you left.
I'm sorry! I forgot
something.
Are you his Tsukishima Dad?
I C3..i
o D o oQLfj o o
iti e younger
I'm sorry
Ms Saito.
I'm Shota's mother
I'm Saito Mikie
Thank you so much for
taking care of Shota.
I'm sorry I haven't
contacted you.
Who is this?
She's my granddaughter
My name is Hitomi.
I've been helping
Grandpa to..
I see. Thank you
very much!
What did you forget?
My handkerchief...
I must have taken it out
together with the game
Let's go and..
Just a minute...
te king to Shota,
iz thai I have
o to learn...
I'd really appreciate it if
if you could teach me
Ms. Saito... This way.
I see ol. Shota.
I'm sorry...
It wasn't supposed to
turn out like this
Is it okay for
us to leave?
I'm sorry
Hitomi. ?
We're leaving.
I'm sorry! I didn't notice
that she forgot something
It can't be helped..
These things happen.
It didn't bother Katsutaro,
did it?
That's the kind of
person he is
I think tt'sto good t Ing
What was?
The interaction between the
real parent and foster parent
If th l»uld have mo e
in erac ion with each
other, they could develop
a relationship where they
could discuss things together
an't would be ideal for
the c ilia,/wouldn't it?
That's my opinion.
s only jf the real
Yid foster parent
g o together, but ou
o consider .lha
have their
wn feelings
A Jfj oesn't necess nly
thatthey'il agr\
ther does it?
For example, if th
parent says something
badabo t the foster t
in front of the child, or
if th parent says
he doesn't ant to return
ill J b:>
lik*tRSt
The child will be caught
in the middle, and he's
going to be terribly hurt
I'm sorry
It's a delicate situation
Interaction maybe ideal,
ut h esjio luaTantee
I hope it works out.
That's the difficult
part of our job
Thank you
Where's Akira?
He went to the library
He did?
Did your mom give
that to you?
What did you talk
to her bout?
Nothing much
You had to talk to her
about something!
What did you talk about?
What is she like?
Give it back!
No!
What are you doing, Yuria?
Yuria took my game!
That's because you were
being mean to me
You're his older sister
Give that back to him
No!
Shota
Yuria... Why did
you do that?
Shota
Yuria..
Yuria... give it
back to Shota
No! I don't want to
I'm home
I'm home.
What's wrong?
Yuria took away the game
that Shota s mother
gave himr anti ^tifc won't
give it back to him
Yuria..
Let it go
No!
Let it go!
How's Shota?
He's lying down
and crying.
Yuria!
Why did you do something
like this? You're his
older sister, aren't you?
Because Shota was mean
What do you mean?
He wouldn't tell me
about his mother
And he wouldn't tell me what
he talked to her about.
It's been a long time
since Shota has seen
his mother, and he has
a lot to think about
And he's having a hard time
putting it into words
I know you want to hear
what happened, but give
him a little more time
He's not trying
to be mean
The children are
feeling confused.