CHAPTER 9
I'm Getting Married"
Please... take good care of Keiko
Dad
I'll do my best.
I'm counting on you.
Cheers!
Congratulations!
A few days later...
Keiko's going to treat you?
She's said she wants to offer me lunch
to thank me for helping out with Mr. Katsumata.
Is that right? That's good, let her treat you to lunch.
I'm happy about Keiko's wedding, but I'm also
happy that you and Keiko have gotten close.
Is everything ready?
Let's eat then.
Keiko's getting married, isn't she?
That's right. Though they haven't set the date yet.
I wonder if we can also go to the wedding?
Sure we can, since she's our sister.
I can't wait...
What will everyone wear?
I'm going to wear my school uniform.
I'll wear a dress.
Shota, how about a bow tie?
I haven't met with Katsumata since then.
Really, why not?
He's really busy
A web designer is always up against a deadline every day.
Almost like he lives in his office
Then you can't really go on dates
Especially with your irregular work schedule
We make up for that with email
Sometimes he'll send me two e-mails in one hour
Here's one now
I thought so
He's says he's going on a business trip this weekend, too
It must be rough
Hitomi!
Mom!
I'll go ahead and sit over there.
I'm sorry...
He's our client department head
We're having a meeting
I'm sorry about the other day Keiko
You were forced to witness such an awkward moment...But maybe that's why it went so smoothly
when Keiko went to tell him about her marriage!
You're kidding! It went well - he gave his okay?
He did.
I'm so glad.
Congratulations!
Thank you
How about we have coffee together after this?
I think the meeting should take only about 30 minutes.
It's okay with me. What about you, Keiko?
Sure. It's okay.
In the meantime, you two can finish your lunch
I'll see you later
Ms. Ippongi!
I'm sorry
She sure is cheerful.
She's such a scatter brain
But it's kind of a strange feeling
She's Dad's real daughter, and you're her daughter
And I'm Dad's yet one more daughter; it just a strange feeling
Shall we eat?
Take your time
I heard from Mom that you used that bedroom since
you were eight years old
Yes... Until I left when I was 18, so I lived there for 10 years
That's the room Yuria and I are using, right?
That was always my room, but for 10 years
you were raised seeing the same scenery
weren't you?
That's true.
It's like you're a younger student from the same school
I ran away from there, so I'm a drop-out
Keiko is the Ippongi school's outstanding student
I wouldn't say that.
I used to fight with Dad all the time.
But you made up with him, right
My fight with him has been continuing all this time
That old man's so stubborn
That's the same for the both of you
Whenever you talk with Grandpa, it turns into a big display
He calls you a sly northern fox, and you call him
A sly old man, or an old raccoon dog
I never called him an OLD raccoon dog
Yes, you did.
You're terrible!
You were the one who called him an OLD raccoon dog!
Oh really?
YES, I never called him an OLD raccoon dog
I only said little raccoon dog...
That's terrible, isn't it?
I meant to treat Hitomi to lunch, but you ended
up treating me instead
It's okay... this is a rare occasion
Are you going to work from now?
I'm working the night shift.
It must be rough
Do your best
I'll leave you here.
Thank you for the meal. Excuse me...
Keiko!
Congratulations
Thank you
This is the first time I've had a good chance to
talk with her at length
How does it feel?
It's a strange feeling.
She's like a little sister, and yet she's also like
an underclassman from the same school.
But at this point she's more Dad's daughter than I am..
I'm home!
Come over here, Hitomi
Hello.
I'm glad you're home
We came to make an announcement.
We normally send this by mail...
Listen carefully now
With Katsutaro as the designated foster parent
and Hitomi as his assistant, the Ippongi family has been
officially recognized by the city of Tokyo as a
foster care home
*Congratulations*
Thank you! We did it!
We did it!
Can I take a look?
Here's my name..
Ippongi Hitomi
That's great!
In the case of the Ippongi family, since Katsutaro's wife Setsuko died
they reapplied to be recognized as
a foster care home.
After deliberation by the child welfare office
they have been officially authorized
We are really relieved
Because of your track record
we were sure it would be okay, but until the decision was made
official, we couldn't relax.
Thank you.
We it all to you.
It was our pleasure
So now, you'll have to go through the newly
registered foster parent training
What?
The Newly registered foster
Newly registered foster parent training
Foster parent training?
It's a two-day training that you have to go through
You'll have sit-down learning, a tour of an institution
and you'll be interacting with other foster parents
I think it'll be a good learning experience.
I'll definitely go.
Even if I have to take time off from school
Thank you so much.
Akira, Yuria and Shota can really feel reassured!
Mr. Wakayama.
Mr. Takayanagi.
Ms Irioue.
Truly, thank you very much
Let's have fun and do our best together
I will.
If you have any problems, you can come crying to us anytime
I will... I'll come crying to you, please take care of me.
I'm so glad.
Hey, everybody!
Let's make another toast.
Katsu, enough with making so many toasts
Even if you leave we'll go on toasting
it's such a special occasion
Hitomi!
Thank you!
Thanks to you, we've been officially recognized
as a foster care home. Congratulations!
Cheers!
Keiko, congratulations on your marriage!
I can't move! I'm stuffed
So many things to celebrate are happening one after
another at this house, aren't they!
The only thing left is making up with Momo-chan, isn't it?
Yujiro
Let's stop talking about that, ok?
If you say so.
Excuse me for a minute
Where are you going?
I feel hot, so I'm going to cool down a bit
Will he be okay? He might fall off the balcony.
Hitomi... go and check on your grandpa
I will
Grandpa!
Hitomi
What's up, you must be tired...
From saying 'congratulations' too many times
No... that's not it
I just started feeling serious.
Serious?
I'm so glad I started being a foster parent
Thanks to that, I can be this happy for Keiko
There are a lot of painful and rough times, but
I think there are a little bit more happy times
From now on, I can experience a whole lot of different
feelings viith Shota, Yuria, and Akira.
I'm really grateful for their existence
They're making my life really fun...
Even though our last names are different..
So I wonder why your mom and I have the same last
name, but we just can't get along.
It's so strange, isn't it?
A strange feeling.
Hitomi heard this phrase so many times today
This evening she's thinking many feelings arise that can't be easily expressed
between parent and child...family...or person to person
Another part-time job...?
Yes, the president from the last time called me
and said we did such a good job that he wanted
to know if the four of us would do it again.
The "Mayuge Neko' thing again?
Seems likely...
What will you do?
I'll do it!
That was fast
We're lucky that we can get paid to dance.
The part time job I have now at the pub is terrible
They really work you to death
Don't say that!
I'm the one who introduced you to that job
What about you, Hitomi?
I'll do it.
It was so much fun last time.
What about you, Junko?
I'll do it. I have no choice, do I?
You need four people to do it, don't you?
Okay then we'll gather on Saturday at the Aoyama office like
the last time
OK!
Be there by 6AM
That's so early!
It's too early
This time is a business trip
It's in Atami.
Atami?
On Saturday, Hitomi and group arrived at the office
Good morning
We're counting on you again!
As soon as we get all this stuff ready
we'll be leaving.
In the meantime, sit down, and read the pamphlet
Atami - Just hearing the name echo
filled Hitomi with anticipation