Chapter 19
Showdown
Episode 111
Written by
SUZUKI Satoshi
Music by
YAMASHITA Kosuke
English Subtitles by
Nippon Golden Network
The preliminaries of the 2008
Dance Beat have begun.
However Hitomi sprained her
ankle during rehearsal.
At this rate, she won't
be able to dance to
rsa is a ion
The fate of ROSE MARY is
TlrefIfc^Tfip 1MJV Vis
resting on their appearance,
which is coming up soon
ft tin their appearance
JJltehb ^JJJIIJLJ JP^OJA
We've been uniting
for this day^oo...
h j. o preliminaries
tor Dance Beat 2008!
Lets hear your voices!
Hitomi! There you are!
I'm sorry
Here she is.
Hitomi...
It's the first time I've
been to Shibuya, so
I got lost
We just followed
the whole group.
Hitomi.. we came
to cheer you on
Thanks
see you came.
too Iflonfioko
I wondered what that
glitter I saw from
the corner of my eye
Please go to the
judging room
Ken
Ymzo
I came to watch.
This is Ken
d vgtie >d flbout y H
I'm Hitomi's
grandfather
This is Hitomi's teacher.
Nice to meet you
She's pretty
I'm Hitomi's mother
As her teacher, will you
tell Hitomi not to
over extend herself?
What do you mean by that?
Hitomi injured
her foot.
Her foot?
Is it true?
Is it OK?
It's my fault
Hitomi fell when she
chased after me..
That wasn't it...
It's not your fault
But..
Hello..
Hitomi's team.
Junko and I talked
it over..
We decided that it
might be dangerous.
Hitomi... VII have
o lerthShtes to go
on stage next year or
the year after that..
I couldn't go last
year either
I know.
I don't care if
I ruin my leg
You mustn't say
things like that.
What if you do
irreversible damage?
There are times when you need
the courage to give up.
Don't force yourself today, and
wait for another chance
I don't have another chance.
If we lose today, Junko
has to go back home
to her family
She'll have to take over
her family's business.
Yuka wants to make up
with her father, and
she wants him to
see her dance
Today is our
last chance!
So I want to dance!
Yuka... Junko...
Thank you for worrying
about me... I'm sorry.
But.
if I don't dance today,
I know I'll regret it
If there's the
slightest chance that
I can dance, I want to
take the risk.
I think that Junko's in
such a perilous position.
Yuka anxiously waiting to
see if her father will
come, Moe wanting to dance
but being manager
instead, how glad I am that
I became friends with
all of you, how grateful I am to
everyone and how sorry
I am that I got hurt
Ail of these things will
come together in
our dance today
So tomorrow won't do
I want to dance today
Then dance
There are times
like this.
A time when you just
have to do something
no matter what
Don't you know how
Hitomi feels.. ?
I know but
I'm worried.
Mom...!
Just do your best
But you'd better dance
to win! You're not
doing this just
for the memories.
I know
Take on the bufflenx)
everybody's life.
and dance like you've
never danced before
Who some Ring
happens o your tea,
and you have to go
to the hospital..!
Thank you!
Hitomi..
Be careful!
Put your leg up
Shall we wrap it?
Please
We'll be starting
in 30 minutes
Kazu!
What do you want?
The same thing happened
to us...It was me
The first time the three of
us danced together
in New York
I got over-enthusiastic
during our practice
the night before TitJ
I twisted my ankle
But Eiji saved me
He was awesome
He told me that he taught
his little sister how
to do it, too
I need your help
r itrdbc
Entry number one
With their ul Is'
hip hop e jhfere's
WAKANACHI! Give them
a hand!
You're good,
aren't you?
Of course! Kazu's a
master at taping
A master...?
Can't you tell
she's a master?
Did someone teach you
how to do this?
My brother taught me.
He helped Ken and me
so many times
I started dancing when
I was in middle school,
and when my brother found
out, he told me to learn
how to tape injuries
Every time he came home
to Osaka, he'd teach me
how to do this
He said it would definitely
come in handy one day
Because I could do this
for the veteran dancers
who took good care of me
mp uuiiu.. stand up
Be careful
It's perfectly OK!
It's OK!
Kazu...?
Thank you very much
Thank you
I'll start with
our decision
ROSE MARY yiU daticfet
The decision's been made
ROSE MARY will dance
Thank you
I appreciate
what you did
I really loved
my brother
I'm suffering, too.
What am I supposed to
How is it?
PNo "To lem§t€ll.
Are you sure?
I'm sure
Are you really sure?
I'm really sure!
All right!
Let's do it one
more time!
Let's go on to
our next entry
If we didn't become
dancers we would
have become salesmen.
Their specialty dance is the
business card exchange
Here£ ry/iu er two
mo ertime
They're so cute!
Wow!
It's time to change
That was entry number two.
l<bn r r MJ
:i im J]
That was ZANGYO TEATE.
Give them a hand!
Next we have the -dOko i"
group all the way from Osaka!
Their name is BLUE SHOES
Give them a hand!
Wow! That's awesome!
They're good
Powerful rivals appeared
one after another
It made Hitomi
all over again
high level of talent it o
to get to Dance Beat