CHAPTER 9
"I'm Getting Married"
Episode 50
Do you mean...
...you're getting married?
I guess that's what
I'm trying to say.
Can you come out tonight?
I can... I sure can.
I'll meet you at ROSE
at about eight.
I won't tell Dad...
I mean. I won't tell Grandpa.
I'll see you later.
Good evening!
Hitomi...
Hitomi!
Hello...
Have a seat.
Come over here...
Come here...
Katsumata Seiji, 28 years old.
Occupation... Web designer.
What's that?
How should I know?
Why don't you ask him?
They met at the end of last year...
At the hospital where
Keiko works...
He was hospitalized with
acute appendicitis, and
Keiko was the nurse in charge...
I see!
What are you drinking?
I'll have a gin tonic.
Roger!
Sorry to interrupt you...
Pleased to meet you.
I'm Katsumata.
I'm Ippongi Hitomi.
Rose just told me that
you were a patient...?
That's right.
He was hospitalized for
about two weeks at the
end of last year.
I didn't think that we
would be dating at the
time, but he called me.
I spent Christmas Eve last
year in the hospital, and
I had just broken up
with my girlfriend.
And she was the one was
with me at the time.
It was just part of my job.
After I was released from
the hospital, I couldn't
forget about her, and
I thought that maybe
we were destined
for each other...
He seems...
...really nice.
He's really nice!
He sends me about 20 e-mails
everyday, asking me if I'm
okay, and if I'm not too tired.
I just send it without
thinking since I sit
in front of the computer all day long.
You're a web designer, aren't you?
I mainly create home pages
for companies.
He works for a company
in Roppongi.
I guess you'd call it
an IT enterprise.
I want to go out on my
own in the future.
You're spilling it all
over the place.
Tuck this in front.
In front..?
I'll take it for you.
I'll get you a wet cloth.
No... it's okay.
You want a wet cloth?
Come and get the
wet cloth, Hitomi.
Come, and get the cloth.
What do you think
of that Katsumata?
He seems a little weak...
What do you mean a little?
He's definitely not Katsu's type.
Roppongi? IT enterprise?
Web designer?
I hate to say this, but
don't you think he sort
of resembles your father,
a man Katsu hates?
Maybe a little.
I'm positive he can't carry
a portable shrine.
As soon as Katsu sees him,
he might yell, "I won't
let a man like that have
my precious Keiko."
Especially after what
happened with Momo.
It's possible.
Meanwhile, Katsutaro was
at "Matsuri" as a favor
to Yujiro.
After I drink this. I'll have
my last drink of sake.
Mari...
What is it?
Actually, it's about Yujiro.
Yujiro really regrets what he did...
Getting drunk like that, and
holding your hand...
But the dating thing...
He never expected to
be shut out after
asking you about that, so
he asked me to try and
subtly ask you about it...
But I really don't know how
to be subtle about it.
Is that why you had two
bottles of sake?
That's right. I drank it all.
Thanks for being
so considerate.
So how do you really feel?
Actually... I was happy
when he said that.
You were? Yujiro will be
so happy to hear that.
Then why did you tell him
that he shouldn't do
things like that?
I don't know how to explain it, but
I'm a little scared...
...of what will happen
if we start something...
Considering our age.
It seems a little late for
something like that.
It's more than enough for
me to go out once in a
while, and for him to
come here to drink.
I didn't think it was necessary to go
through the formalities
of dating and things
like that at our age.
I see...
Do you understand?
I do... I guess if you were
in your thirties or forties...
But we're past that age already.
That's just it.
Will you just explain
it to Yu for me?
You want me to tell him?
You're giving me
more homework?
I'II treat you to sake.
Let me heat it for you.
I'll take it.
Here you go.
I went to see Dad today
to tell him that there
was someone I was thinking
of marrying, and that I would
bring him over on Sunday.
But Momoko showed up, and
they got into a fight
about your dad...
And I thought, "Oh no!
Katsumata's the type
that Dad hates."
Actually, it seems strange
that he's your type, Keiko.
That's right.
I thought you liked the
more masculine type.
Maybe it's because
m a nurse? but
I seem to have a weak spot
for guys who need a lot
of attention
And most of all, it's the
first time anyone has
asked me to marry him
So I thought,
Why not?"
What do you think, Hitomi?
Do you think Dad will like him?
I don't know...
I think it's important to
take him by surprise.
You know how Katsu is so quick
to start an argument.
What should I do?
You have to judge his mood.
How about if the two of you
standby at Mako's place,
and Hitomi will see if he's
in the right mood, then
call you two over?
That might be a good idea.
Will you do it, Hitomi?
This coming Sunday.
Got it. We'll wait for
the perfect timing.
Hitomi!
Grandpa...
How was Mari?
I understand how
Mari feels, but
I don't know if Yujiro
will understand the
subtle nuance...
You're back...
Were you waiting for me?
No, I wasn't, but I couldn't
help wondering what you
two talked about...
I'll tell you now.
i want to hear, too.
You, too?
You don't want me to?
It's not that, but I would
have to explain a lot
of things... about getting drunk,
and everything else.
I already told Hitomi
about that.
About you doing this, and
Mari doing this to you.
You already told her?
He told me.
Come on in, Yujiro.
Come on in.
I see... is that it?
I'm relieved...
That Mari didn't hate
me for what I did.
She told me that she really enjoyed
your date to Kamakura.
That's why she wants to
keep things the way
they are now.
I think I understand.
You do?
I had a friend in
Sapporo like that.
They loved each other, but
as soon as they started
dating, they broke up.
We haven't verified yet
if Mari loves Yujiro.
We don't know yet, but
Mari says that they're
past the age to be
talking about love.
But, I think she does
love him... otherwise,
she wouldn't have gone
to Kamakura with him.
I agree.., She does,
doesn't she? Thanks.
I think it's important
that you put a lid
on those feeling of love
and things like that,
and just go on seeing her as
a customer at her place.
You have to draw the line.
I'll put a lid on my
feelings, and just
go on seeing her as one
of her customers.
Do that.
I will.
A woman's heart is really
complicated, isn't it?
It's hard being a man.
It's so hard that I'm
going to sleep.
Good night.
Yuka's really getting
into it, isn't she?
She's finally made
up her mind to
live away from her parents.
What is she going to
do about money?
She's going to work part-time
at the pub where I work.
Where is she going to live?
At my apartment... We're
going to be roommates.
It's really unexpected
that you two would
agree to share and apartment.
It really is.
I thought so, too.
But it'll cut my rent in half
so I decided to do it.
The problem is moving out.
I'm not going to use
my parents money.
I won't use their
credit card either.
And of course, I won't
use their car.
So I want you all to help me
move all my things over.
I don't think I'll have
that much stuff.
Okay...
Yuka's house really is
awesome, isn't it?
She really is a rich
girl, isn't she?
It's opening...
What are those bags?
Are we supposed to
carry all of that?
Thanks for waiting.
These are my things.
Help me.
Hurry!
Help me!
Take this.
You take this one, Moe.
Here, Junko.
You want me to carry this?
This is all of it.
Let's get going.
Yuka!
Say farewell to being
a little rich girl.
I don't want to!
Say it!
Farewell, little rich girl!
Let's race!
Wait!
Wait for me.
Hitomi and the others are
running so that Yuka can
start a new life.
Continue...