CHAPTER 20
The Next Step"
Episode 118
~D <D—^J (11
Written by.
SUZUKI Satoshi
JVIusic By.
YAMASHITA Kosuke
This is IppongiHitomi
S t!*j|I liworkiru ere rtTii
!5f he next e£k
Give h s of
Use that d V er there
itomi ill e working
o's office as
a part-time 0fk§r
Can you use a compote ?
A little 1t
Then will fbiinnntff1
this list
All riaht
Hit Tni?
Will H ^lfed
thlslor
JEtfvT 11 n< n
this
Allfialft.
Answer the ptr Tfes Tiile
we have \irtn^ting
fay
Sorrf^but can you iso
p ocure the eqdipment?
flitomi
Get the ento
lunch , oo
We can t go out
to lundh Joday
Okay
Take notes.
Write it down1
I'm counting on
you, Hitomi.
I'll do*njf
Hitomi stone week
office worker las sta
Tthe office, there was a
oyntainof work to tlo,
ana lor Hitomi wffOVtesn't
us~tllb wo kinjln^an
office, it wasn't easy
Office t asn t easy
h i) 3 JJJ J
Tomorrow's too late
i need it riqht away
By next wSfek Monday then.
This was ihc firs lime
Hitomi hafifi osel m
|i j i twork
sr^was seeing ^r f Tfite first
time H"? standing at
th^helm iTIhe company
j Oil!*) 3 J hi
waiting
JWe'll g&^with Monoka s
proposal
Make up t! IT materials f T
the presentation
3'iTrs Trv to keep
/on waiting
This way, please
Can you sent! e
fax fever for me?
Take :are of it form .
\ie' I „ eavini flow
aiLh
Assistant Branch Manager...
J3 J19J 1?
How bfcuttaking
a short break7
^nk you
•Can a I o., ' om"
or i an ue
h, s t
wa^ ly mpre.sed
iVif) ^^a/yxjy:
Is t Iwa s ikefiis
ho. its us ..
n<. Us snecia iy
his
]yj -Ha ju\T)A
Y ;tHre1 wice .. ge.
Don'* i.ention e.
Islt for the pay
Or sjt burden
ot esponsibilit^p
not just that...
t being told,
ank vou '
hank you?
If one of my worker! has a
proble , and I come up
With a good idea, eyil
thahk me for it
If I incr ase sales, te
people at the top will
say. "Thank you," too.
And sometimes thel:ustomers i
use our cosmetics will say,
Thank you"
n other w ft
hi?}) IJmli^
mefe 1|ik in
eve e
B t ikin
13D-L ^
It's not Jift ti J^.o
i roi,
o make ^
u y^a* J)
It means that you foun v
so i Shg in com
with fhe world
tioesn't it?
Rnd for the first time,
II have found
^t you want in life.
f course, the best thing
ouldbedSin In
you tike, and making
hope rifi in-., if. to
Shall I g^toac
to work now9
Her part-time job
is ov£ r
Thank you for working
here for a week.
Jhank yo
Come again when we
^§t~busy okay?
I will
Thank you
if was my pleasure.
haiYk you
Go flbye
Thank you b th o ixing
Binner for Jhe w^ek.
N Dt at all
They're bo.Yi tten
go tJ^it ccoktn .
Their jepfcftoire grown
quite ntioD
fJlSybej jfbe Jikfe^/lari
*wheni£ro/~ljp. and
open my own Jiftie pub
How precocious
m going to do
my homework.
Me too
Take your tfea
with you
o your t^ff.
pjrteaisre Jr
Thanks
Shall I put here?
Sure
We ot it cleaned
up q fckly
It s so different
whe ure here
Gr dpa
^hall 1 massage
^our shoulders9
Jill ou
Really9
Of c lirse
Okay
Reacfy7
It'^tiff!
Jsnfjt?
It's built up over
ihe years
Years 1 stiffness.
it's not easy
working. i§lt?
No matter what "kind
of work $ Udo..
Was i lomoko working hard
he as working
super hard
Tha nard, huh7
When h st thard,
isn t t oppressive7
thi Y h a e ffre to
a ^Juu&iilJs
:>u s nto ie'"jo.
I fee! like n a fling mfe
hat this
what
o _have
Also... Shet larnerthat
you can' just like it
You need people to jell
you, "Tha \ o .'
That's what gives yo
something in comm n
With the rest of
the world.
I feel like she was telling me
f that I ve enjoyed my
life up until now. so
I need to find wh
I want to do now.
Aren't you glatl
you learned Something.
I'm glad.
Do you like what you *Jo
i o now
You didn't before9
I us to think it
was too plain
When us o eemydad
watching the store and
holding clothes up for
the customers to see
Ithougntit o ed
really oring
That's now it s ith
young people, sn'rtt9
MaJFbe
But when 1 o ver he
store an tar e
working in t Jtho ign it
wasjprettytotere in
The kind ^ c othes ou
sell changes ith he
seasons, doesn t
In the spring, you II
school clothes, n
n the summer. youN>e I
Aloha sh r s
began to think x>f it
a business that tun s
the seasons o his o n
Then it escalated fbm
there, and Ytoegan \
•feel as t V>ugh a n
charge fw t vet e
til this nei hborh od d
in th$rjc«oses.
That's what it jriean o rj(
There aren t nany peo ..e
who find pb h ithe
like from thetoegin In
so! don't
//hat's
wrong with grdluall le nm
to like*wh 1 you do.
That may be true
Ypu're good,
aren't you?
Am I?
Press 0own hard
around the neck
That's it. !
^The dried bonito in
s Iciji makes a
•different soup .base..
Your miso soup will
change from today.
Thank you for the meai.
it's okay
Ill get t
Thank you
Hey, KEN! Did t>u
sell anything7
A little over
10,000 yen
You ve gotten good at
this, havent you?
Wha .will you have, KEN9
%/liso ma 1< el, .medium bowl,
arge-serving..
Oife&rd fllfjjiisSjriackerei,
medium owl. large serving...
I'll pay for yours.
Thar
Thank you
Hep lygj itintp into
his role as the-sec- nti
g&nbr li5fif)reside. 1
isnt+ie^
4keVies ^rryingth^
"wei laji
ion his sh Ider
Je\ come1
Moe1
Hello.
Mayuge Neko" again?
Mr Ishn called,-End asked
if we'd do it again this
coming Saturday
Sure. 'II do it.
It s been a while
since I danced.
wpnder //hat to flo about
the other members..
That's right..
I know someone.
Mayuge Neko ?
Yes
Me'?
It's thistance... the one
Yuria a H Akira were
eachinjj you at the
flower-viewing|3arfy
4 knowlh lit
It steady popular
with Tiildren..
Weil have to make you^ip
a littl lit..
Just with £ome whiskers
like a ^St...
ve never done anything
like that before.
You won't do jt7
I ll do it
Tha ~k you'
Actually...
We need one more person...
We need a group of
f tir to dance .
One more person. 9
ThisiS more un
thanl thought.
Do you likelt?
I feel like I can dante
a little differs: lly
Girls are lucky
Tjiey look good in
stuff lik^his.
How's this.. ?
fperftt, KEN!
They'll loVe it!
hope so
Wait a jminute
Maybe it should 6& a
little ^>re colorful
Colorful?
Where?
ay be at the base
£>f <pie whiskers.
s try that
to s ike itll turn
ont to be an awesbme
per ormance of
JJlayugri^eko"