HAPJER 9
I'm Getting Married"
Episode 54
TcayJ fen. fe^av^tomeet
1th ek
oya
fice like
the a
JilJ
Be there m.
That's so early!
It's £00 early.
This is going to be
a business trip
It's in tami
Atami?
M M
' I
fm m
/tg
Thanks for waiting
Shall we go?
This is a regular hot
springs inn, isn't it?
That's right
So "here are we
gofng to dance?
It's what always comes
with aplace like this
At a banquet room
A banquet room?
Excuse me
This is a little
too tight
m sorry
J was a/ool!
I thought it was going to be
on a Las Vegas-style stage
u're too naive,..
Di u forget? This is
Mayuge Neko."
A/ill |he guests be
rinkmg here?
I'm sure they will be.
We're going to be dancing
for af&nchtof drunks.
I can't do that.
I don't want to
I'm going to
gum it down.
Wait, Yiika
Excuse me
We tarl'X dance in front
Ofya un'ttbf drunks.
{
W ^an't dance ill rout j
of a bunch of dru l<s
They're not serving an\
tiquor St this liquet
^fs^ntertainment for the
zAo crtsenior citizens' c
It's entertairime or the
ocal senio ftiziis club
A senior -stiAns club?
f i idi b i iyui iicy iwci tr
suppose Vi an
nka" ^Japane oik)
^singer impersonator,
J>ut he couldn't make it
t the last minute
^Sowegot he
job instead
Try to gel he old f Ik "16 join
the fun like the last time.',
There s a dressing room
back fhere, so yo
get every n
f you want to to ice,
we have the i eo d
everythin I
We're counting on you
T i&y won /be drinking
It's like walkin
int^ian6ther e a
Li % going back to
the Showa era.
wonder iflbl ^folks would find the
Mayuge Neko" entertaining?
They won't be interested
from the beginning
ifstfe they amejiere
ex Acting t5 hear
some "enka" singer.
Shall we dance to
erska'* music9
No way
Then what are we
going to do?
Let's just decide if we're
gbing to do it or not v
u mean you would c6ftie
all the way here, and
go home without
doing the job**
It can't be hei fed.
I just don't fee!
like dancing
That's not professional.
What is 'professional" anyway?
Finishing what f %y
ask you to do
I don't agree with you
f you can't show them something
that you thi?ik is good,
I don't think you can fulfill y ur
responsibility as a professional.
You're too logical.
What do you mean?
That's why you always end
up fighting at the pub
She jDst ignores the
customer's order,
and tells them wh t she
thinks is better.
When you go o a restaurant,
the sommelier recommends
tHe Wine,-doesn't Jie?
t's apub, so you
haveto<J<Hs bring
whaijhetustomer orders^
"et'sYiot fight about
the pub right now
Okay
As your manager fl have
something to say
think it can't be help if
we deci e not to do >i!s
No* want to do it
But Hitomi *
hat's your reas for
wanting to do this"?
I have a feeling that if
we quit now, the four
of us t be able to
dance togef ■ V again
I want to do it...
To^elp us o
form a un .
ot Id on the
dea of uhit, .but
like our spirit
ou W ance with
u t spirit alone..
You ave to have an idea
How about this?
What is it?
It's a "bon" dance re d
ft has the dance
moves, too.
Let me see that
Can we use it?
1 think we might be able
o use some of this
Will it wo K>
Let's give it a tr
What made you suddenly
want to leam to dance?
I realized heft 1 went to
the club with Hitomi..
ukciy neA< j;u.btj.
So the next time I go with
her, if I'm really good
at it, it would make
me look good
Next!
T tit would make ou look
good, wouldn't it?
Okay... together now
But was surprised at
Keiko s announcement.
idn't you like
(hat Katsumata?
How could I like him?
I don't know about Ihis
web or IT stuff, but
that guy can't even carry
a portable shrine
now^oii really love
eiko, don't you?
\0 ourse n<Jt! AA/ho wants
a tomboy like that?
I'm just worried abou"her,
She's like 6 little
sister to me.
ittle worried abfout
hat Katsumata, t ^o
You see what I mean?
nty been ix months
jnce hey/siar e! dl ti
ve that starts off
dzmgus a<ly
urnST)Ht qi ick$
That's just it
It's only been
six months
fter only six months,
already her fiance
ust feme red.
A lot of my predictions like
-this have"been wrfrng
The coupfes J think w Tit
last long, endup hippy
o that meahs his one
Will work ut
What are you
talking about?
They look like a hard
audience to please.
If we can get this crowd
going, it ifteans we're
really good, doesn't it?
I'm determined pow
I didn't expect that
from you, Yuka
I just love a
hallenge'
it's almost time
Standby
Good afternoon, all of you
in the 'Full of Life Club '
Did you njoy the
*hot springs bath?
I'm so fglad.
What e e in ore for you
toda is « 1 -Nlaneki Neko "
/
(becko n cats), b \ e
Mayuge e o' (eylbrow cats).
eas - ive them
j^Ljii-n
• Mil
da t
e version
U J\ jpJ
a ake up*
It's a 'bon" dance See?
It's a Mbon" ance. See?
What do yo n
Isn't it i n
That was a disaster,
wasn't it?
I thought it would "be
a hit with Jherr.
it's net easy e ng
a dancer
3:OJY/J/S
i not rn esame
^ he la im
imepla in inj .
JJ- J jljh
o iveri n s
now tasked you 1o
, oth impossible>
eel b tlUb t f
Please don't be upset,«md
ork^vith 0 /^jain
Here's bOr fee for today,
and n lace of a bonus,
I'm giving you coupons to
use the ot springs bath
Please use jt.
I guess we'Il^ust take
liat we can et
Let's go.
Re&dy?
Tlitomi... 6u're really
good 1 getting people
to do things, aren't you?
9 6u talked me into
it again today
I just want to dance
with ml of you
That's jwhat i like
about dancing
When I felt lonely in
Sapp to, found
friends in dancing
Friends, huh?
That fnight not
-be a bad thing
I'm going to play, too
You are?
s
It's Mr. Katsumata
What to coincidence
i hanks for waitin .
What's this?
Cute, isn! it?
It's cute.
is it a matching so ?
Shall we go?
But he wasn't there
with Keiko