HAPTER 18
Season of Love"
Episode 105
Written by.
SUZUKI Satoshi
JVIusic By
YAMASHITA Kosuke
Engli li Subtitle By
ttlPpbN GQ iDBN NETWORK
/IQJ^
jinU y;^ «p?
BiJilL,
wait mm&
JJD iaslil
Jfitomi1
Hitbmi*
the >iOe
Don't scare me
like that.
f had a strange dream
The service for th "firsi
anniversary of Setsuko s
death was over.
On this day.|fi§tppongi
family was filled with
ervous anticipation.
It was "the flay the
announcement would
be made for t teTfcSu t§
of Akira's entrSfi
that's wrom, Akira?
Afent you going to eat?
t)o T ojr lomachtiur 7
* as /ordering
what would Jia W ?
I don't 3 in.
Butj/ou saidjou did
well on the exaif?.
thought I didy/ell, but
what if there were o hers
who did much better?
But the resi its are out
already aren tthey?
So even if you ^off about
if now. the resu ts won t
change, will |hey?
TWs trite ut
Worrying won t do any good,
So don't you hin it's
better to stop worrying
and just enjo ing
your breakfast?
JlliesI
fiUelrcious.
Isn't it?
It was/fealty busy again
tfay, wasn't it?
We finally have a
chance to rest.
ito i really
som thing drastic
h 1 was a old mo e
1 think she should
reconsider
What yW
talking ab ut
W lit are you
talking about7
You're ^getting marrie ,
aren t you?
You're getting arried,
aren \ y
Who s getting fi§cP
lA/ho's ge.iing'm ~TrJ§8?
You
Me? Who miliarying?
No, I'm
! wouldni
do th
But as saying
before you came
Isn t my bride here yet?"
He %'s r darling
He's not mjFpla ling!
What tell
them an y?
JDontgt ethatl
ou've been telling
everybody that you
and I are g tfing earned
haven't you?
No I didn't
I said it was a dream
it was a dream ..
Everit \ was a $ream,
it s very anno in .
l3on t ever dream
about that ajpftfil
I can't help it!
You came out... Wearing
awe cling gown.
A wedding g n
And theiwopf us
were doing this .
That's right
It's Vrfel/frrith just
the two of us, but.
That's a strange re m.
So you te I nt
to mirr
Puttinn thai .aside...
In the end, you didn't
marry Hie
A guy showed , and
took y *ti a y
KEN?
Th Itlream is full
of holes..
First offell^EN and 1 are
not getting married...
We're not Ven d ling!
And ev Yi ifjby ome rhiracle
that should happen..
Youii&v Yio reason
to complain.
I don't (ike that guy
\Nhp
He's using his t tQ^
to hit on
He's not hittin
me'
And besides, the c fier
Lflay, I'm the' ritTSftho *
panted to talk o im
What ab ?
I wanted to fell him
to enter Dan Beat.
Then why doesn't he?
He's a dancer; sn't « ^
ffe is, but heiiasnt
We had a good friend he
"fid L
wa , he just h^s
eas
I see! I see it all
clearly now.
No matter what you sa ,
you like the guy.
h s that thgfemly vsfay
U* tlS ?
Acting Presided...
Why did you take sSHTany
orders again, and all of
them small orders, too?
ISon't keep doing the same
thing over and over again
Gfet off my tack!
We re in the service
i aiistry soVrtiats
wrong ith t king orders
from our £USto s?
Butu{!ici ame
thing thfe last time
What's wrongf
What's going on?
Hitomi... Telephone!
1!o Akira
How id jt go
J } \
Akira parsed his exam7
He did
C r ationsl
Wh \ h ^r ntfpa?
ust calle him.
He was really happy
i p J
Everyone £er is
eel bratihj>t o
Thank you! \ fie ry^u1
Akira passed his
entrance exam1
Congratulations Akira
wasallfeiojfetli my
firs\ lioicetii s Tiot>l.
I, V
support y Yrgavfetrie.
Dad... iTttttky ulor
^flng Vtoglifr*
jti ,1om llfhc
I'm sorry I adey&O-woFry^
along the Way lien I
zeroes on my lelfts^&nQ
told youl w ^srVt going
EriflJ* izhxtl
Iso 4Thank you, Hitomi
&nd Yiina forgiving me
r&ouragement ail the tinl^.
Mn rcllytjrateful
When l|tart hill s W1* '
Ill ytftk^vefi harder in
scho&fend &tlhomfe €00
I'm counting on II ;o jj
PJj^ jDll^IIb /
We're ll fcotilifig
on you. too
Shall we^elnow?
Let's drink a toast*
Congratulations. Akira!
Cheers1
it s a present for Akira
Jor passing iiis e^ifi
Thank youf
ira will be so happy
mBoiglad #or^\kira
ereallyitforked fiard
Here this is
ontheiiouse
Thank you
So, how is itjj Ing
withyou?
ow is what going9
Your guy... Mr. Suzuki...
Who-?
That's rigfl..
is name is Suzuki.
It realty Is a
misunde standing.
There's nothing
etween ^s
That's just for
now^sritJt7*
^venmthe future
That's because you
thinkthat way
You .never know how love
dsvJestineclio turn put
Why does it matter
soinuchilo you9
I'm^vorri Itabout you
Yo re past 20, and you
donftiav boyfriend
ou should have seen
when I was 1)..
Iwa so popular lien we
had co-ed mi fers
I had trouble-keeping
up with them
Til l?s have changed.
T ^r re a lot ttjirlswho
have boyfri^hds
epon'tfee!*h 1
o e is ever
ing
We e ifferent from
girs n the past
If s ow yo ...
But fy u do fall in
love ^ke sure you
don't ave any regrets
Yo can hide it from
others, but don t
hide your feelings
fr m yourself
It'strue that I want KEN
to dance again
Dance is all he has
he three if us.
itomi?
W Ye^ou thinking
"bout something?
Could it be love7
No. it's not.
flils, iSII me...
Thank you... But jm Tine.
DonWorr
Yuria! Let's play arts
since I passed my^xam.
It's no fun ^playing
.vitlrjustlwo of us.
/Ill you play. Hitomi?
Sorry... IJI tfss.
It can't|>e helped... I guess
I
p ay wit. you leri.
What you need when it comes
to love is Murage
I can't forget!
I cant forget'
I love him"
Stop it! You re disturbing
the neighbors
Stop it1 Stop
2008fp3H
i vidian fdiiy my wu
§e s efore ance ea
March,"2008
2008f£3E
t a ch, nd nl wo
weeks eTore Dance <§a
March.^008
itomi was giving
it all she had
It s hot1
WhaHi a p n en ed.UHitomi?
Y li're full of
nergy-today
you're inspiring
me-stbo
You're ing go fi.
We only ttavelw "weeks'
That's our Jeader1
uka. We have to
Tt
to work.
^SlUl we call it a
<Jaylor today7
We're leaving
See you I ler!
Shfe s toned down,
hasnj-she?
You me~n Yyka?
She's a little rich
nirl isn t she9
She used to wear ore
xpensive things before
%'s "having a hard time
Jbecause of her father
Is that right?
Junko s having a
hard time, too
Her family runs a "gyoza"
restaurant in Utsunomiya
and shfe ""being pressured
to take over the business
and she s being pressure
to take over the business.
it sounds like ever
having a hard lime,
doesn't it? But it'll e p
them to dance bette
Each carrying
own burden...
That's how we feel.
Because dance is life
What a good thing to sa .
Dance is life, love, spar .
Hitomi1
thought you went to
your part-time j V
We met up with BLUE SHOES1
BLUE SHOES from Osaka
had come to them