CHAPTER 7
"Lets Be Friends"
Episode 42
Stop it!
Yuzo and Hitomi came to the
dance club to save Yuka
who had gotten drunk after
failing the audition.
Who the heck are you?
You won't believe
this, but...
This young lady and I...
...ate pot stew together.
So what about it?
That's why I'm taking
Yuka home.
Don't get in our way!
Old man!
Wait... Hold on...
We'll leave the rest
to you, Yuzo.
Hey! You can't just
take her home!
Hey! Are you okay?
Yuka!
Are you ok?
Get away from me!
I don't care what
happens to me.
Don't say that. You need
to take better care
of yourself...
I don't want to hear
any preaching.
You're probably
laughing at me.
The rich girl who rented a
studio to practice,
and still failed
the audition.
My dancing is all just for
a rich girl's
self satisfaction anyway.
So no one enjoys
watching me dance.
Isn't that what
you're thinking?
Don't talk like that.
If you say that, then you
won't be able to work
hard at it tomorrow.
When I failed the audition,
and  went home, everyone
treated me like
nothing happened.
We prepared dinner like
we always do, and we
ate dinner like
we always do.
And for some reason, that
made me feel better.
It's like they were
telling me...
It's not important.
No matter what happens,
life will go on
like this everyday.
No matter what happens,
you can still cook
nice, hot rice.
I'm sorry, but I don't have
any idea what you're
talking about.
It's just...
...that you're not living
your life alone.
There are lots of people who
worried about you.
Lots of people want to dance
and be friends with you.
You're the one who's closing
your heart to everyone.
It's such a waste.
When you're that good
a dancer, you should
be able to enjoy
dancing more.
Is this where you were?
I looked aII over for you.
You turned off your
cell phone...
Let's go home... Your
father is worried.
Never mind!
I'm going home on
the train today.
Hitomi...
What's your goal?
Next year's Dance Beat.
So you actually have
a real goal.
Miss Yuka!
That's right... No matter
what happens, it's not
like the world turned
upside down, is it?
Even if you failed
the audition...
Life will go on like
this everyday.
Isn't that right, Daisuke?
That's right...
That's what it means...
That's right.
Even for me... when i lose all
my money at the horse races,
I feel like my life is over.
But when I come to work,
and I'm working like
crazy, before I know it,
I forget all about it.
And when Saturday comes
around, I'm raring to
go at it again.
That's not the same!
That's exactly
what it is.
No, it's not!
Are you going to hit me?
Welcome!
KEN?
RAY told me that the miso
mackerel lunch set is
really good here.
I can use this, can't I?
Sure... Are you sure you
want the miso mackerel?
Miso mackerel, medium bowI,
large serving with extra
pickled vegetables.
One miso mackerel, medium
bowl, large serving with
extra pickled vegetables
coming right up.
Knowing that you like miso
mackerel gives me a sense
of kinship with you...
Did you have something to
do in this area...?
I have a meeting after this,
but I wanted to tell you
something while I'm here.
You wanted to tell
me something?
Your dancing at the
audition wasn't bad.
Really?
Thank you.
You made a mistake, an
you missed the beat of
the music in some places.
Your moves weren't that
well-executed... And you need
to build up your muscles.
Also, considering the
differences in your
height, you might have used
some different moves.
They're nothing but bad things.
But your dancing had the
one thing that was
most important...
You were enjoying yourselves
when you were dancing...
It was fun watching the
two of you dance.
It really was good.
Please come back again.
And...
What?
Please tell me more about
when you were dancing
with CHEAPASS and when
you were in New York.
If we have the chance...
Thank you!
Good for one large bowl
at Morimoto Shokudo
Hitomi!
Have you seen Yuzo?
Yuzo?
I haven't seen him
since last night.
While I was in the bath,
I think he went out
drinking somewhere.
I forgot all about it!
What?
Yuzo!
Where was he?
You idiot!
Where have you been?
What happened after that?
Hitomi...?
Here... have one.
I got to be real good friends
with those pick-up artists.
We were drinking
and dancing...
Bring him some water.
What's all the commotion?
Pull yourself together.
Dancing sure is fun!
Hitomi!
Rose!
I heard you failed
the audition!
I sure did.
Thinking that you would
win the audition was
a big mistake! Dancing
isn't that easy.
I'll do my best!
Yuka!
What are you you doing?
With so many choices, I don't
know what to get.
But they're all delicious.
I'll take 100 grams each of  the
"shirasu" (young sardines)
and "kyarabuki".
(stalks of butterbur in soy sauce)
"Shirasu" and "kyarabuki"...?
For some reason, this town
is really soothing.
You...
...told me last night that
even though you failed the
audition, after eating dinner
with everybody, you felt
so much better.
I don't have that...
Ever since I was little,
I hardly ever ate together
with my parents.
In exchange, there was a
housekeeper who would
fix my meals for me
everyday...
Maybe that's why I got so
caught up in dancing.
When I'm dancing, I don't
feel the loneliness.
It's the same or me.
After my mom divorced my
good-for-nothing dad,
she used to work until
late everyday, so...
I always ate by myself.
Then you're lucky that you
get to live with that
lively family now.
That's right, l am.
Can I...
...come by your house
for a little while?
Sure. Come to the house.
Grandpa will be happy
to see you.
Really?
Let's go.
I'm home!
I brought Yuka with me.
Hello...
I'm sorry about
the other day...
Our idiot neighbors had
to ruin things for you.
No... I should apologize
after all the trouble
you went through to fix the
meal, and I left early.
This is just a token
of my apology...
You didn't have
to do that...
I love "tsukudani".
(food boiled down in soy sauce)
Thank you.
I'd better be going.
Aren't you going
to come in?
I just came by
to apologize...
We didn't get to do
anything for you...
I'll be going.
I'll see her off.
Thank you.
Be careful!
Yuka!
Don't tell me you came
here just to apologize?
I don't like your dancing,
but I like your house,
and this town.
See you!
Thank you!
I'll see you in school.
Hitomi felt like she had gotten
a little closer to Yuka.
Excuse me...
Did you want something
at your house?
No... it's nothing.
Who in the world
was that anyway?