r £ £ r(95)
CHAPTER 16
Goodbye Shota"
Episode 95
Written by.
SUZUKI Satoshi*
^Vlusic By.
YAMASHITA KosuKe
EngliTi Subtitle By
fiippbN gqIden Network
hota will be in ut
of this house afte. e
econta term s
Decemb i t
That's about a too th
from now, isn't it?
That s rig ...
Let's treasure
each r&ment.
Study hard
Hitomi. *
Just for a day... I'd like to
do something for Shota
I want to show him a
place that i like
It's okay... Where is it9
Tsukiji
Let's eat at the diner
you work at
That's agood Klea
Maybe I should takeiiirh
to my da ce school, 4oo
vant to go,-too
You do >
Then shall we take Shota
out just for one day7
It was Decembp? 24th, and the
day was drawing near when
they would have to
part with Shota..
What do you think?
Are you surprised7
This is the spirit
of Tsukiji.
It was still |)arKy\/ en
everyone started
working, so b* his time
they're ail starved..
Tsukiji nlen^ll have pride
n the work they do
Men pridethfemselves in
Icing \h&t Jives on
their work and working
n arhfest, %o prow up
to be a man vyfio tias pride
tn what he does.
hat are you having. Akira,
Yuria and Shota?
,Miso mackerel, medium bowl,
large serving with extra
ic!led vegetables
One miso mackerlnneUiam bowl,
large serving with extra
pic'l tl vege ables.
You'fe^oingio
• 1 • • • •
That was great
What do you think7
Isn t Hitomi cool?
She's cool
She is.
Everyone practices in
earnest like this..
that's why ney can
have fun d Ming
That's it
efriave special
ueststo a .
ntroduce them, i o i
Somepf you may already
know but these are
the children I'm living with.
Akira, Yuria and Shota.
AYW T
1 brought the three of them
here to show them how
earnest I am in
<5/vhat do
! heard you're
good dancers
eM up'
his is o today
Formal?
We $ant Sh'la to remember *
the taste of f sukishima
It s ready!
Go ah€ad, and feat'
Llts eat.
Dothey Jiave "monja'
irHzu-Oshima?
bonder
Theyjnust
After all, Izu Oshima is
__spart of Jokyo, iTi t it?
That's right...
Monji" is a dish that's
representative of Tokyo.
Even if they do, ^BfiJI only
find this Tsukish ma "monja"
here in T is ima.
That's rig W II
very ie St (Fl ly
find our bran TIifMFija"
here at a u rant
You don't have fo rush,
and eat it like^that
Cool it off first...
I'm going to eat
ots of it.
Lots and lots of jt.
It's your faulffor
saying that
A m sorry
Don't eat so fast.
Shall we go7
ji^v^rwiiviuiiho^
-But J Jived ith kir
That's right... hota arhe 1
o i e e e tei o
jttiMtej, iiiiiiiii?
But it's stran e .
When I think that we were
raised by the same ath
_and mothers feel tike e'
brother anfl iste .
. .i jji.
J fell 1 same v a ...
YguVemy ol est isier.
Soy&u'fTlth
^ame; a/..
Then v ut 7
Am I th§ youn er ister?
You'retiot Jike a Is er...,
BdVV e ok like
jour mother ith ..
Otfr'blcJer othlTl
"^You're right!
No,J'm no !
r 0
rea. lady- ike
But you et along
feally.jiice
You had a hard time
at the beginning
Shota... When I le.ttha "
house I was sad but
It'll be okay
Dad and I will always feel
as though we're father
and daughter
Shall we-go?
Thataight.. They had a
areweil party for Shota
Everyone's drunk already
Good evening
^Rose9 Did you
know Shota7
We CfeetHo see each other
once in a while when
1\vas out walking,
didn't we?
Sh a asked m§ aYe tly
ha question ion£?Tay
Wh id he ask you?
He ed me f I as
an ncle or an aunty.
What didyoTlltiim7
human being."
Thank you for waiting.
Are you ready?
Are you ready7
Let me have
some first.
Wait a minute..
Shota wrote something, ,so
he's going to read it how.
My Memories pf Jsukishima"
.by Saito^Sliota, third grade,
j^roup one..
^otne pf my memories of
STsukishima .are sleeping
on bunk fceds with Akira.
p aying cards wit. Yuria.
Getting scolded ad
Taking a bath ith Dad
was sad "hen ^/!om died,
b i Hitomi came, and
it was Ln ajain
Fixing m ^fls with
everybody.
Eating meals with
everybody..
Yuzo andT Untie Yujiro
playing with me..
Getting side dishes
fromUme.
Keiko taking me
to the festival
I'll forgd
s iss tiria.
I hope you all won t
-forget me either.
lorn..
Akira..
Yuria..
Hitomi...
And everyone in
Tsukishima..
Thank you alt for helping
to raise me..
That's all.
-hlJJ
Two more days before they
have to part with Shota