CHAPTER 12
I Can't Go to the Festival
Episode 71
I'll show you how to
get there, Eriko
I'll eat it all
The lunch party
at Ume's house had
turned into a disaster
You press down, and
pull it off with the
spatula, and eat it.
I've never had
this before
Hasn't your husband
ever brought you to eat it?
If we come this far we always
end up going Ginza
I want to eat
something else
Why don't you
just try it?
Your dad and grandma
really love this
What do you want to eat?
Hamburger!
Do you have
hamburger?
No, we don't. This is
a monja restaurant.
Spaghetti!
We don't have spaghetti
here
Tuna casserole.
We don't have
that either
That's because this is
a monja restaurant
All we have is monja
That there is monja!
Maybe there's nothing
here you can eat...
Icecream!
Icecream?
That's good!
Is it OK? Eating that when
he didn't eat a meal?
It's OK, as long as
it's what he wants
OK, Makoto, ice cream
please
One icecream, Hiroshi
Here you go.
Not this kind, don't you
have real icecream in a cup?
No, we don't
I guess it'll do then.
Why don't you try it, Takeshi
I'll try it.
It tastes lousy
I thought so.
Can you throw
this away?
Are you sure
about this?
You're trying to
please your wife
Your wife is trying
to please your son.
If I lived there
I'd have to try to
please someone
I don't like that
Then do you plan to stay
in this house forever?
It's hot in the summer
and cold in the winter
It's bad for your health!
It's the house you were
were raised in
I didn't like it.
It was too small and uncomfortable
My house is big!
Everyone has their own room.
I read the books I
like in my room,
my wife watches the
movies she likes in hers
and my son can play
his games in his room.
No one will get
in your way
You can do whatever
you want
Your family doesn't confront
each other, do they?
What do you mean?
Takeshi lied earlier,
didn't he?
He said Shota broke
the planter...
And you just pretended
like you didn't know
If I said something
my wife would have
started nagging me.
So you're running away
You should confront
each other
You live in a big house
with your own rooms,
so it got to the point
where you don't
confront each other
anymore
You're sassy,
aren't you?
That's right, I am!
After all, I'm Momoko's
daughter.
Tetsuo
I'm not going to
do this anymore
I'm against your
living together
Why change your mind
all of a sudden?
Because I'd feel sorry
for Ume if she had to
live with that wife
of yours
What don't you
like about her?
Everything!
She spoils your son
She doesn't care about
other people's feelings
We went to Makoto's place,
but your son didn't
even eat "monja' there
He finally chose ice cream,
but he just took one
bite and left the rest
He said it tastes bad
compared to the kind
he eats at home
Your wife permits
him to do that, you know.
She told Makoto to throw
icecream away
What about her is
a "good wife"?
Is it because she's the
daughter of a director?
Because he paid for your house?
Anyway, I'm completely
opposed to your living
together with Ume.
Wait a minute, Momoko
Don't say things
like that.
His mother has to come
and live with us.
Then let me ask you this...
Why do you want to
live with Ume?
Because it looks bad
After all, it's just
the two, mother and son.
His mother lives in
a cramped place like this
while we're a big house.
it makes us look bad.
That's what my
father said, too
He said it looks like we're
treating her coldly
Is that it, Tetsuo?
Is it just for
appearances?
I'm just thinking about
my mom's happiness.
If you live together
in this kind of form,
how can you expect Ume
to be happy?
But I have a sense
of responsibiity.
It's just for your tedious
sense of responsibility
and society's opinion
that you want Ume
to live with you?
Are you sure you should
be saying that?
What about the
shopping mall?
What about it?
I don't care anymore!
All right, I won't listen to
what you have to say.
Dear! Let's go home!
Tetsuo!
What is it, Mom?
I'm going to stay here
in the tenement.
Everyone here is
more like my real family
Sorry to bother you
Dear, hurry up!
I'm thirsty
Ume, I'll make
some tea
Like her real family?
That's sad, isn't it.
I'm happy that Ume would
say that, but
the reality is that Ume and
her son can't agree to anything.
You should've
seen Mom.
She was really something.
What are you saying?
She couldn't have been.
She said, "Is it just for
appearances, and your
sense of responsibility
that you want to live
with your mother?"
Momoko said that!?
There was talk about Tetsuo's
company letting Mom's
cosmetics company lease
space in their new
shopping mall, but she told him
she didn't care about that
Momoko said that?
Never mind! Just make
me some tea
Tea?
Please make me some tea
Momoko
Are you OK?
It's nothing
It's hot!
What are you having?
Somen noodles.
Somen
You don't have much
energy, do you?
It's too hot
**e r o rtnindofa!!! n a
thoughts, "Tid you in
fire, fire is cool."**
The deadline was fast
approaching to get
the others to participate in
the summer dance contest.
Shall we enter this?
The summer dance contest
Let's form a unit
I'll be the manager.
I don't want to!
Not with this
selfish girl!
I won't do it either!
It's better if you
confront each other!
Hitomi?
Moe.
What do you mean, confront?
I feel like...
I still have my summer
vacation homework
It hasn't been done
I have to try again to
convince Yuka and Junko
but don't know
what to say
Wait here..
Where are you going?
I'm going to get them
and bring them here.
What, Moe!
Just come with me...
Come on
Hitomi... I brought them.
Sit down... Come on,
and sit down
Please listen to me!
What?
What's wrong?
Before it's too late,
I wanted to talk to
both of you.
You all came to the festival
the other day, right?
When we danced at Rose's
place to Mari's singing
the Festival Mambo song
What did you think
at the time?
n
That dancing was fun,
after all
I had fun, too. I thought
I really, really want to
dance with you all again!
So let's not let stubborn
pride get in the way,
and let's all dance
together again.
We still have time
I want to do this.
I want to struggle
and grab onto something.
Maybe that's going
a little overboard, but
The prize is $5000
Let's all split
this among us!
I give up!
Shall we do it?
Really?
You did it, Hitomi!
Let's make a toast
Cheers!
You can have mine, too.