C APTEr!3
The Birth pf ROSE M ttY
Episode 76
Ve re called the
B\pe S^O Is.
What's your name?
IPs a nice name.
Then sho us..
How you^ance
here in kyo!
e'llsh wyou
what we can do
Let's go tside'
I'll sh wyou
A dance b III "had begun
in Tsukishima.
Clap your hands!
1! me, Kazu
Hiiomi.. i II yu.
Which one was better?
It was...
Clap your hands!
Let me, Kazu
II go, Hitoitii
What about this one..
Which one?
Who was better?
Don't ask me
What are you doing?
You're disturbing
t.T& neighbors'
Break it up
J"m sorry
We're leaving
right away
Good work
*Make sure you leave.
Shall we finish this
on the stage then?
Are you taking lessons
somewhere?
HIPZ
RAYs class
We won't lose to you!
Shall ye go?
kymtfs about 1 ib dance
Jjatt \ had spread
throughout the town
hk you for helpin
out all the time...
pjeask^ake care of the
fstorfe again today.
Just lave ittolis.
TsiTushirtna is
rdoting for tu
m e eadbands/O tf
>ler£, Ume. V\fe made
^>rie for you,4oo.
-P your spirit into it
ho cares about
\onomiya"?
\ Th ing of Japanese
pancakes is rnonja"
Monja"'
Yeah!
^onja"1
Yeah'
Do your est, ROSE MARy!
We will!
fiarik ou everybody
hll we go?
e e going to our
an e! \son now.
*Do your best!
oulook good
in that, Ume
Do I?
f's ail the yedrs
f experience.
That's good, Y Ha.
Hike it
think ito,k if the
three of us can do it
hat was great. Yuka!
That was super ool!
*We w Ih't think fcoutthe
individual award nymore
*fhe o 1y way can win
against those girls
is foftvin that contest!
It'll be ROSE GARY'S
showcase, won't«it?
Shall we do our toes y
You almost got i .
Ifiid, didn't P
Once m re!
Your timing s off,
Hitomi.
Once more!
I'm glad we had this
training camp.
Vpn qlad we J^a _|his
training amp..
liiidn'i hink e
ijulj iji
We goi some power froii.
si kishim , idn i e?
I'm clad to, e r^ra.
Hi omi... Yourlimin was
ff during th imax
know
e still have tim
aU/^ UiU ^
e!)! see what we rt
o n ilfti£i .
I'll racti£t.
Osiee more.
On the4 %t day of Ah 1r
tfSlmng camp, "Mr. Ho Ik
incited them to <go out on
his 'ishing£oat to give
ihem a change of scenery
Be carefu!!
Thank you
^e Iffeful!
his is mori,.. Hell
be piloting the boat.
G 1 to it.
h le e boat is moving,
ally dangerous,
o e sure ou stay seated.
When you're on Jhe boat,
you're very masculine,
aren't you, Mr. Honda?
Am P
He 5 normally very quiet,
but when y to really need
him, you c G coun\>n him.
Pon-chan.. 7 ^Remember the
time you saved me when
I wasxJrowning?
That's right. If I hadn't
jumped in, you'd be dead.
You almost drowned?
Really?
When we werfe in
middle school
At a time like that, you
don't think about the
I realized -it, I had
jumped into the water
My dad threw me a flotation
ring, and i grabbed on
to it, and jt saved
my i e oo.
Then the *wo of you
almost drowned?
When something like that
happens, you become
lifelong friends
I'm hoping that someday
he almost drowns, and
I can jump in, and
save his life
And we can both drown
together again
That's how it'll
end up, won't it?
Give me a hand.
There are a four "gals"
here, watching...
Kachidoki Bridge
jsjhat J" %iji?
Tsukiji Market
__Isi^/lfsilkiji?
There s ihe Tokyo Tower!
Was it this close?
It's close, isn't it?
L t^t^e^ou and
the Tokyo Tower.
t' \ a y Yp fe
Jqg fin ^ett Tjat it.
-et'sir "tone
more tim
*tfey kids!
hat ate oTF85!ng
We e practicing
rddnc
Are you going to e. ter^
the contest, too?
No, e'ffc not!
We're "bing to show
it oHitomi
You are? Do your be i.
ey' Shbu callyou^
,aunty or tfcle?*
&>w sho^c i answe« h
m uman In
e o .
oua p9 Th n e're
rien aren
See ou'
Th as pretty~slick.
hfll>ve*trySg
a i n.
Isn't Jhe scenery
pretty nice here?
1A/e re coming jp on
Odaiba soon.
That's KEi
Hey! KEN£ over there...
ign ver there on
the Harumi fier
You mus\J)fe mistake??...
ilJi
Maybe you nodded oft and
you were dreaming.
That can't!) .
But I i n't see
him either