CHAPTER 17
Dance is Life
Episode 100
Written by
SUZUKI Satoshi
Music by
YAMASHITA Kosuke
English Subtitle by
NIPPON GOLDEN NETWORK
We're going to
quit dancing.
Yuka! Junko!
What's wrong?
I'm sorry...I had
a weird dream.
Hitomi!
What's wrong, Hitomi?
Thursday
Fetor
Yuka and Junko aren't
here after all
They both turned off
their cell phones.
h e e n "be fek
ike Is
u a* e o transmit your
iri o he
o he lire n*i 1r
apiitt J lu^s
ome trk
om*n>ac ! Com
lopjl 11 S Sill
No...you have to do it!
Let's do tonce
e . together
c 1 fcome back!
This is no time for me
to be dancing
If I don't take the offer, they'll
have to shut down the
restaurant, won't they?
Come back! Come back!
Hello
Where are you now,
at a karaoke room?
I'm at home...That's
Grandpa singing.
How misleading
I'm at Makoto's place with
people from my company.
We're celebrating again
That's right... We got
another client
Won't you come, too?
Akira. Yuria
My mom asked me
to meet her...
Is it OK if I go?
-4/Vefii e.l ad
Thanks.
You have to "keppare"
in your work
I am "keppatteru"
You have to "keppare"
more since you're
the only guy here
"keppare" more
than Momoko
T(ti& s azumashiktTSi '
TtahiTTtJ§?sta fl
what you're saying.
Can you explain
t zumashikun 1" ^ans
it's uncomfortable.
and keppare" means to
work harder tr/Ji T0 T
Is thto it?
It happens at work, too.
Someone's bothered by
what's happening at
home and can't concentrate
on their work
it's happened to
them, too.
What do you do when
that happens?
I let them alone
for a while
If they make a mistake
I'll overlook it
Even if I'm really worried,
I'll just bear with it
and wait until they
settle down
I don't have
to do that
We have to turn in our
entry by next week
Don't you remember when you
first came to Tsukishima
and you were torn between
your dancing and taking
care of the children,
and you collapsed7
I did that,
didn't I?
I thought I couldn't
-Thfe childr el "fed me
That's what you have to
do for Yuka and Junko
Do your best
Try harder!
Hitomi!
What's wrong?
We thought we'd tell
you tonight
What is it?
We talked it over
We're not going to
enter Dance Beat
Let's disband
ROSE MARY
It's impossible!
Junko and I are too worried
about our families
Don't say that.
We've come this
far together.
We won the Summer Contest.
If we work hard enough,
we'll get through the
preliminaries, too
That's what I thought
until last week, too.
Look at this..
We've already filled
out the entry
Tear it up and
throw it away
Yuka! Junko!
I'll do whatever it takes.
I don't know what
I can do, but
I'll give you whatever
support you need
In any case
It's impossible now
I can't dance feeling
like this.
I'm sorry
Hitomi... What's wrong?
-y did something happen
I'll get it.
ftello... Ippontjl r s dence.
Akira?
£h la!
How are you?
I'm fine.
We're all fine
over here.
Hello... Shota?
It's Yuria
How are you?
I'm fine.
Me, too
Yuria...I want to
talk to him, too.
I'll let you
talk to Dad
Hello, Shota! It's Dad
How are you?
I'm going to school now
You're going to
school now?
How's your mother?
She's fine
Did you make friends?
Lots of friends
Really?
My turn..
Hello? I'll let you
talk to Hitomi now
Here she is.
Hello, Shota
It's Hitomi
Hitomi... I'm on the
youth baseball team
I'm Number Seven
on second base
You're doing well,
aren't you7
Are you working hard
at your dancing?
I am
Dance Beat is coming up
pretty soon isn't it?
Next month
I don't know if I can come
and see you dance, but
I'll be rooting
for you
for you, Hitomi
Thank you.
Do your best.
Shota.
Hitomi?
What's wrong?
What did he say7
Shota! What did
you say to her?
It's not him
Hitomi?
It's not you...
I'm sorry
I'm okay
I see?!i Is that
4fVHdl iidMpciicu
I think Yuka and Junko
still want to dance
But I don't know what
to tell them
I wonder if it's
My teacher said... Don't
give in to our feelings
v in vitb our will
What does that mean7
When you think it's no
good, it's just the
way you're feeling
right at the moment.
it if v. : fh" "I f -M
Z3Ui ;i yuu hunk, 5 udii lu ;i.
I'm going to pass '
it's your will
So if you won't give in
to your feelings and
angon o our will,
ou cantfvin
'
I'll do my best on my
entrance exams, so
don't give up Hitomi
What a good thing to say
He's right, Hitomi
After all, you're
the leader
nti if,yoti ay you're
ot isban irk Mhen
^pu re noi isl Yiding.
e po e"1
What's that7
You taught me, didn t you?
Doesn't that mean "do
your best" in life
Sapporo dialect?
It's "keppare"
P .re "keppare"
I didn't understand
it either
Keppare 1
You tell her, too
Keppare''
What are you doing?
Everyone's feelings were
echoing in her heart