CHAPTER 15
Tearstained Towel Blanket
Episode 89
That's Shota
You're right! That must be
Shota's mother
Then the man next
to her is..
her fiance. He was playing
While I'm dan n , I'll
see that's ong or.
ha^nteJ iDJiYMii
^he e ia i in
FmajjnUig ja p Jl
Wait a minute!
Child care counseling center
Mikie? H was going to
call you just now
Your next meeting
with Shota is
What do you mean?
Hello, Mikie?
Can you hear me, Mikie?
I've lost confidence
I can't raise him,
after all
So
I can't take Shota back
Did something happen?
In any case, let's
meet and
Hello?
Mikie? Hello?
I'm not getting married
after all
If you don't mind
can you explain...?
His mother was more
important to him
than me or Shota.
Even if this is the case,
I don't think it has
anything to do with
taking Shota back
You've finally started to
restore e bond with
him after meeting together
so many times, so I don't
think you should give
up so easily
I can't do it
Unless I have someone
by my side
Unless I fee! secure
I can't raise Shota
The same thing will
happen again
I don't want to make the
same mistake again
What are you going to
do about Shota?
He's going to be sad
He's finally gotten
close to you again
I'm sorry!
Please leave Shota with
his Tsukishima family.
I'm sorry!
Mikie! Open the door
Ms Saito!
Open the door!
We waited an hour but
she wouldn't open the door
She won't answer
the phone either
If we stop the meetings
with his mother now
and forget about her
taking him back,
it will really hurt
Shota psychologicaily
Even if it's not made
clear, children are
very sensitive
He's been preparing himself
to leave Tsukishima and
going to live with
his mother again
ally
callin f riage,
Ms a o i n
41 lirfiii&ij "ni
Mikie s ri s ic
abon it... Ht " e ike
she u je * in r.e
liitl
the nex. in >o now?
We need to tell Katsutaro
about this, don't we?
I'll leave it to you.
If there  rou e ith
Iiis 10 h Carriage
ittias o ece red
Jo i X '
Will it be cleared up?
7e... can't really say
Don't you think that's
irresponsible?
We're sorry
I didn't mean all of you
I meant Shota's mother
How can she say that she
can't take him back now?
What does she mean she
doesn't have confidence?
It's a problem for us too,
for her to say that she
can't take him back now
We'll take whatever
steps necessary
We'll continue to keep
in contact with Mikie
Under the circumstances,
what's most important
is Shota's feelings.
That's right
After he's finally gotten close
to his mother again.
Inoue will explain to Shota
about postponing
their next meeting.
Please gives Shota all the
support he needs
We will
Thank you
About your meeting with
your mother.. She's
too busy to meet with you
this week, so she wants
to postpone it for a while
It's OK
When can we meet again?
We don't know yet
She's busy at work so
she can't find the
time to meet right now
So Mom doesn't love
me, after all
That's not true.
She's just busy
at work
That's right.. She's
your mother, Shota
How could she not love you?
She loves you very much!
Then why won't
she meet with me?
Katsutaro started to tell
him that it's not that
she doesn't love him, but
I9CC Tk
I can't blame Shota for
feeling that way
I called Mikie, but as usual I just
got her answering machine.
She hasn't gone to work
either, has she?
So it seems.
She can't recover from
the shock of having
her engagement
fall apart, but
What we need to worry
about is Shota
You're right
What's most important is
Shota's future.
Yes, take heart,
and keep working at it.
The next day Hitomi went to
the child care counseling
center by herself.
Shota's deeply hurt..
He's saying that his mother
doesn't love him after all.
Shota's in pain
I'll give her a
piece of my mind.
Tell me where she lives
I'm sorry. We can't do that.
^JOlDL tfl^T^l
that ^car.
Mikies ill and
emotionally unstable right now
Until she recovers
U J • 'dL ^i'J'ik, iJl'J 1-^jJjH} i' 1
de Ire tb rais o a again
But if we do that, it'll hurt
Shota even more.
He's been hiding it all
this time, but he's
wanted to go to his
mother all along.
You've opened the lid
on those feelings...
Isn't there anything
you can do?
Hitomi... We Yittp do what
we can to support Shota
But in order to raise a child,
St important
the parent's feelings.
If they have what it takes,
then we'll do our best
to support them
But they hav to
have the desire.
She couldn't ar e it 1
what Mr. Wakayama
Hitomi didn't know
where to turn.
The next day...
I never heard of anything
so terrible
I feel so sorry
for Shota.
I agree... How could she
say she wants him and
then turn around and say
she changed her mind?
What kind of mother
is she anyway?
I can understand that
i 3
your on emen all
t like that, but
she can at least raise
her own child
No, she's just weak...
A woman who can't live
without a man...
I understand how
she feels.
But the woman is hopeless
He \ a « edlo get ned. btSt
ie gave it«jp because
iu^ J} ;>
didn't he
He should just tell
her to butt out!
fhelo ^f
Idtel
y ujesocool!
That man is the root
of all evil.
Who is he anyway?
His name is Imazata, and
he's heaorily s to of
a Japanese restaurant
in Akasaka.
Imazato in Akasaka?
You've heard of it?
It's a well-known and
established restaurant
His picture came out in
fit e restaurant
iriQ ryjs magazines
He sells bento undies at
the department store,
doesn't he?
That's right, that's him.
I've seen him
around here
Me, too
Probably to shop for
the restaurant.
Really.
He comes every Friday to
buy dried food at Shige's
I've never talked to him, but
Shige told me about him.
What time does he come?
The last time I saw him,
it was about 10 o'clock.
Friday at 10?
That's right now!
Hitomi!
Wait, Hitomi!
Come back!
I'd better go along, too
Bring him over here!
Okay
I'll punch his
lights out!
You don't have to go
that far..
\fyjQl >• J b
orkefl p^boutit...
^fs go back inside.
Go inside and
have some tea.
Hitomi.. That shim
O O • « 1 • • *
The guy in the suit!
You're Imazata,
aren't you?
Yes, I am ...
What is this about?
I'm a member of
Shota's family
My grandfather and I are raising
Shota in Tsukishima.
Hitomi had something
that she wanted to tell
this man who ended his
engagement to Mikie.
and hurt Shota badly