HITOMI
CHAPTER 8
"Two Kinds of Love"
Episode 46
Shall we do this
coming Sunday?
Where to?
To the place where you parted
with your real father when
you were five years old.
I don't want to go.
What are you doing?
Were you the thinking
about Naoko?
No, I wasn't.
Good night.
He's embarrassed.
It's Sunday.
Hitomi?
Where are you going to dance
for this part-time job?
I won't know until I go.
It's a party or some
kind of event, but...
Anyway, it's the first time
I'm going to get paid for dancing,
so I'm looking forward to it.
I'm leaving.
Do your best.
Akira...
What are you going
to do today?
After lunch, maybe I'll
go to the library.
The library...?
Isn't... Naoko
coming today?
I don't think so...
We didn't plan anything.
I see... you didn't
plan anything...
So I guess she's not
coming today then.
If you did, she would
come, wouldn't she?
You didn't make any
plans for today?
No, I didn't.
This is my first
time in Aoyama.
But having an office in
Aoyama is chic, isn't it?
I wonder what I.C. stands
for in I.C. Promotion?
I.C. ...
I know what it is!
Inter... national...
National?
City!
That might be it!
Maybe it's a major
production company.
It might be!
It should be around here.
This is it, isn't it?
Maybe it's a little
further in.
No, it's not.
I found it.
Here it is.
Here?
I know what I.C. stands for...
Right there...
Ishii Chuji...?
Are you the part-timers?
I'm Ishii Chuji,
the president.
I hope you're not going
to say you won't do it.
Can we?
Please don't say that,
I'm asking you as
your manager.
I'm asking you, too.
Thanks for waiting.
Shall we get going?
Where are we going?
To the amusement park.
They're called "Eyebrow Cats",
and they're
quite popular with the kids.
Here's a picture you can use
for reference for the make-up.
Something like this...
The rest you can do
whatever you want.
Don't forget the eyebrows.
It's an important point...
After all, it's "Eyebrow cats".
What kind of event is it?
There's a stage outside
that door over there...
To put it simply, it's amusement
park children's show.
You see them often, don't you?
You go on for 15 minutes
each time at 12, 1 and 2.
So you get paid 8000 yen for
45 minutes of actual work.
It's really popular with
students, but if you
hire them all separately,
some don't show up, so
it's good that there
are four of you.
Here's the video.
The dance moves are on
the video, so just take
a look, and practice a
little before you go on.
Let's just look at the video...
I can't do this!
I can't do it either.
Wait a minute!
I know how you feel, but...
For one thing, Moe...!
Yes?
You're the one who found
this job, aren't you?
That's right. Why didn't
you check into it first?
But I thought it
would be good.
It was for four people, and
I thought it would be the
chance you needed
to form a unit.
I'm not dancing in a unit.
And besides, doing something
like this wouldn't work.
Hitomi's the one
who suggested it.
Because I want us
to form a unit.
Dancing forms
friendships.
I thought we could go on
to Dance Beat from here.
It's impossible with
this group...
If I'm going to do it,
I'll look for other
people to form a unit.
Me, too.
How can you say it's
impossible when we
haven't even done
anything yet?
You don't know until
you do something.
What's going to happen
with that kind of dance?
Even for children, it's
pretty low level.
We'll change the
dance moves...
Let's come up with our
own dance moves.
Mr. Ishii...?
Do you mind if we arrange
the dance moves ourselves?
Sure... As long as the
children like it, you
can change it as much
as you want.
You heard him...
What are you going
to do, Yuka?
How many minutes
do we have?
If you subtract the time to get
ready, we have thirty minutes left.
Junko...?
Help me.
From the top...
How about this?
That's cool!
What about this?
Moe! Your steps
are all wrong.
Do it like this...
It's time to get ready.
Standby...
Let's have fun, and dance.
Hello, everybody!
Where's your spirit?
Once more!
Hello!
Well done!
You'll be seeing some fun
friends here on stage.
Let's all dance
together.
Here we go!
Those were the "Eyebrow cats".
Give them a hand, everyone!
Thank you, "Eyebrow cats".
It went pretty well, didn't it?
You made the wrong turn, Moe.
We need to practice.
That was wonderful!
The children loved it!
Just what you'd expect
from dancers.
I'm counting on you guys
for the next performance.
Take a break for an hour.
Here you go!
On the house!
It's warm.
Cheers!
After finishing the three
stage performances,
thanks to the generosity
of the president, Hitomi
enjoyed a day at the
amusement park.
Hey! Keep moving!
I'm sorry...
I'm going. I'm sorry.
Naoko?
It's you!
Wait! What's wrong?
Don't tell Sano.
Goodbye.
Naoko!
What was Naoko doing
here anyway?
Here's your fee.
I even added a 1000 yen bonus.
If you don't mind, please
come and do it again.
Thank you for your
hard work today.
Thank you!
Shall we go?
Here you go...
Thank you!
It's the first time she
got paid to dance.
While she savored the
happiness, she was
bothered about seeing Naoko
alone at the amusement park.