Tryingg too Hard to Find Happiness'
Episode 59
They're sitting in front of Mr. Katsumata's
apartment, but there are no lights on
These two have decided to wait until Mr. Katsumata
comes home
What are you going to do when he comes home?
Are you going to grill him?
I'll start by grilling him.
Hitomi saw you in Atami. What's going on?
But he might pretend that he's innocent
We'll deal with that when the time comes
But I didn't expect this
Expect what?
For you to go this far.
I thought you'd say, "Don't butt into a
stranger's love affair"
Keiko's not a stranger
After I left home, she lived in my room for 10 years.
I can't just let it go
He came home
Is she the one?
That's her
So she's the Atami woman.
What are we going to do?
Should we barge in?
I didn't expect him to be with the woman
If Keiko finds out about this, the shock will be
too much for her
Let's at least tell Dad
You're going to Tsukishima?!
It's a matter of great importance to Keiko
We can't just let it go!
While they headed to Tsukishima...
Good evening!
Keiko! it's unusual for you to be here at this hour
I'm on my way home from the hospital.
Where's Hitomi?
Hitomi went over to Momoko's place
To help her move in, and they
were going to have dinner after that
Did you come to talk to Hitomi?
Not really.
I want to show you something.
What is it?
Is it a handkerchief?
When one of my patients heard I'm getting married,
she embroidered this for me: "Happy Wedding"
Even the patients love you, don't they?
That's right... I have something to
show you, too. It's good!
What is it?
It's this "For big sister Keiko"
What is that?
This is also a "happy wedding" card.
Yuria and Shota made it for you
The children are also happy that you're getting married.
Aren't you going on a date today?
He's so busy we hardly get to see each other
I see...But I'm so glad that everyone's so happy
about your marriage.
I heard the teachers at the orphanage were really
happy for you too.
When I went to the staff room, they gave me a
big round of applause
Mr. Kubota even cried.
Is that right?
You made your best effort.
You worked hard, and became a nurse.
You worked hard at your job, so
you were able to make this connection.
You need to treasure the fate that brought you
two together.
I will. No matter what.
I'm home!
Hitomi
Keiko!
Momoko's with you?
This is perfect
I didn't say you could come in!
This is no time for us to be fighting
What is it?
Will the two of you sit down?
I heard from Hitomi.
That she saw Mr. Katsumata in Atami.
Hitomi! You mean you even told Momoko?
That's because neither of you would believe me.
So I thought we should see if it was true
Since the two you didn't want to do it, I thought
we should do it
Did you talk to Mr. Katsumata?
I was going to, but when we went to his apartment,
he wasn't home yet.
While we were waiting, he came back with a woman.
The same woman that Hitomi saw in Atami
So I came here to tell you that.
It's none of your business.
How can you say that?
We were only thinking of you.
Why do you want to throw a wet blanket on my happiness?
That's not what we're doing.
Since we know, we can't just ignore it
Someone like you wouldn't understand
Even having a mother and father
who are there and feeding you,
you left home for your own selfish reasons
Keiko!
You, too, Dad...
The only reason you raised me is because she
left home, and you were lonely...
You only took me in so I could take her place, didn't you?
You're wrong about that, Keiko
I thought that ever since I was little!
Ever since I heard that you had a daughter
named Momoko who left home after you had a big fight
and probably wouldn't come back - that's what I thought.
You're badly mistaken.
Dad really hates me
He wouldn't be lonely even if he couldn't see me anymore
If he was lonely, it's because he couldn't
see Hitomi anymore
Mom!
All he ever did was yell at me, but he couldn't
spend enough time with you.
When I brought you here for the first time,
he carried you with him and really took care of you.
That has nothing to do with what we're talking about.
Sure it does.
You raised Keiko with the same feeling you felt when
you were holding Hitomi didn't you?
And now Keiko is the one with a crisis
What business is it of yours anyway?
You're making a big thing out of something that
wouldn't have been a problem if she didn't
know about it, if you hadn't told her!
How can you say that?
What's all this this? We can hear you from outside.
Are you fighting again?
Keiko..?
It's something very important to Keiko.
Momoko!
When Hitomi went to a hotel in Atami for a part-time
job, she saw Mr. Katsumata dressed in a cotton kimono
walking arm-in-arm with some other woman.
Is that true, Hitomi?
She's mistaken.
No, I'm not!
Do something, Katsu.
Go over to that Katsumata's place and..
Hitomi and already went
And what happened?
He came home, arm-in-arm with that woman Hitomi
saw in Atami.
After we saw that, we came here to tell you about it
You mean that Katsumata's at his place
with another woman?
That's right.
I'm going to beat him up!
Where are you going?
To Katsumata's place, of course!
Do you know where he lives?
Well, no...
Idiot!
In any case, don't stick your nose in it.
I'm going to marry Mr. Katsumata
Is that OK?
He's betraying you!
It's OK.
Even if it's true
Why?
You won't understand!
You don't know how much I wanted to be married,
and build a warm family life.
Keiko
So you have no right to butt into my life!
I do know how much you want a warm family
I saw how happy the teachers at the orphanage
were for you.
Even more than me
But..
How do you expect to build a happy family with
someone who betrays you like that?
You have to confront him and confirm
Don't be afraid to see how he feels about you
Katsu
What are you doing down here?
What's wrong?
Are you crying, Keiko?
It's okay... This is grown-up talk.
Keiko's fine, don't worry
Head back upstairs
I'm sorry we made so much noise
What are you going to do, Keiko?
I'll go over to his place now.
But that woman's there
Then it's perfect...
The three of us can talk it over
Momoko
Thank you for worrying about me
I'm sorry I said such rude things to you.
And Dad...
I'm sorry about what I said earlier
What was that?
Saying that I was just a replacement for Momoko.
That's how I felt when I was little
But when I was in middle school, I realized that
you were really looking out for me
I'm going now
Shall we go with her? I'm worried.
You're right.
Are you both going?
I'm going, too. Dad, take this.
Then I'm going too.
What am I supposed to do?
The iron is on.
Do you want me to turn it off?
No... finish the ironing
That's Akira's shirt.
Hey Katsu! Wait a minute!
Right here.
Keiko
I'm afraid..
What am I going to do if it's true?
I'm afraid!