Trying too Hard to Find Happiness
Episode 60
I'll go over to his place now
But that woman is over there
Then it's perfect
The three of us can talk it over
Hitomi and the others were worried, so they went to
Mr. Katsumata's apartment with Keiko
Right here
Keiko?
Can you go by yourself?
Stay calm
If anything happens, I'll help you
Just go ahead
We'll wait for you here
Someone's coming
Hide!
It was him after all
She kissed him!
See you
Keiko! Go and talk to him.
I'm afraid!
Keiko!
I can't!
Okay! I'll go
Hey! Katsumata!
Give it up
We have all the proof we need
I'll make tea
No... Don't bother
Just tell us what's going on
Sit down
Mr. Katsumata
Please tell Keiko the truth
Who is that woman?
Until last year, she was my girlfriend
We were together for three years
It was right before I met Keiko.
You mean you got back together again?
Yes
When?
You mean you were together before you
came to Tsukishima with Keiko?
No.. It was right after that
She called, and asked if we could go out to eat
Why didn't you turn her down?
You could have told her you had a fiancee!
That's true...I could have
But you couldn't forget her, right?
Yes
You felt that way, and you were seeing Keiko?
I thought I could forget about her
Keiko wasn't seeing you just so you could forget
about your ex-girlfriend!
Keiko dreamed of having a happy family
She wanted to have that happy family with you!
Keiko...
Why are YOU crying?
What were you planning to do?
Were you going to sneak behind my back,
and go on seeing her?
I knew I had to tell you, but..
You're going to choose her.
Mr. Katsumata
You promised me, didn't you?
That you would build a family filled with
warmth together with Keiko
Was that all a lie?
At the time it was true
I was moved by Keiko's strong desire to get
married as soon as possible and have a warm family life
What a strange thing to say
What do you mean, it was true at the time?
That was yesterday, but today's different?
That's not how it goes
To Keiko, building a family life IS her life
Family is everything to her
To Keiko, that is life itself
That's who Keiko is.
You mean you didn't even understand that
and you were dating Keiko...?
I'm sorry
When Hitomi told us that she saw you with another
woman, Keiko and I didn't believe it.
We trusted you
and you betrayed that feeling.
Keiko put her life on the line, and trusted you
And you betrayed that feeling!
I'm sorry
I'm really sorry
Mr. Katsumata...?
Raise your head
Goodbye.
Thank you, everybody
It was kind of strange, wasn't it?
Having the family around when you're breaking up
That's true
It made me reflect a bit
That maybe I was trying too hard to find happiness
And when it started to fall apart, I tried to
pretend that it wasn't happening.
It's the same for me
I have a ways to go.
Shall we go home?
What are you going to do, Mom?
I'll grab a cab and go home
Pull your spirits up, Keiko
Just forget a guy like that.
I will
Good night
What are you going to do, Keiko?
I think I'll walk a little before I go home
and shift my mood
Good idea. Do that
Dad... I hate to think of what's ahead for me
Will I ever find someone who will accept me?
Of course! Tokyo's a really big place
That's true
Thank you.
Good night.
Keiko...?
You're really adorable
Keiko
I'll see her home
I think she needs me at a time like this
I'll see you home
There's no need
You don't have to be shy
Shall we go?
July, 2007
Summer came to Tsukishima
What's wrong, Katsu?
You've been putting that same shirt on
and taking it off so many times.
I don't have much energy
I wonder if it's the summer doldrums
Maybe I should eat some unagi (boiled eel)
What are you saying?
Summer's only just begun!
A western clothing store is always one
season ahead
It's especially hot today
I'll bring more summer things from upstairs.
I have a feeling summer things will sell today
Keep an eye on the store for me
Yes indeed,
it's really summer today
Did something fall?
Katsu!
Katsu!.. Are you OK?
It's a crisis for the Ippongi family
But Hitomi doesn't know it yet