CHAPJEr?
Let'£ Be Friends
Episode 41
3jiP IJrteJ
o.. to la es ?
(JiUJ
onito la es)?
hen o! e acec^vith
a len V.
When you're faced with
challenge
It has th
katsu" (to win)
That's awesome*
See hOW worried everyo. %
s about you, Hitomi.
you'll have to do
your best.
c*w whether
I win roe
I don't like pr tending
fo be friends
Who do you think
you are!
After practicing like crazy
for about two weeks, Hitomi
and the others auditioned
for the prombtion video.
Congratulations,
Mika and Emi!
It 'S the
announcement of
the judges decision
C? C J! ' i
•••A lot nfiriD-
the final winner today..
"fThe winner is fromHIPZ!
ntry number nine... Kyoko,
Chisato and Kuriko!
Congrgtu.ajons.
s ti'lSf'fJfea?
Kyoko,~Chisato and Kuriko
They're shaking hands
tthK
ow
The rour groups on this
stage are the winners
of the audition Jfor
background danc ft
Give them all another
roun
plause
It's too l
isn't it?
These things happen.
hall we go, and have cake
to cheer us up
i know a good bakery nearby
Why, KEN? I'd Vt agree
with your decisi n
Tell mfe why you
didn't ptk me?
Your dancing is closed
Wfiaf (£q
you mean
by that?
I don't understand
It means your heart
is closed
You need to open up your
heart a little more
-and enjoy your dancing
Together With
everyone here
Keep working
at it
Junk©,,?
Let's go after KEN,
and ask him, t *
We already know
it "fsfecStose
Asnoi ej9Afc
Hrtomi...?
For Hitomi, this was
first real audition that
she tried for since
she came to Tokyo
She tried * riesQn
her own way,^nd
she thought
worked hara at it
It made h Y r "Slize a am
howhars:i le o.k o
dan Ingtold tV
Katsutaro had told Hitomi
to call when the results
were in, but Hito_adnl
been able to do that
I'm home!
mi.ome Grandpa.
I'm orr J didn't dill
^tuall , failed
fl
lever mind tmt...
flurry, and help me
Ve inner..
You and I are making
inner to ay
i IIUOJI
Wished
eating yet?
Not yet.
That's perfect then
Someone gave me "tatami iwa hi
(baby sardines dried, and
entwined to form a single
mat-like sheet), so
I brought some for
the children
It's full of calcium
Thank you.
You're always
thinking of us
Say, 'thank you
all of you
Thank you, Umel
You don have to
thank me .
We're n ghbors,
aren't we?
Ume...?
I failed today s
audition
After all the support
you gave me
I'm really sorry
That's too bad
You win ome
you lose some
ike the Weather... Sometimes it
rains a tl s "metimes it shines
That's true:
Sorry 4b bothery
Thank you so muc
Thank you.
s!U) ||li6 9M lie s
tatami iwashf ?
Wh^.t?
Will you do somethin out
that dad of mine
Did he do something a ain?
Mari t, fe
He has a date with
day after tomorrow
He went to the department s.ore,
shirt to wear on thetfate
Th 1 makes me mad...
i fell shirts here!
That's what I fol him, nd o
you knowjrfhat he to d me. 9
That the "*hir. s yo ell
here aren't hatfjreat
That Yujiro
Yuzo... S failed the
a0£,rf'°n foday.
You did...?
After you gave us he
atsuobushi
I'm sorry I wasn't
bod enough.
Forget bout t
It's just suob
It's just written with the
character "katsu" (to win),
so just eating it, doesn't
Vn an you'll win.
So will you tell
him for me %
Tell him not to waste
his money like that
All right I'll tell him
See you ail later
No matter whafhappens...
We have to eat
No matter what happens.
we always have a nice
h *1 meal here at K ™e
L Ys make this
When 1 got home
I was so happy.
Because didn't call,
they all knew that
I failed the audition, so
they just acted normal
when I came home.
making dinner,
a was
r
hildren re doing
their homework. Ume and
Yuzo just stopped by.
matter what happens.
we can
and no matter what happens
life will go on like this
everyday and it made me
realize that I can do my
best as long as \ have a place
like this to come home to
it cheered me up a little
I'm sure it's the same
for the children, too
You have to make a place
like that for them
Do your best.
Don't lose... don't give
And believ
most
That's what's
important!
If you don't know the
words, don't sing!
You're in better spirits
than
1 thought.
Of course I am!
I can't be depressed just because
I failed an audition
And here hought
I would comfort you.
Tanaka Moe
Hello? Moe?
I'm at BROCKS right now
Yuka's in trouble
Yuka? What kind
of trouble?
It's terrible'
She's in terrible trou 1e
Rea«y ferr,b/ef
Don't try to snatch
Yuka away
Who are you? It's none
of your business!
Where are you going?
Hey, Yuka!
Are you okay?
It's terrible! Come over
here right away
Wait* Moe?
Hello! Vloe!
What's wrong?
Yuka's in trouble
I don't know what's
going on. but
someone s trying to
take Yuka away
she's at a club
She wants me to
come right away
At a club9
I'll come with yob
You'll need help,
wont you?
Wait a minutej
She's okay
Not you again!
It's none of your
business!
This is the place!
What is it?
I'm nervous!
I've never been to a
P<dC6 ilK6 iIS
You don't have anything to
worry about with the way
you're dressed...! Hurry!
Let's go!
Hurry!
Moe!
Hitomi*
u?ht help
Hello.
It'll be a great help
So what's going on?
Look
over there>
Shall we go?
y any chance
Is'Yuka drunk?
opelessly drunk...
he s been drinking
y herself all night
So who are those guys?
they're fighting
over Yuka
The two guys in the red
and orange tried to
pick Yuka up first
After that when Yuka was
dancing by herself the
in the green and
two guys
light blue jackets
tried to Pick her
In others words, the red
and the orange are
warm colors, aren't they?
That's right
They're warm.
The light blue and green
are cold colors
That's Tight
They're c Id colors
So it's a battle between warm
colors and cold colors
So what about it?
Tin just trying to get it
straight in my head
3 'keep telling you over
and over again!
We came up to
She said she didn't want
you two and she was
going with us'
D°nt make up stories'
That's right.
i)< dois
Yuzo!
Isn't that why
you came?
Stop it'
Hav n't you heard of
Yuzofrom Tsukiji?
Of course they never
heard of him
Will he be okay?