CHAPTER 15
Tearstained Towel Blanket
Episode 90
You're Mr Imazata,
aren't you?
What is this about?
I'm a member of
Shota's family.
My grandfather and I are raising
Shota in Tsukishima.
Mr. Imazata...
Why did you call off
your marriage?
e... Shota's mother
she's lost confidence, and
she can't raise Shota
She won't meet
Shota anymore.
Shota's really sad
It's none of your
business.
Yes, it is
I'm Shota's family.
Wait a minute. What are
you all doing here?
You're scaring my
customers away
I'm sorry
I'm sorry, but there's
a reason for this..
Come back here!
Hey, Imazata.
There he goes
I'm sorry
Shosuke
This is the guy
He's the one!
So you're the one..
Abandoning the woman you
love, and Shota?
I'll teach you
Wait a minute!
Don't run away
What's with all of
you anyway?
Mr Imazata... I'm not here
to complain to you
I have a favor
to ask you.
Shota was really happy when
you played with him on the
rooftop of the
department store.
And when I saw how happy he was,
it made me realize that this was
what would make Shota
truly happy.
After all, he would be
living with his real
mother, and their was
someone who would
become his father, too
That's what would make
Shota really happy
Please <<in- a ou
how Shota feels.
That's what I wanted, too
It seemed like Shota and
I would get along,
and I really intended for
the three of us to live
together, but
my mom
Your mom has nothing
to do with this!
Yes, she does!
She raised me all
by herself
I'm her only son
Eventually, I'm going to
take over the restaurant.
I'm all she has
Mr. Imazata... It's the
same with Shota and
Shota's mother, too
You're a full-grown man
should take responsibility
s man, ...
My responsibility as a son
is more important than
my responsibility
as a man.
I can't take on the burden
of Mikie's life, too
I n it* ath tic, but
this really made me
realize that
That does it!
Calm down!
Just calm down
So what about Mikie?
I'm sorry, I'm just
not strong enough
This is Mikie ddf ^s and
cell phone number..
If you have something to
say, then say it to
her directly
It has nothing to do
with me anymore
He ran away
You coward!
What's wrong with him?
But what should I do?
\ think ylikie'jjS
ffluc.-: oo A/e<ik.
Ndt ^yihg t ^ confidence J
to raise Shota unless
has someone she
can re1y on
can re1y on.
I can understand
Have you felt
that, too, Mom?
Right after the divorce,
when you were just
about Shota's age ..
I think I was relying on
your dad somewhere
deep in my heart.
I was at a loss right
after the divorce
I was busy at
work, too
When I came home in the
middle of the night,
middle of the night
and saw you sleeping,
there were times
I would cry.
But you raised me,
didn't you?
That's because
you needed me
Every once in a while,
when I'd come home
after work, you'd come
running to the door to
e come pne Jiome
h le m ate, you'd tell
about school and
what you saw on television
Every time that happened,
it made me realize that
I had to try harder.
You're the one who gave me
the courage to raise you.
Welcome home, Shota
What's wrong?
om on? ee e n more
She's busy right now,
so if you wait...
That's a lie!
Mom doesn't love me.
Hitomi! What's all
that racket?
Have you heard
of flying?
I'm going to do that now.
Wait! I don't
understand.
Mikie... Are you home?
This is Hitomi from
Tsukishima..
Tsukishima
I live together with
Shota in Tsukishima
Mikie!
If you're home, please
open the door
Mikie!
Are you home?
Mikie
I know I did a terrible
thing to Shota, but
it can't helped.
I can't live without
someone to rely on.
What are you going
to do now?
I'm going back to work
It's the only thing I
know how to do
He should forget
someone like me.
Shota would be much, much
happier if he stayed
in Tsukishima rather
than live with me
You're wrong! Shota
has always
Never mind!
I abandoned him once before.
Shota doesn't need
a mother like me.
All he needs is you and
his Tsukishima dad.
What is this?
It's Shota's treasure
Grandpa asked Shota what
he remembered about you
He said that he remembered
you lying in bed with him,
and telling him stories
"Bremen Town Musicians"
Shota remembers that
clearly even now
He sounded so happy When
he told us about that.
Isn't that the towel blanket you
covered him with back then?
He's treasured that ever
since he came to live
in Tsukishima.
in Tsukishima
I lost it once when I hung
out the bedding, and
he cried and looked for it
He was crying so hard that
I climbed on the roof
to look for it
To Shota, this was
his mother
Something he should
never lose
I love Shota, too.
So do my grandpa and
the other children
That's why we don't
want him to leave.
It would be unbearably
lonely when he's gone
But
it's you that he needs.
You can givr him what
my grandpa and I can't
Please live with Shota,
and raise him.
Shota