CHAPTER 9
"I'm Getting Married"
Episode 52
Keiko? Go! Go! Go!
Well done, everybody.
Come as fast as you can!
Right this way.
AII right. We're coming over now.
It makes you nervous, doesn't it?
After what happened with Momoko...
Mako... ?
What about your shop?
Don't worry... I left it in Hiroshi's hand.
No, you didn't.
What are you doing here?
Because want to see it for myself.
Just get back to the shop.
I'll tell you what happened later.
Keiko...
Don't any of you interfere...
Once it's over, I'll be sure to tell you the result.
Are you ready?
Grandpa... ?
Keiko's here.
Keiko?
Why are you all dressed up today?
Dad... ?
Do you have a minute?
Sure...
What is it?
This is Katsumata Seiji.
This is my father.
Pleased to meet you. My name is Katsumata.
Mr. Katsumata...
That's right... Mr. Katsumata.
Won't you come in?
Come on in.
If it's all right with you...
Please... come in.
I see... so you met when you were in the hospital,
and that's how you got to be friends.
That's right.
She really took good care of me.
I don't mean to be rude, but what do you do for
a living, Mr. Katsumata?
I'm a web designer.
Baby designer?
It's work that's related to the Internet...
He designs home pages for companies.
That's...
...really impressive, isn't it?
Not at all.
Actually...
Mr. Katsumata and I are dating.
I thought so...
That's what I thought...
You knew?
Of course I did.
I've been through a similar experience before as a father.
Which means...
What does it mean, Mr. Katsumata?
It's...
Shortly...
We're... dating with the intent to get married.
Actually, I already proposed to Keiko last week, and
she agreed to marry me.
So I came here today to ask you...
Please... allow me to marry Keiko.
Wait! Wait a minute! Raise your head.
Mr. Katsumata... please raise your head.
I see...
Mr. Katsumata...
If we make a mess out of this now, we'll regret
it later, so...
Just let me tell you this...
Keiko isn't my daughter...
She is my daughter, but she's not really my daughter.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Keiko already told me.
She did?
Keiko's had a hard life...
She's really suffered a lot since she was a child.
Until she came to live here, she was at an orphanage...
That's why until she came here, she didn't know
much about the warmth of a family.
So my late wife and I became her real parents, and
raised Keiko.
So to Keiko, marriage is having a family...
It means having the warmth of a family.
Mr. Katsumata... can you give Keiko the warmth
of a family?
Yes, l can. Together with Keiko, I'll do my best so
she'll have the warmth of a family.
Right now, I work for a company, but in the
future, I'm hoping to start my own company.
Once I do that, I can work at home, so Keiko
and I can spend as much time as possible together.
I'm a good cook, so when Keiko's busy, I can cook.
And we'll have about five children.
That many?
Don't worry... I love children.
Mr. Katsumata...
Have you...
...ever carried a portable shrine?
I'm sorry... I've never carried one before.
You haven't? Why not?
Grandpa!
I'm sorry to ask you such a strange question...
Mr. Katsumata...
I'm really grateful.
I'm going to trust you, Mr. Katsumata.
Keiko... Thank you.
For bringing the man who means so much to you, over to meet me.
You really didn't have to worry about me.
Don't say that.
I wanted you to approve of the man I'm going to marry.
Thank you.
Mr. Katsumata... please...
... take good care of Keiko.
I beg of you,.. please take good care of her.
Dad!
I'll do my best.
I'm counting on you.
Please take good care of her.
I really will do my best.
Private party
Cheers!
Congratulations!
Go ahead, and eat Mr. Katsumata.
Is it okay to eat this?
Of course it is.
From what I heard, it went fairly smoothly, didn't it?
What was unexpected was that he didn't let the
issue of carrying the portable shrine bother him.
Grandpa really looked happy that you came over to get
his approval...
I was happy, too.
I wanted to make sure Dad approved of him.
Aren't you glad that he approved?
So when is the wedding?
We haven't decided yet...
He's so busy that he doesn't know when he can take off.
Keiko... you mustn't rush a man.
If you rush him, he might run away.
Don't say strange things like that! You won't
run away, will you?
Of course, I won't!
Cheers!
Are you drinking, Dad?
Do you want some, too?
Keiko s getting married.
Are you happy?
I don't know.
Are you lonely?
Neither.
They must have gone home already.
It seems so unfair.
I've known her for 15 years, and she's going to marry
a man she's only known for six months.
I can understand how you feel.
It's painful being a man, isn't it?
It's painful for you, too, isn't it, Dad?
It sure is painful.
Let's drink tonight...
Two men in pain...
Shall we drink then?
Cheers!
I'm home!
Grandpa?
Grandpa!
Are you in the store, Grandpa?
What are you doing?
Grandpa...
Look at her...
She was so little.
And now she's saying, "I'm getting married."
It's strange, isn't it?
It's so strange that it makes me cry.
As she looked at Katsutaro, Hitomi remembered what
they say about the father of the bride.
To be continued