CHAPTER 20
The Next Step
Episode 117
Written by
SUZUKI Satoshi
Music by
YAMASHITA Kosuke
After the tenement's [block's] annual
flower viewing party, the
party continued over
at Rose's bar...
I think it's great
You're a really great
dancer, and you still
want to try something new
That might be over-exaggerating
a bit, but I wanted to do
something that's entirely
different from dancing.
What do you do, Keiko?
I'm a nurse
That must keep you
busy, doesn't it?
But it's worthwhile
I feel like I'm being
of use to others
What about Keiko?
Are you kidding7
She's like my
little sister
But I think she's looking
for a more family type
of love... The love of an
older brother maybe
Excuse me for
a minute
What are you doing, Makoto?
What do you mean?
AY... I'll set it up. so
you can approach her
It's OK, never mind.
I want it to be
more natural.
Let him do it
Excuse me, Ray
Would you come and listen
to what my brother
has to say?
Sure
Thank you
Be careful
Let me introduce you..
This is my older brother
Thank you for coming
to cheer us on
You remembered?
Of course
I loved the way
you danced
Take a seat here.
I ove over there
Have a seat.
Thank you.
Stay
I'll just be in
the way
Stay here,
please!
Hey Keiko! Are you
drinking7
Ken and I were
just talking
About New York, and
things like that.
Do you go to the
clubs often?
Once in a while.
I've never gone to one.
Take me the next
time you go
Let's go together,
Hitomi
Sure
What's wrong?
You seem depressed.
No, I'm not.
Then I'll go with
you too
Can you dance?
Of course I can!
I love to dance
I think he can
Since he's always
moving his body
Really?
See? The legendary
dancer says I can
I can dance. See?
Where's Hitomi?
I think she went into
the studio
She must be depressed,
after all
About Yuka and Junko
being scouted
I don't know how
to comfort her
Hitomi?
Mom!
I heard..
What are you going
to do from now?
Are you going to try again for
next year's Dance Beat?
I don't know
Then what are you
going to do?
You quit school
already
I'm still thinking
about it
Don't you want to
dance anymore7
Why?
Because you were the
only one left behind
I don't feel
like that
Yuka and Junko
are special
Then why are you
so depressed7
I'm not depressed
fes, you are.
No, I'm not!
I thought I gave it
all I had, and
I thought I had made up
the difference between
myself and Yuka and Junko ..
But I guess the people
watching could obviously
see the difference
I love dancing, but.
I was wondering
what's ahead
Is it going to end as
something that I just
enjoy doing for my own
self-satisfaction?
You don't want to do it just for
your own self-satisfaction?
I don't know.
I just don't know
Then why don't you
quit dancing altogether?
It's better than being
half-hearted and just
dragging it out,
isn't it?
You're so cold, Mom!
I'm just giving
you advice
I thought if you chased
the idea of dancing out
of your head, you'll come
up with something
It's not that simple.
Are you awake?
Does it still hurt?
It's just as I thought
You tiori'i remember
On the way home from
Rose's place, you
fell down the stairs.
I did?
I'll come back to check on
you in a little while.
Keiko..?
You really seemed to be
enjoying yourself.
At R te s laeg..
With Ken..
We're dating.
What?
Keiko! What are
you doing?
What's with
you guys?
Let go of me
Keiko! Keiko!
What's wrong with you?
Are you OK?
Sorry about that
It's nothing. I had a
bad dream
That hurts
What is this?
Don't you remember?
You fell down at Rose's
place last night, and
hit your forehead, so
Keiko and Hitomi had
rljlj j) J i
They did?
Is that what Momoko's la?1
She says Slic"liars
things, doesn't she
It really got to me
But I don't think yo'^fe d
to fif^h into anything.
Just your b Ing he iff this
ousema estnean
t Children 3 |>y\
What do you think
about Keiko?
She's cheerful and knows
what she wants
And she's lite, too
Are you thinking
about dating her?
No, J'jp no
What's this all
about then?
At first glance, she's
cute. Then when you get
to know her, she's pretty
har and adorable
Hey Hitomi
Keiko's not that
Icfora 1e,js lie.
$io, I think s ^ f j
adorabie
Dorft i\/erre((hl.
What?
Girls are like that.
The/'sa* tbiirgs
the^ng ~fft trie 71
I do ay !hing§
onlrtlean.
o i^jne th 1
ilh i «!• j
tAte.c ire'
Keiko! How unusual
Keiko! What are
you doing here?
ftameto at before
I go to work.
Hello Ken
Hello, thanks for
the other day
What, are you dating?
Miso mackerel
^ST&stHicio
Were you OK
after that?
I guess so.
But it was fun,
wasn't it?
|.et£40 it again
Maybe it's better that
she wasn't scouted.
t<= pretty harsh, snt ^
In that kind of business
Thereare e Dwillju^t
shovfe y Vi o
Hitomi's not suited
to a world like that
She always wants to get
along with others.
gijt Ren* a nice c, .
ii ^ isejie s
Jjot liarallf
You write his name in
English, don't you?
That's right
Dancers all transliterate
their names & 1n(j thfe
Roman alphabet..
a literate
e would
toefcATSUlhim.
Jjto tfOiO Y 3 £
Winfc is Ume...
UME.
Doesn't this look
11 e/orm
r own nit?
Hello
How strange
I need to talk
to you, Dad
What is it?
About Hitomi
What bout Hitomi?
I'd like to 4J0 nwitfi
yo , nd alTabodfit
Shall we talk in the
oth Y rp Tn .fi
We have coffee
Soun is ood.
Wait a minute
You two have time on
yourii Ti s, on'! o 9
You want to satch
the store, don't you?
1s I ight
All right. 'WHI
wat Ti le^toTe^
We're/ittiily
arenj
jIQ jp j jii^
They get along when it comes
to Hitomi, don't they?
Work part-time?
At your company?
I thought you sh
try different thing .
"■How l)Out next
for £ week?
It's OK with me, but do
you think I can do it?
I wouldn't ask you to do
anything that difficult
But you'll have to work
ov im everyday
Vlalftheiime, you might
be working until the
middle of the night
I can't do that
I have to cook dinner
Don't worry, I already
got Dad's permission
You talked to Grandpa7
He thought /might be
• • • i j JY) >»I • 1
a c. Sng^jpf pace
He and the kids can take
care of the cooking
e^ficP
It would help me out
Wj M A) io
OK ..I'll give
it a try
Be sure you dress properly.
Do I have to?
Of course you do
The first term has started
for the children
Good morning, me
Yuria?.. You look
so grown up now
She's a middle school
student now.
Akira's in his
We're leaving now
Akira, your lunch!
We're leaving
Good morning.
I'm going to be working
in an office starting today.
Take care of dinner for
me, OK Grandpa?
All i ht.
I'm leaving
She doesn't look like
the same girl, does she?
She looks so smart
Hitomi's life as an office worker
for week is about to begin