HAPJER 17
Dance is Life"
Episode 102
Written by.
SUZUKI Satoshi
JVIusic By.
YAMASHITA KosuKe
MIT
Engli TV Su title By
filPpbN GO NETWORK
i "torn Trow.
What are you going to do9
I'm going to convince^them
h, it's you
When Hito 1 came to convince
Junko and Yuka, Junto's
older brother, Keii"hi
Was there
I talked to Dad after "St
f wanted to hear how he really
elt ab&Qt the r ^taura T
And it se i o
wa?1 you iota e t
ut oesrT he Iflestgon
sua I <a e over
jjho -wftbvj'i
This j5 Moe,
our Yiager
I'll bet you
manager b
a lousy danced,
di<3n' ou?
That'sino way to
talk o erf
1j)jlJ tombli^p
j m nio'ilh jii'iil
« you* «i •
h b le's business
Ste.i er .
Hitomi,.
What did Dad say
about • ou?
He sai- ince
f-ijillly, ilr) •iO'ilJj))
JiiD b Lllte
la< sLu/oiA
30ly i XJtpx
het erHashimoto Gyoza,
well-known restaurant
in Utsunomiya stays
open or not
iiitti Uiyxk
JjliLJ b
I don't know if I'm going
to take jt over, not,
lit I feel I should go over, and
elp out a few da week.
p J'va HJXjili liU* /J/
mind right here, and now
Just quit dancing, and take
over the restaurant.
YoQJI put Mom's mind
ease ^ "bu o
li
You aid our
ittJii^} Yj!Q»
Isn't your amil living a
"STcltim i Aoo?
You don' have^HTfeto
ia llil'iljlj, «b Jltf-
Yuka h s othitfg
bJivrtm %
You realty are pushy,
aren t you?
You re/big, and
obstrusive
How rude1
to/a iii^l?
y*m fil&m & vii am
jiUte uijia jjia Hy 7 jj
jiu h jjy'ilij\yj
& Jii Ja^ Oil J
Hitomi's havirf a
hard time, o
She s helping her' randpa
aise foster c II ren
while she tries th keep
p with her a ing
toi^fel) J)J
I ftofr 0111*13
J J 3 J Jjfl'i
have time to be
anc<ng,£Jo ou^
Just give if , so
f ou an Ut,all Mr
efforts ntb h \
uu idve u u
j ■ v- J i«iu/«l oi 1 /
We don't Oboe
j • i rta jloajfc
a|i issocitu
I understand t you're
both wrig hrotigh
I really do know how
hard s or ou
But.
That has nothing to do
with giving up Pricing.
I told/you^ve ouldn'
So it, didn't *
*et me say on**
last thing..
This is hat KEf^
told me..
Ydudon'tj stdan
*hestage
You e not shoeing your
te Unique,-but the
way you live rite
Don t run away from life,
even though you have
doubts and suffer
hardships..
If you still want to dance
after all that, then
you're sure to dance
at your very best
Let's c Yne a . o
face with li
K
e..
Confront it
and keep dancing
And I'm siite we'll be
even better dancfers
Let's dance together again
Don't let herfool
you, Junko
She might have said
some cool things,
but if you fall for this,
you'll just make our
parents unhappy
The restaurant Will cloSfe
down, and yrifll make
Dad and try
And besides, \fthat do you
mean y i e anyway
"Whatyo r I on islike
perform n 100I play!
Ybucan t drq"Y7h^"app!iuse
when yo er:o r'ed in yo^ir
*fthdergar e. a , o you re
a juiiltilJ,
even afW ou're rown-up
if that's not it, then
you're just chasing
after the spo light
You just want to Yne out
on television, don* you?
You'll never m^ke t*
You'll just end ifcdancirtg,
living^ ovefiy ith
)( Mit
ilm 11 ike hat.
It n e
H^iUiUJiiViU
Re .aving your oli^ation
tojqjfjattiib^j J
over he res auran s illion
uurnvjis
Jlj fc ^Wrtt J'ii
You're already 2 ^ears old!
There's no way o can
i ake your d but now*
The idols these days are
making their debut
when the ' e 1
It's about timeyou stop
ch iing a ffream ha
i
can never come ruel
nolillilj 'OUUIte
ilfoj) iiH yjJSOD
iJillli J)Ai J/^]jj)t/VJJ
J j ViJill "bl/J JlU,
ft only jia ens 0430 nt
\(4[n^Aj -JiU-ijM
1\linet - ine oint/iine
villi aw it
fulfill heir dreams!
It s afwaste of time to
jput our tf tt into
sbme hifig that will
n&ver show results!
Youishould all
uit dancing1
e ic 1! on4 cafe what
jy u
but ont talk about my
fnends like that
What do you mean
by frifencte9
You just happened to4 ein
the same Aass toge er,
and spent a year hanging
out with each other.
ou don t know
amng of friendship
We re a team.. We share
he^ove of dancing,
and dance together
JDon't insult my friends
and don t say bad
things about dancing
ou may not nde> stand his,
t)ut to ftie, da cing is
something w derful
It took me 20 years to
find it, and it s
someihinq e; llv
Th Vi
h-jT
recoil
jjliLJ \0 J}?
Areyo n o et "fern
bv/n \
if I lose, I'll take over
he restaurant.
I'll quit da ting, and take
over the restaurant
Junko. ?
That's okay with
you, isn't it9
\ II iqtit.i
II tell Daffthat.
^eiichi
Thanks1
Don't forget what
you just said*
Junko *
What are you going
to cfo, YuVa9 [
rfl do il
Hitomi*
Thank you
Okay
Let s do our bes\l
o ur est1
You're going to
work part-time9
You're going to work, so
you can helpps out?
You're tjongfo rk, so
you can help us out9
It won t be much
It'll be a great
help, but..
I'mjiome1
fnrpome1
Are you here again7
Dear
Yuka s going to give us
from her part-timfe jo
Yuka's going us money
from her part-time job.
You dontiia do that
It s uncalled tor.
Just do whatever you want
Dad!
Don't run away,
and >isten..
This is what i want
to fftow
We've never been a family,
but I want us to be a
family from now on
sfor waitm
I talk TTtcrthem.
ow did it go?
/My mom was , HI
as usual, my dad
treated i^ike
a si cinger
But I'm going to
<Jo wh f I wilt.
Shall we go?
-Waiting i a er^ Turn ry
jmi'jji
io... I have1 o
li!0 JLJLH
—Shall well e 1 yf>z 1
*Z6o IcJek!
How many did
J»J*1. u
I^Jidnt |at any, didi?
She ad dbout three
Wednesday
e e's our Str
hat do you call this7
tathappe ?d...
t ertainiy^ooks that
ay, doesn't it9
It holds some rremorjes
Won't it do?
No.. It's fine.
I'll accept this
ROSE MARY's Sntry just
made it in time...
Ypu're s&fe1
Safe!
I'm glad that you" e
oing to e enterin
ij} Uiiy WlTJ
ha as oing
r m Moe, and
as worried.
KEN aye me some vice
He lid9
Oon't run a a rom ife...
if ou still want to dance
Iter having doubts, n
s- fering hardships, you'll
a ce at your very e 1.
s that right7
3 it 'ltt
Isn't t E SHOES9
ou both... . tiled
my brother1
ou an t come in here.,.
We don t allow
■outsiders i ^rc
Lisle 2 here .f
What do you think
you're doing9
G i 3head
^hat e you
i.ere ior?
We're going to enter the
Tokyo preliminaries...
Why come all ihe way
to Jokyi for that9
You can enter the
Osaka preliminaries.
It's no fun unless m j
enemies are right
therein ro tofm .
ou and EN!
£on't run away, and show
at you can do