CHAPTER 16
Goodbye Shota
Episode 91
Written by
SUZUKI Satoshi
Music by
YAMASHITA Kosuke
Takaya
Wakaya
lb; j
r
J (f-
UJ 'JX )
English Subtitle By
NIPPON G0LDEN NETWORK
It's you that he needs.
You can give him what
my grandpa and I can't
Please live with Shota,
and raise him
Shota.
Child care counseling center
Mikie?
HlriTit. I'll be
waiting.
Ms Saito is coming
over here, and she
said she'll raise
Shota herself
Really?
But what happened?
It's rather sudden
She said it was
because of Hitomi
Hitomi?
I'm really sorry for
sounding so unreliable
Let's talk this over
carefully
This way.
I'm very sorry.
Let's talk.
We called Katsutaro.
Follow me
This way
When I saw Shota clinging
to the towel blanket
and crying, I just
couldn't sit still.
Her fiance gave me her
address, so I went
over there without
telling Grandpa.
I Understand the
circumstances...
I'm really sorry
I apologize, too
She's young, so sometimes
she does things
without thinking
I understand that she was
thinking of Shota...
But of you made just one
mistake, Mikie may have
collapsed emotionally.
If that had happened, it's
possible that it would
haVe affected Shota's
whole life
The most important thing
is the child's future.
No matter what happens,
please don't forget that.
I understand. I'm sorry
I'm sorry
But I guess since Shota's mother
says she wants to take him in,
and raise him, it's OK.
It might take a while,
but please watch over
Shota the way you
always have until now.
Thank you
I really feel bad about
what I did to Shota,
and the trouble I caused
everyone here, but
nuiii iiuvy uii, iiH yuiny iu
take a whole new outlook
and do my best
to raise him.
We're glad that you
feel that way.
We'll do all we
can to help you
Thank you.
But because of everything
that's been happening
before you live together
with Shota, I think you
need the time to sort
your own feelings out.
When a mother has doubts and
is troubled about raising her
child, there maybe
problems with the
mother's emotional state too.
You may be able to gain
more confidence by
thinking back to your
own childhood, and
your relationship
with your parents
^llim^ jo nljffo'ji
so e alk frankly
3 it JU a iillu-
n e o uild a ood
rela to p i ota
for the future.
I'll do that
I'd like to ask your advice
about something
What is it?
Hitomi's been a great help with
what happened this time
Will I be able to meet with her
again, and talk to her?
We'll talk to Hitomi
about it, and if
she agrees, we'll probably
pres "nl when you meet
All right, please ask her.
Shota.
Your mom's no longer
that busy anymore
So she said she can
meet with you again.
Really?
oingto tud "tiard
so she can be a good
mothe to you, so she wants
you to wait until then
Shota. Can you wait
a little longer?
I can
You really are a good
boy, aren't you?
I see. I'm glad
But I hope his mother won't
come out and say that
she doesn't want to
take him again
I think it'll be
OK this time
kV/lbth& ridlSbn were able
4ojje thfeirVeelings
across to each other
is o or probably felt
guilty about not doing
nlhin fdrTiim as a mother
for so many years
She thought Shota hated
her, and she couldn't say
with confidence
she'll be a good mother.
Shota's something
like that too...
He thought the reason his
mother wouldn't see him
was because she
didn't love him.
It's hard being parent
and child, isn't it?
Even if you care about each
other, you just can't get
your feelings across
to each other.
What's so funny?
It sounded like a parent
and child that we knew
Are you talking about
me and Momoko?
Bullseye
007-911 m
It's November
November 9, 2007
This is the 96th Ippongi
Katsutaro sticky, sticky
natto race
Ready, Go!
Make it stickier.
As you'd expect from
third-year middle school
student, and Akira..
He's quick
Faster and faster
It's getting stickier...
There goes grader
Oka Yuria..
Third grader Saito Shota's
catching up...
What's wrong, 20 year-old
Ippongi Hitomi?
Yours isn't getting
any stickier
Work harder!
Wonderfu!! That's
magnificent
In order to restore her
bond with Shota, Mikie
met with Ms. Inoue and
underwent counseling
to help prepare
psychologically
Shota has calmed down, and
patiently waited for the
time when he'd see
his mother again
Then one day, Hitomi got a
call from Ms. Inoue and
went to meet with Mikie.
We asked you to come here today
at Mikie's request, Hitomi
Thank you for coming
Were you busy?
Not at all.
How is Shota doing?
He's fine
Once he understood your
feelings, he felt secure.
He's not fighting with
his sister anymore
Really?
What about you?
Ms. Inoue and the others
have been listening
to me talk
We meet like this and talk
about her childhood
h s 15 that, I'm beginning
to understand myself better
I realize why I've always
been afraid to be alone
and why I'm always
relying on others.
When I was little
my parents divorced
They didn't get along even
before that, but
When I was in the fourth
grade, my father left
Why?
According to my mother,
he was disgusted with
Tokyo, and went back
to his family home
I was abandoned
my father
My mother found a boyfriend
right after the divorce,
and hardly ever came home
I was so lonely...
But I put Shota through the
same thing, didn't I?
I'm such a fool
Doing what I hated the
most to my own son
What is your mother
doing now?
She passed away
when I was 8
What about your father?
Her father is still alive, and
in his hometown
We've been recommending that
she go to see him once.
At a time like this, it's good
to have the support
of a family member.
It's OK.
He's probably forgotten
about me by now
Mikie
What's wrong?
This song...
It's Miyako Harumi's "Anko
Tsubaki wa Koi no Hanai"
When I was little, my father
used to sing it all the time
Mikie.
You really want to see
your father, don't you?
When something happens, I think
family is important
If you know where he is,
don't you think you
should see your father?
Thank you, but I'm not
going to see him
Let's not talk about
this anymore