CHAPTER 18
Season of Love
Episode 103
Written by
SUZUKI Satoshi
Music by
YAMASHITA Kosuke
English Subtitle By
NIPPON GOLDEN NETWORK
What are you
here for?
We're going to enter the
Tokyo preliminaries...
Why come all the way
to Tokyo for that?
You can enter the
Osaka preliminaries.
It's no fun unless my
enemies are right
there in front of me,
you and Ken.
Don't run away, and show
what you can do
RAY... What's
this all about?
It's nothing.
Are you okay?
I'm okay
Don't worry.
I'm fine.
But rumors sure
spread fast
They've ...already
heard about last
Do you know something?
What did they
What rumor do you mean?
It's nothing
There's a rumor
1GMVI0BD... What is it?
The information hasn't
been confirmed,
so it would be bad
if rumors spread.
Don't worry...
We won't tell
If you don't tell us,
e i lima ine
strange things, riu
spread it round...
Don't do that!
Then just tell us
a little
Just a little bit...
leas§*
@Do
Just a little bit...
OK...just a bit; un n
436ft1 {II afiyone
The rumor is that Ken and
Ray are going to dance at
the next Dance Beat
Tokyo preliminaries
And they're going to
dance as CHEAPASS.
Ken and Ray dancing
as CHEAPASS?
CHEAPASS is the legendary
dance unit that consisted
of Ken, Ray, and Eiji
Although they broke up
after Eiji died in a
motorcycle accident four
years ago, they are still
what dancers aspire
to become
That's awesome!
Is it true?
I OcJtyou.. -J<don t
know or ur
themdirectl 7
I did ask Ray
I told" Y^iaUheR iS
rumor going around
M J
She didn't deny it, but
she didn't confirm it either
So I think Eiji's sister
found out about it
But isn't the deadline past for
the Tokyo preliminaries?
That's right
-Aasn tihedea lin. or
/the Yiltrie today
For previous s cf
Dance Beat, the 'I
accept their entries right
up to the event..
t il acdexciteme . o
Jthe O^nt, on* t
That's why I don't want
you to tell anyone
about it because it's
still uncertain yet
Do you understand?
Yes
That's awesome,
isn' it?
That would be so awesome...
The return of CHEAPASS.
Don't you want to see those
two dance together?
1-b]
But they'll be ful
fefnv if th-
going to enter
Okay... let's put all of
our effort into it
and do our best
Today is Akira's high
school entrance exam
Mom... please watch over
me, and help me to do well
on today's exam.
Please
Please...
I'll be going now
If you get too nervous,
then write the character
for "people" in the palm of
your hand, and drink it
You'll be fine. You studied
really hard for this
Do you have Shota's
postcard with you?
Here it is..
LkUJjr , 1 • 1
charm n too.
You'll V in
Do you any ice? Ice!
We're busy
right now
We need to bring down the
fever
I wanted to make
an ice pillow
we don't have
enough ice
Wait a minute
Stay away from him!
Akira's going to take
his exam now
We don't win take any
chance of him
catching what you have!
I'll get your ice
so go back inside
Go on!
I'm going
Go back
JDoy urb ira1
Sio thtfl TfII
spread your germs!
What are g 0u
?
hn ml J]
I'm not the one
who caught a cold
Thank you, Hitomi...
You, too, Ume
Iit sjiardforan^ll-Ts wife
in the house for times
like this, isn't it?
That's true.
When are you going
to find a wife?
He's too old.
Idiot! She's talking
about you.
Me?
That's right... How old
are you now?
I'll be 34 this year
You're 34..
j_L< JLOb
a .i. anfl tlied vftien
he was 33
11 Ryoma!
iJ£ 3]jiyj^
oil., i men who are 34.
still single
a new lifestyle.
^St'e thfe trenfi.
Uever rniftl about
Jif lifestyle..
Hurry and become a
full-fledged adult
You're so unreliable
at work, too
When I'm not at work, you're
the acting president.
So take control of the
business properly
I know!
Do you7
Just be quiet and
go back to sleep.
My fever went up again
It's hot
That's because you're
getting wound up
You're the one who
got me wound up
Yuzo's the acting
president from today?
Until Yujiro gets
over his cold.
It might be just
a little test
for Yujiro
A test?
Once in a while lie, when he
eats here, he says it's
about time he left
the business in Yuzo's
hands. ^o hfe c Yi
take it easy
Wanting to take it as
i lit just be ^a figure
of speech. but he must
want Yuzo to become
a full-fledged businessman too.
o he can survive
here in Tsukiji
Don't complain about every
single thing that I do
It's because you're taking
impossible orders like this
Who's going to deliver
all this anyway?
On top of that, it's
all small orders
I took the orders
on the phone
Since I'm the acting
president now.
At least you could
stagger the delivery times.
All of them are for delivery
by 2 o'clock
Just get a bike delivery
service to do it
You'll lose more
money than you make
All right! I'll just help
with the delivery!
That will satisfy
you, won't it?
I'll have a miso mackerel
medium bowl
Are yoy going to eat?
Of course I am!
I need to keep up my
strength if I'm going
to help with the
deliveries
Hurry and pile
everything up
Get back to work
I'm doing the
best I can.
Aren't you just spinning
your wheels? From what
little I heard.
They don't take me
seriously at all
They thi Kldorif
know my job.
Because it's th r t
Will you come with me to
Mako's place tonight?
I need a diversion.
eall ike o
iiHul!TL31
Welcome
Ken
I'll have a miso mackerel
medium bowl large serving
with extra pickled
vegetables
fla e ea p er ITre
Your miso mackerel
really is delicious
Thank you very much.
He came back again.
Thank you for waiting.
Miso mackerel medium bowl
large serving with extra
pickled vegetables
Thank you
Thank you for your
help the other day
Thanks to you, the three
of us are entering
Dance Beat
You are?
I'm glad.
And here's something
I want to ask you...
About Dance Beat?
If you have time later,
I'd like to talk to you
I have something to do
this afternoon..
I should have known..
I'm sorry
n SyVour rtieal
You live in Tsukishima,
dont you?
I haven't had a lot
of monja
Do you know of
a good place?
I do. It's where
I always go
I can be there about
8PM if that's
OK with you
Sure! Sure it's OK.
It's fine with me
I'll meet you at
the station then
Thanks
Can I borrow this?
Go right ahead
,, Hi"
She told me she was busy
There's a convenience
store lo "/< so
I'll meet you
around there
The pickled vegetables
• III
I'm glad you did well
on your exam, Akira
I think I did, but the
results aren't out yet
But I'm relieved for now
You can sleep all you
want starting today.
Good fortune comes to those
who sleep and wait!
You're right. I'll sleep
for about 10 hours
After we eat, will you go
over to Yujiro's place
for a little bit? He's
having a hard time.
Okay
After that, I'm going over
to Makoto's place
ilium Are you going to have
monja with someone?
Something to do
with dancing.
With Yuka and the others?
His name is Ken..
Is he your boyfriend?
Mo, he's not!
Your boyfriend?
I said, he's not!
He's not!
How long?
He's not
Ishida Yujiro/Yuzo
For one thing
I'll have another
bowl, Ume
You made ir*
m»stakesf< Tia
Whar^hrge ":tsia,<e
u ookinfi o* ble
cttiers, r«u ft
t; o had lorjsn aF"\ind
3 b JaBv^?
4he rders... The Silly ho
-was .. UD^D^'J $5)
ma ing the bonito flakes
had to /atch li rore.
Itv/as d Ta
Irfthe encMhte e itfferies
wera-J 1e, IsTJ 01
inconvenienced
our customers
h Ts actually ?;t
o leini
What I'm saying is
"You make one mistake, and
you cause a lot of trouble
all over the place.
Do you understand?
That's why you can't
find yourself a wife.
That's something
to worry bout
Don't you have
a girlfriend?
It's nothing to
brag about
Are you seeing
someone, Yujiro?
ibyi^jr/iio?
That's a good idea
If someone like Hitomi
would marry Yuzo
I couldn't ask
for more
I feel bad for Hitomi,
but it would be
good for Yuzo
Not you, too, Ume?
Won't you consider?
Please let us call you
"mistress" in the future
No. I don't think so!
It's impossible
You heard what
everyone said.
She's embarrassed
I'm not embarrassed because
it'll never happen.
If you'll excuse me, I have
something to do.
Take care, Yujiro
I'll come with you
Where are you going?
We s tildt 1k about
olir "tirfc
m not iims.teti 1
Come back here!
Grab hold of him!
My honey..
Hitomi was excited that
she was going to meet
Ken whom she admired