CHAPTER 11
Summer Without Grandpa
Episode 61
July, 2007
It's summertime.
tfi in*
lYl lULa
!
[Vl 100 il«J(l
h s summ n
Stop saying it's
hot already!
It makes it even hotter!
fBefjuiet! YouremTcin
iteveh ore oppressive
Oppressive!
JtssoTi 1... You all
ook e$s*
Shos Ice'
It's on the se!
aitamin e.
Jt'£ o per son
What's wrong, Katsu?
You've been putting that
same shirt on and taking
off so many times.
I don't seem to have
much energy..
I wonder if it's the
summer doldrums.
What are you saying?
Summer is just
getting started!
Ws es. ^ially
hot today
I'll bring down more summer
things from upstairs
l have a feeling summer
things will sell today
Keep an eye on the
store for me
I ' idb Ulieii IIUl
It's really summer
Something fell down...
Katsu!
Katsu... Are you OK?
What's wrong, Ume?
It's Katsu!
He fell down
Are you okay, Katsu?
What hurts! T hurts'
Don't move me!
It hurts!
Grandpa fell down
the stairs?
Makoto went with him
in an ambulance
me and I will stay here,
so go straight to the
hospital, Hitomi.
The hospital is
Did he hit his head?
I don't know anything.
You'd better go!
We'll be fine
I'm sorry!
Call Momoko
That's right
Shall I call Keiko?
Could you?
What about the children?
Akira's at tutorial
school and
Shota and Yuria are..
at the pool
I'll go to Tsukishima
Take care of the
shop, Yuzo
Okay
I hope he didn't land
the wrong way
s i i e ic on e
Katsutaro broke
his left knee
They're examining him now
to see if there isn't
anything else wrong.
Hitomi?
This is Ippongi's
ce11 phone...
I'm unable to come to
the phonee right now...
Please leave a message at
the sound of the tone
Haven't you been able
to reach Momoko yet?
No matter how many times
I call, it goes
to her voicemail
What's she doing at
a time like this?
It can't be helped
She's working
At that time,
Momoko was.
Here's a cold
drink for you.
Thank you.
Your daughter
just called.
What did she want**
She said she left a message
on your voicemail
I set-...
haven't listened
to my messages
Ms Ippongi...
How did it go?
You could At get the
dep Wmeril store..
They have enough with
the brands they're
handling n "to, so-they
don't have any room
for our line of cosmetics.
e lly tried afdto
hem o ree
I really thought
we'd get it.
It's really tough here
in Tokyo, isn't it?
Isn't there a place
for us here?
Ms. Ippongi!
ii JlJl
c nt of e sto e%
e pf^jetteci we could
get our start in
That's right.
I feel really bad about
leaving everything to
you because I have to go
back and forth between
here and the main office
But after two months, and
mbers ttke this.
I'm sorry
The manager's so
sarcastic
He doesn't do
anything.
It can't be helped
t'stlo our best
our best
I I I j I
This number here..
Isn't the k an
extra zero 7
I wonder what happened?
He uses those stairs
everyday, so how
could he fall down?
Will Dad be okay?
He'll be fine. The doctor
is with him now
£ a broken bone,
fietffce okay.
One of the members of
the judo team had a
broken bone, and it
healed in a month.
Maybe it was the
summer doldrums.
Ume said that he wasn't
feeling well since
opening the store
i won e f he slipped
The fatigue just caught
up with him..
He's been working extra
hard for the past six
months since Setsuko died
What are we going to do if
something happens to Grandpa?
Don't say that.
Ms. Ippongi?
Thank you for waiting.
We've finished
all the tests
How is he?
Fortunately there weren't
any abnormalities in the
brain waves and
He'll o have surgery
for the broken bone,
it's not rig urg°n . arid
ilam/jaiy jlJiUivL.
An! of ourse,t ere won't
befaTfyJitt Teffects
So he can continue
as before
Once his bone has healed,
^ tJi) jjkl^Uiiilj
hat T£t>eeri omg.
But he'1 ed a little bi
of p sic hera
Thank you.
Everyone... Please
keep the noise down.
We have to prepare his
hospital room, so
please wait here.
Aren't you glad?
After taking Katsutaro's physical
condition into consideration,
they decided to wait a few days
to do the surgery.
Including the physical
therapy, he'll be in
the hospital for
about a month.
3?0i
J^ jJJ ilII*}
I'll) 30 jh'Jtt iV
i^you ok-.jy?
o^s it r
o... he gave me
pain killers.
33 JJJ
JUrfi Mi yjj/iml
Th T^ecause^ou knew
iiovy io Ml «lov)i>,
iJ&aj ^ imj^xfrj ato?
Yu 5 ontactU them, and
e I ai in
j/af ai yji/Xud^
e I
¥yen'|jb fen able
e e ind a out Momoko
VII. Ull !••» JJU" IdVC
® isito ...
Ati Vi )!< iy-iijjM ircni i.h-a -iiill
■ttf J Jj ^Mj •i^iiU
m n
ia ou call him?
Tniaht we should
til il^JJ)IiiUVA
b^ Umjiiiftil if
tetter o, and let
jjIilj m
I dke hexhildren
O 10
kr o get
IC
turn* ji^lUnly
\fia/ yj n jhij u misih
Thanks
I'll treat you
He's going to
treat them.
What a time for
this to happen.
When he fell down the
stairs, the first
iLlJ) ULUjili J J
w ^Ihechildren.
What's going to happen
o i ilcJrehif
so ething a penecftome?
a "Bli t hile
ih. ere arrumng^ne
Hitomi.. Wha e ou go ng
b 'lo Vihlte hi) JOiW?
on*| want yoB to over o
it, and get Ick again.
Talk it over with
Mr Wakayama and
the child care counseling
center, and figure out
some way to handle it
We could have someone
else take them in...
Actually, as soon as we
got the phone call,
we talked it over
juuu* iJlujUi
in the hospital for an
extended period of time,
e ou tiave to the 1<
other alternatives,
but since it's only
going to
e I a dec sio
te e alkit e
with the two of you.
We have to think what's
best for the children.
Even if it is just for a
short period of time
a change in the home environment
isn't very good for them
I can do it.
Iltoe in
The children have been
helping out a lot lately
rj) ijjjinnj jj) jiji
Hitomi!
I'm counting on
you, too
uc n how us
t • • o! •
a ly counting
IxUJ Oim-
x your e t first
Hitomi..
Please don't forget...
rep o - in't s
on't overflfo t>and if
!Jrquestion, o a
jjna u /by b1
OilJ ffijl^
I omecr ing o o .
JjjV) try • 3 ^ia/1
I do my toes i ho
iijki) toiti/J L
Thank you
Is Katsu okay?
He II be aid ft*
jn about a m hth
I'm sorry to worry you
I'm so glad.
hat's wr Tig, Hit Tni?
I'm startsrt o
Worried
V/ill I be able to !e
ing Ipr a month?
e ve ^ a ting for yo
How s a s
ow*s
Other than his knee, he's
ite* 1 • • J J iuall\
He is?
I'm glad
Really lucky
Everything will be OK
You have all of us here.
While Katsu
u b
get her through this
Okay
The Ippongi family's summer
without Katsutaro is
about to begin