CHAPTER 16
Goodbye Shota
Episode 96
Written by
SUZUKI Satoshi
Music by
YAMASHITA Kosuke
English Subtitle By
NIPPON GOLDEN NETWORK
Akira...you're not
in the picture.
love closer together
5ALB
Shota will be leaving
tomorrow
R.cidy .
Mine... lght
lutit... -i-iee
TWO....
T o
Thank you for waiting...
Wow! Look at that!
[ worked hard.
Shall we eat?
Fried lirimf)..-?
a e.
ou' e ding there on
thfefc parent you?
An ill ra high speed £o 1
it goed ties per hour
Fifty miles per hour!
t o.s that fast9
It must be hard when
the boat rocks.
It hardly rocks at all.
ingS in tfie
a>er, and it rises
above the water and runs.
You e om j to ride on
something awesome..
Yo i st be looking
forward to it
Are you done here, Hitomi?
I'm done
Shota... Do you want to
take a bath with me?
I ll bring myt.ofhp .
Shota... what do you want
^avAaii j j/^i/
A baseball player.
to laiijkLjj
hen is it possible
or you, too9
Of course
It's about 0.0001
percent, but
with a stomach
like this. 9
on't Ik &ut
tomacfi'
That's a scientific
water pi lol..
Long ago, we had water
pistols like this..
/JJ jaa i
Like this9
rank it1
I win'
\ lost1
Are you still playing?
ho a won three
in a .row...
The champion'
YotT-re bod'
one more time
That's enough. We have to
get up early tomorrow
One more time
This isn't the last time
Let's play again someday
That's right! The three
of you are siblings ..
Even if you leave this
house, you can play
together anytime.
Shall we go to bed
now, Shota?
Good night
Let me introduce you.
These are my children .
Shota... Yuria.
And Akira
Hello.
Let's be friends
Mom died
"TAay.. You still
have your dad
Can you go to bed
by yourself?
Shota
Shota.
Let's go home together
Your dad's home is
where you belong
The towel blanket is gone
It's something
Shota treasured.
I 3 JJiUj
Shota
t II be dr b tfeiifig...
jyo ca . Se p ith
i LJ'-llih
Thank you.
You helped me
look for it
Listen to him...
j tm 13
lium
Shall we go then?
Good night
Thank you
Good morning
Shota... Take care.
Come and visit during
the festival, OK?
I'll come
Shota.. I enjoyed
1ia you here
Your side dishes
are delicious
I'ti ad
I'm glad
We'll see him off.
We'll say goodbye here
See you cam
«>
Thank you for everything.
I'll never forget what
you've done for us.
You don't owe us anything.
We really enjoyed
living with Shota
Thank you, Hitomi..
If it weren't for you,
I don't think I would
have had the courage
to try it again
Take care, Shota
Get along with your
mom and grandpa
Make lots of friends.
I'll write to you
Write back, OK?
We'll be going now
Thank you
I'll do my best
Shota!
See you again
See you!
Shall we go?
Shota
Take care!
^Doyoufbe^V