CHAPTER 7
"Let's Be Friends"
Episode 38
They're holding
an audition...
The song will be the
d-Darts' debut song.
You can do it solo
or as a group.
The deciding battle
will be next Friday.
The place will be
Club BROCKS.
This is KEN, one of my
old dance partners.
He'll be in charge of
choreographing the
promotion video.
I'm looking forward to
seeing what you can do.
That's where you come in.
You're really tall.
You'll make a great weapon
when it comes to impact.
I'm a weapon?
Hitomi is full of enthusiasm
about the audition for
background dancers that
KEN will be judging.
Just as Hitomi is enthusiastic
about the audition, the
children are just as
enthusiastic about
helping her out.
My next mission is...
After the meal, I have to
clear the table.
Thank you for the meal.
So, who's washing
the dishes?
You and I are washing
the dishes, but Shota
will be taking the
dishes to the sink.
Roger!
If you pile them so high, you
won't be able to carry them.
Sure, I can.
You don't have to carry
them all at one time.
I'm going to carry
them all at once.
Don't do it!
Look at that.
That's why I told you...
Why didn't you wake
me up, you idiot?
What is he doing so
early in the morning?
I know, but you could
have woken me up...
We live together!
All right. I'm on my way.
Let them wait.
Your storeroom blocks the
light, so I can't tell
what time it is!
Don't take it out on me.
What's wrong with Yujiro?
He overslept.
Yuzo got up, and went to
Tsukiji without waking
him up, so he's
all upset.
You should think
about your age...
Be quiet!
That's what you get for staying up
until three in the morning.
Especially when you have to
work early in the morning.
Why did he stay up so late?
It's Mari...
Remember she invite him to
go somewhere faraway on
Sunday two weeks from now?
That's why he was looking
through the guidebooks
to find a place where they can go.
Is that why he was up until
three in the morning?
It's only a day trip, and he
was looking at Hakata.
If we take the Shinkansen,
we can go there, and eat
ramen noodles, and come back within a day.
If you go there, you'll have to
come right back, won't you?
Give me back the paper.
I want to read the
sports section.
I'm looking at the
culture section.
There's a special on
middle-aged couples' day off.
I've had enough of this!
You'll tear the paper!
Hello!
Mari!
I have to meet a friend,
so I just stopped by
to have a quick word with you
about where we're going.
You mean on our date?
How about Kamakura?
I was thinking the
same thing.
Here... I was reading
this article just now.
I read the same article.
That's why I thought of
going to Kamakura.
What a coincidence.
Do you think it's fate?
That's all I wanted to say.
We'll discuss the
details later.
Sorry to intrude.
See you later.
Kamakura... ?
That takes the cake!
I'm speechless.
Fate... ?
Kamakura...
Here we come!
Kamakura... Kamakura...
How shall we go?
Something's not right.
You think so?
Shall we change this part?
That's not the problem.
We just seem to be
unbalanced somehow.
But you're the one who
I'd make a good weapon.
At this rate,we won't
even reach the finals.
Maybe it was a mistake
to pair up with you.
Please don't say that now.
That's kind of harsh.
Hey, Junko...
If we're off balance, then
how about if we include
one more person?
Her?
That's impossible.
Not after I slapped
her the other day.
That's right. And doesn't
Yuka plan to do it alone?
Is that right?
Can you seduce her?
I'm asking you if you have
the confidence to convince
her to join us.
Confidence... ?
It's ok with me if
it's ok with you.
Go ahead, and convince her.
You'd better apologize
to her properly, Junko.
"Self-preservation
at all cost..."?
Junko... Do you
have any savings?
I work part-time, so
I have a little bit.
Why?
The best way to a woman's
heart is food, isn't it?
Yuka!
About the audition...
Won't you join
me and Junko?
I'll pass...
I'm going to
dance alone.
Won't you think about it?
We already have some
of the steps...
Then show it to me.
That's not my style
of dancing...
In other words,
it won't work.
Then join us, and
make it work.
Besides, you and I don't
even get along, do we?
I don't want to end up
fighting with you like
the last time.
Can't you just
think about it?
This time, Junko said she's
willing to use a lot of
your ideas... Didn't you?
Can we just talk about it?
We can talk while eat.
It's Junko's treat!
We could have steak, shabu
shabu or sushi.
We could even have
pot stew...!
We could go to a high-class
Japanese-style restaurant.
What do you like
to eat, Yuka?
I knew it wouldn't work
from the beginning.
For one thing, Yuka's father
owns dozens of restaurants,
so she's probably eaten
steak, shabu shabu or
Italian until she's
tired of them.
That's true, but...
That would catch my
attention right away.
Then maybe beef bowl or
ramen noodles might work.
Maybe it'll be so unusual,
it'll grab her attention.
But we'll finish eating
in five minutes.
We won't be able to talk.
Hitomi... How about "that"?
You know... What we
had the other day.
Oh, "that"?
Yuka!
You're so persistent!
Don't bother me.
We don't have any lesson
tomorrow, do we?
So what about it?
Would you like to come to
Tsukishima and have "monja"?
"Monja"?
That's right... "Monja.”
I've heard of it.
You fry it on an
iron griddle.
You mean "okonomiyaki"?
No... it's different.
It's not quite as
well-done.
The feel of it in your
mouth is something
that's beyond comparison.
Isn't it?
I think I might like
to try it.
Maybe I'll go
with you.
So, you're going to bring Yuka
and the others to eat "monja"?
That's right.
That's why I made reservations
at Makoto and Hiroshi's place.
Yuka's a really rich girl
so that's why I thought
"monja" and a place like
this downtown area would
be something new to her.
I'm sure she'll love it.
In that case, after you
have "monja", why don't
you bring her over here?
So after you eat "monja",
you can take a walk
around, and work up an
appetite, then bring
her over here, and we can
have pot stew together.
I'm all for pot stew!
Me, too!
Really?
Then I'll have to shop at Tsukiji tomorrow...
Why do you put in "yosenabe"
pot stew anyway?
You should ask Yuzo
about that.
Knows a lot of cheap
and delicious places
to buy food.
You're right.
I'm all for that.
Me, too!
In that case, shall we invite
Yujiro and Ume, too?
I'm all for Yujiro
and Ume, too!
We'll do that then.
I've had enough already!
Act your age!
Is that Yuzo?
And Yujiro?
What's going on anyway?
What are they
fighting about?
All you talk about is
Kamakura... Kamakura
from morning until night.
Buying all these guidebooks.
What are you going to
do with all of them?
And who is this Gen Raicho?
It's Minamoto no Yoritomo!
Gen Raicho/Minamoto Yoritomo
He's the founder of the
Kamakura shogunate.
While we're on our date, that
topic might come up, so
I have to study up on it.
You're really having an
academic discussion here...
Talking about the Kamakura
shogunate and stuff like that.
Will you listen to this?
All my idiot dad can think
about, is his date with Mari
and he hardly does
any work anymore.
I was late just that
one morning, and
that was because you
didn't wake me up.
Why should I wake you up?
Ail you think about is your date.
What? Are you against
my dating Mari?
What do you mean "date"?
You're not a young kid.
My heart is as pure
as a young kid.
Have you looked at your
face lately? You look
like a pigeon that's been
shot with a peashooter.
Say that again!
That's enough, you two.
You're drawing a crowd.
You used to only talk about
our dried bonito flakes,
or about our customers...
Now all you talk about
from morning until night
is Kamakura... Kamakura!
I can't take it anymore.
Yuzo!
Yuzo...?
Did you hear that!
Lecturing his own
dad like that.
Shall I go, and
check on him?
Go after him.
Yujiro?
Aren't things going well
with your business?
No... we're doing fine.
But he was saying something
about your customers...
It's about the future...
Our customers are all
Japanese-style and
old traditional style, high
class restaurants, so he was
telling me to look at the
newer restaurants that
emphasize the taste of food.
I see... Yuzo's thinking
about the future in his
own way, isn't he?
Being the idiot
that he is...
Sorry about the commotion.
Good night.
I've only seen him as man whose
mind is always on work,
so it throws me off.
Seeing him getting so caught up
in something else like this.
It's a good thing...
Age doesn't matter when it
comes to falling in love.
Why can't you just
indulge him?
It's not that I'm against it.
I almost forgot... Will you
help me go shopping in
Tsukiji tomorrow?
We're thinking of having
a pot stew party at home.
I'm going to invite some
friends from dance school.
Dance school?
I don't have time for that.
It's probably some of those
good-looking guys who
can dance like this...
I don't want to help.
I see! That's ok then.
They're all girls...
Three of them.
What did you
just say?
Gather around. Come on.
Gather around.
One...
...two ...three.
We have just enough to have
a "gokon" (co-ed party).
What are you saying?
Let's do it.
No! We're not having
a "gokon" party.
The next day, Yuka and the
others came to Tsukishima.
Will Hitomi's strategy to
convince Yuka work?
To be continued...