CHAPTER 19
Showdown
Episode 112
Written by
SUZUKI Satoshi
Music by
YAMASHITA Kosuke
Powerful rivals appeared
one after another
It made Hitomi realize
a11 over again the
high level of talent needed
to get to Dance Beat
Entry number 16.
That was BLUE SHOES!
Give them a hand!
Kazu! Why did you change
the dance steps?
The audience
was shocked
At this rate, we're
going to lose
I'm sorry, ail of you
When I thought about what
my brother would say if
he saw me dancing so
filled with pain, I just
couldn't go on
I started thinking I want
to enjoy dancing more
Kazu...?
I'm so sorry
Kazu!
I I was the best
Isn't that enough?
iplojbiu a ,
with I
It
a e
Ple ^fe^StCh e
Did you lose
confidence?
To each his own...
4 jiisjiiiafit not be ia good
&camn,er \ if y ^u try
Sushi and tempura, there's
way to compare them.
Siyo drfftcnow
e ~ i V
It's almost time for you
to go on, so cheer up.
U tie...! Dad's here
I ran all the way...
I wanted to make it
here in time
I feel like Mike Hashire Merusu
(Japanese drama)
You look like a "hashire
surume" {running squid)
Here's your video
Shota
Shota sent you a message
in a video letter
to cheer you on
I want to see it!
He looks the same
Hitomi! How are you?
I'm fine!
I'll always treasure the
ball you gave me
One of my friends on the
baseball team asked me
to give it to him, but
I didn't give it to him.
Don't give it away
o is e ay for you
to show your stuff, so
I want you to
do your best
Here's my cheer
for you.
Rah! Rah! Ht-to-mi'
Guts!
I'll give axhee
Join me, everybody
Rah! Rah! Hi-to-mi!
Rah! Rah! Hitomi!
Rah! Rah! Yuka!
Rah! Rah! Junko!
Rah! Rah! ffto
Rah! Rah! Moe-chan.
Rah! Rah! Moe-chan!
We have Ihe s r
ROSE MARY
You'll be on next
Please stand by
Here's entry 13
8 DD HAM!
Give them a hand!
ROSE MARY will soon
be on stage
Kenichiro. ?
I came.
Why did you come?
So I can teirSac! $ntl
Mom the result.
You remember your promise
to take over the family
business if you lose
don't you?
Don't worry
I remember
Good luck!
Be sure
to win this!
]JiJ
He ere
Yuka's indebted
to all of you
He kept saying he 0
$iever watch you dance
Yuka.J?
Ar tft cufcjIacP
Here's entry 23.
MARSHMALLOW STICK!
Give them a hand!
You're next
What's wrong. MOBO?
What is it?
Pain... pain... pain..
Go far away!
Thank you
Good luck!
He's so* lite
Do you remember the
day we first met?
It was in front
of the school
Moe suddenly came up to me,
and tried to pick me up
She tried to
pick you up?
That's right
I remembered seeing you at
the test for Ray's class
And I got up the courage
to approach you.
If you hadn't come up to
me that time, we wouldn't
be here, would we?
I owe it to you that I made
friends with Yuka and Junko
Encounters are strange,
aren't they?
It smells nice
Show everybody ROSE MARY
t\ vm; r u tier 3
MARSHMALLOW STICK!
Give them a hand!
They're on next
They're next
Hi-to-mi! Hi-to-mi!
You're calling for
an encore, Dad!
They haven't even
started yet.
Our next entry is the
winner from last
year's Summer Contest
at BLOCKS
Their favorite food
is 'monja'
Here's entry number 24!
ROSE MARY
Hitomi!
Entry number 24!
ROSE MARY
Give them a hand!