CHAPTER 8
"Two kinds of Love"
Episode 47
Don't tell Sano...
Goodbye!
Naoko!
Good night.
Good night...
I'm glad your part-time
job went weII.
It went better than
I expected...
At the beginning, I didn't
know what would happen.
What did Akira do today?
Akira?
He said he was going
to the library...
So I guess that's
where he went.
When I asked him if Naoko
was coming over today,
he said they didn't make
any plans, so he didn't
think she was coming.
But I have a feeling that
deep down, he was hoping
that she'd come over.
I have something to
tell you, but...
What is it?
Just come with me.
Today's part-time job was at
the Arakawa Amusement Park...
Arakawa Amusement Park...
I ran into Naoko there.
She was there by herself.
She was at the amusement
park all by herself?
No, she wasn't playing.
She was just sitting on a bench
in front of the Ferris wheel.
When I went up to her, she
tried to run away.
Then she told me not to tell
Akira, and she ran off.
I wonder what that was all about.
Hitomi...
Come with me.
Akira was...
...abandoned by
his parent.
Abandoned?
His mother died soon
after giving birth
to Akira, so...
Akira was raised by his father.
What did his father
do for a living?
He ran a small
printing company.
But business started
going downhill until
finally, there was nothing he could do.
Akira said that one day
his father took him to
the amusement park in Arakawa
when he was five years old.
After Akira had ridden all
the rides in the park,
his father said he was going
to the bathroom, and he sat
him down at the bench in
front of the Ferris wheel.
He told him not to
move from there,
so he waited and waited for
his father to come back.
Because he was told not to
leave the bench, he kept
the promise, and just sat
there, waiting for him.
When the park closed, an
employee came, and asked
him his name, then a
policeman came...
What about his father?
He didn't come back.
He's still missing until this day.
He doesn't know if he's
dead or alive...
Akira told that story
to Naoko, didn't he?
But, in her own way, Naoko
was trying to understand
how Akira felt back then,
by sitting on the same
bench that he sat on.
Hitomi felt like she had
touched on a part of
Akira's feelings that were
shut deep down in his heart.
Good morning, Shimada...
Sano... good morning.
I didn't expect Dazai Osamu
to be so interesting.
I went to the library to
study yesterday, but
I ended up reading his book
all the time I was there.
You did?
What did you do
yesterday?
Nothing much... I just
lay around all day.
You did?
He seems dispirited,
doesn't he?
His fever went down, didn't it?
But he says he doesn't have
much of an appetite.
Did something happen with Mari?
I'm sure of it. it was after
he came back from
"Matsuri" that he drank all night.
That's right.
Hello!
Mari?
Dai! Here's some pickled
vegetables... I bought
too much, so I thought I'd
share some with you.
Thank you for always
thinking of us.
Yuzo! Come to my place
to drink once in a while...
You haven't come
by at all lately.
I was holding back
since my dad was there.
You don't have to
worry about that.
Come with Katsu
sometime, Hitomi.
I will.
Goodbye.
Thank you!
That was cold!
That must have been
a masterpiece.
"Eyebrow cats"? I sure would
have liked to see that.
How about "Makoto Neko"?
(Makoto is his name; pun on similar pronunciation)
What do you mean?
A cat with my face?
Dancing like this...?
That might be good.
I'd like to see that.
A Tsukishima souvenir...
"Makoto Neko" for 500 yen.
It won't sell.
It'll never sell.
What are you saying?
I didn't expect you to hang in
there until the end, Yuka.
I wanted he money.
What did you decide you're
going to do from now?
Are you going back home?
No, I'm not.
I'm going to rent an apartment,
somewhere and live by myself.
Are you really going to do that?
I've already decided.
After all, even I think it's
strange for me to live in
luxury with my parents' money
while I'm always complaining
about them all the time.
It made me feel sick.
But it's not easy...
You'll have to work part-time.
I'll find something.
You'll have to separate
the trash yourself.
I can do that much.
In that case, you can
eat my share, too.
Are you sure?
Go ahead, and eat.
I like people who willingly
take on hardship.
Although I don't like your dancing.
I don't like your dancing either.
Let's just enjoy our
"monja" today.
Friendship suits "monja", doesn't it?
I bought croquettes.
It's Akira's favorite.
Then maybe I should put green
onions and deep-fried tofu
in the miso soup tonight...
Akira likes that.
No matter what happens, if
you eat food that you like
for dinner, you'll manage
to get through somehow.
Hello...
Yes?
It's Naoko.
Welcome.
Thank you for yesterday.
I didn't tell Akira.
Thank you.
Shimada...?
Sano...
Why are you here today?
Is it for math again?
No... I wanted to
talk to you.
You do?
Come on in then.
You don't have to serve
tea or anything
Really?
Okay...
I'm a little worried, so
should I take a look?
Do that.
What did you want to
talk to me about?
Actually, yesterday...
I went to the amusement park.
I sat down on the bench in
front of the Ferris wheel.
Why did you do that?
I wanted to know
how you felt...
...when you waited all that
time for your father.
I felt like crying.
I could see a small
roller coaster,
and the Merry-go-round.
When I thought that's what
you were looking at while
you waited for your father...
So what about it?
I'm sorry.
I wasn't going to tell
you about going to the
amusement park...
But I really didn't want to
hide anything from you.
That's why I'll never bring
up your father again, but
I wanted to tell you
what I did.
I'm really sorry.
What is it anyway?
Sano...?
Why did you do that?
Why do you have to
talk about that?
Sano...?
Go home!
Just go home!
What do you think you're
doing, Akira?
It's none of your
business, Hitomi!
That has nothing to
do with it, does it?
Just leave me alone!
Akira!
Wait, Akira!
What's wrong, Akira?
What happened?
Sano...?
I'll have you know...
That this is my
only father.
The father who abandoned
me never existed.
A father like that
isn't a father.
Wait, Akira!
Akira!
Come back, Akira!
Akira! Akira!
What happened?
Sorry about the
commotion...
Akira s hurting...
But there's nothing we can
do to stop the hurt...