Trying too Hard to Find Happiness
Episode 56
The Ippongi family has been officially acknowledged by
the city of Tokyo as a foster care home.
Congratulations!
Thank you! We did it!
Can I take a look at it?
It's true, my name is on it!
Amazing!
The two-day training for newly registered
foster parents finally started.
At this training session, they'll have lectures
and group discussions, and also a chance to visit
one of the child care facilities.
Good morning!
Your name please...
It's Ippongi Hitomi.
These are today's materials.
Ms. Ippongi...
Good morning.
It's about to begin...
I know this will be useful for you.
It looks like...
...I'm the youngest one here, doesn't it?
Of course! There aren't many 20 year-old foster
parents around.
Oh, right.
Ms Ippongi...
Mr. Izumiya... Hello.
Isn't it great that you've been
recognized as a foster care home?
Thank you.
But it all starts now.
Please apply yourself and study hard.
I will.
This newly registered foster parents training is meant
for new foster parents who will be caring for
foster children in their homes.
A case like Hitomi's where she is living in the home
with the children as an assistant to Katsutaro
is very rare.
Good morning, everyone.
I'm Izumiya, the section chief of the child care
counseling center's treatment services section.
In school, we have what we call classmates or
contemporaries of the same school, but for all of you
who are here for this training class, you can be
considered foster parent classmates.
You're all here as foster parents.
Being a foster parent comes
with many hardships.
You can talk with each other about your concerns and
encourage each other...you'll feel like you
have someone to rely on.
Treasure this chance to meet each other,
enjoy the next two days, and make friends.
Thank you...
People decide to become foster parents
for a variety of reasons.
They want to be useful to society in some way...
After raising their own children, they want to
raise another child...
Or there are those who don't have any children...
Whatever the reasons the foster parents and foster
children will form a new family.
You'll soon be meeting the children, and
these children for one reason or another are
no longer able to live with their parents.
Many of them have been deeply hurt,
and carry that hurt in their hearts.
But that's not the children's fault.
It's a family problem.
It could be illness, poverty, neglect...
There are a variety of circumstances.
These children carry more sadness and pain in
their hearts than we can even imagine.
Please let these children get a taste of what it
means to be a family
Make them realize how wonderful and warm
a family can be.
And that an adult is looking after them
Let them experience that feeling every single day
If you do that, you'll see the children's eyes sparkle
And they'll be able to enjoy going to school
What he said reminded Hitomi of
the three children living with them.
Shota, Yuria and Akira had smiles on their
faces now because of all the time they spent in
the warmth of Katsutaro and Setsuko's home.
And Keiko, too
In truth they're not my real parents, but I
thought - they are my parents,
and I am their child
These people who fully turn to face me ARE my parents
In the afternoon , they started a discussion
about becoming a foster parent
In each group, an experienced foster parent
served as an advisor
About the last name...
We're wondering whether to raise the child
using the child's real last name or our last name?
That is something to be concerned about, isn't it.
I think it's case by case.
For school children, thinking about when they leave home,
Many foster parents will use the child's real name
from the beginning
But for younger children, it's hard to know how
much they grasp the situation, and
to avoid confusion, a lot of foster homes
use their own last names as an alias.
In our case, the children all use their own last names
Our nameplate lists different names for three
of the children living with us
Are there young children?
Yes.. We have a child in the third grade
His name is Shota, and he uses his real name.
So you're already thinking  about the children's
future, aren't you?
To let them know they each have a life
of their own before they came to us.
One of the children is already independent,
and is a nurse now. Her name is Keiko...
She came over the other day to tell my grandpa that
she's getting married, and to ask for his approval..
Grandpa told her that she didn't have to worry
about what he thought anymore... In fact,
he was grateful that she came home to him as if
she were his real daughter
Keiko was this little, and now she's telling me that
she's getting married. Isn't it strange!
This is what you brought the hijiki (type of seaweed) in.
And this was the "kinpira gobo" (fried burdock root)
It was really delicious
This one was the gomayagoshi (black sesame sauce).
Do you want to count them all again?
Katsu... You remember when Keiko broke all of those
planters over there
! do... Keiko really was a handful
She was the first child we took in as foster parents
She grew up to be a really good daughter
Thanks to all the hardship you went through to raise her.
I watered them everyday.
I'm talking about Keiko!
Being a nurse is hard work, and a respectable profession
Maybe I should enter them in the next exhibition
Not the plants, Keiko!
I know!
You're hopeless.
Hello!
Hitomi...
How was today's training?
I really learned a lot
I feel like we're classmates
I'm glad to hear that.
It must be rough
You have to do a training like this everytime
You register new foster parents, don't you?
Yes, but we still don't have enough foster parents.
There are so many children who need foster care
So, even if we're busy, we don't mind.
Hitomi....you have one more day's training..
Please do your best.
I will.
Goodbye.
Thanks for your hard work!
The next day, they went to visit a home
for orphaned,
neglected or abused children.
It looks like everyone's here, doesn't it?
My face is small, my heart is big, and they call me
Kubota, the man with the mustache
The children who will be comihg to live with all
of you, have all lived here at a facility like this
or at a home for infants.
The children are all at school right now, so
we'll start by looking at the dormitory
I'm going to check with the dormitory first,
so please wait here for a moment
Hitomi?
Keiko!
What are you doing here?
We came to see the orphanage as part of our training.
I was raised here, before I went to live in Tsukishima
Is that right?
Keiko?
Kubo-Papa.
Do you know each other?
She's my Tsukishima father's granddaughter
She's looking after Shota and the other children
Is that right? Nice to meet you.
Everyone.
This is one of our graduates
I looked after her for three years.
I'm sorry to intrude
I came here today because I have an announcement..
What is it?
I'm going to get married.
Really?
Congratulations!
Thank you
Thank you very much.
I want to thank you, too.
I'm so glad
It was painful for Hitomi to see Keiko look so happy.
It's begun - the Eyebrow Cats
Commentary by B-Boy MOBO. Enjoy!
Get into it and try the cat poses
Big, wide open and...POSE
Whiskers pose...eyebrows, eyebrows
Eyebrows, eyebrows
And now, introductions
Yuka...big movements
Hitomi...Junko
And last is Moe...Nice spin!
Now hip hop step, New Jack Swing
Butt and point, your butt keeps the rhythm!
Next to the side, big with down rhythm
That's Running Man, then
Handshake - it's fun in pairs
Try it with your friends
siblings and parents!
Right, left, cheek, jump!
Then all four Touch - Pose - MEOWWWW
Hip hop step - Housing style
All four - big moves
Step with down rhythm
Last is pose with crossed arms
Nodding heads
Everyone gather together and....
POSE!
Great, how was that?
That was the Eyebrow Cats
Please watch, and try it with your family, siblings
and friends! Dance the "Eyebrow Cats" together.
Commentary by: M-O-B-O...!