CHAPTER 18
Season of Love
Episode 104
Written by
SUZUKI Satoshi
Music by
YAMASHITA Kosuke
English Subtitle by
NIPPON GOLDEN NETWORK
Hitomi went to have monja
with Ken in Tsukishima.
Good evening
Are you celebrating again?
\hidi ^ nyiii... ^v^ yui
another client.
You're really doing well,
aren't you, Momoko?
Let's call Hitomi.
We should all call her
Hitomi's already coming
With her boyfriend.
Boyfriend?
Someone's already here
Check it out
Does Hitomi have
a boyfriend?
I don't know their
relationship status, but
he's a customer at the
diner, and they were
enjoying talking to each
other this afternoon
What is he like?
I he one of the
guys in Tsukiji?
If he was, I'd
happy for her, but
he's a good-looking
dancer
A good-looking dancer?
Hitomi!
We're having a company
drinking party
Good evening.
We just happened
to be here
A likely story
Who is he?
This is Ken. He gives me
advice about dancing and
comes to the diner
once in a while
Pleased to meet you
I'm Suzuki
Your name is Suzuki?
Common, isn't it?
Is that right?
I'm Hitomi's mother...
Hitomi says shes's
indebted to you
My pleasure
We have something to
talk about today
I see! Just for the
two of you
Come on in.
I like him! Is Hitomi
going out with him?
Probably
He's wonderful!
Hitomi's not doing
too badly
It's good, isn't it?
Isn't it?
Our ^oup bl! s
different..
of iff ffent va ie les
Thanks
What did you want
to ask me?
It's about Dance Beat.
I heard a rumor that you
and Ray were going to
enter it this year.
new about the rumor.
Are you really
going to enter?
I want to see you
and Ray dance.
I'm happy to hear
that,
but I don't know
Why?
Because CHEAPASS
belonged to
three of us
hld^j1V
Ul's sister ame
Yid he ibl3 RA ot to
urTaway, n be sure
UJH\J:hi
I see...
That's pretty heavy..
It doesn't
match monja
I'm sorry
I Ijl i
Thank you
It was delicious
Come again.
Next time let's have a
leisurely meal together.
You don't have
to say that.
But you're indebted
to him, aren't you?
I'm going to see him off
Why don't you Xdki a e o r
and show him around?
You don't have to
worry about us
OK, let's go.
Goodbye
Did you see that?
Isn't he great?
I have to give
Hitomi credit!
He's good-looking,
isn't he?
He's legendary
There are some cool
guys here in Tokyo.
I agree
I wonder about that.
I don't think so.
He s just putting on airs
He probably thinks the
silent type is cool
But he just doesn't have
anything to say
By any chance, are you
in love with Hitomi?
Are you?
It's not like that..
It's the neighborly
thing to do to
make sure she's not hooking
up with some weird guy
Then you should be glad
it's someone like him.
I'll have you know that
ol a lot stranger
than he is.
Why are you all agreeing
with her, Sapporo team?
Is this where you
were, Yuzo?
Mr ishidas gry
You just disappeared
Get off my bat**
Are you my dad's shadow?
Let's go! We want
to go home already.
All right! I'm coming
Put it on my tab, Mako.
All right
I'm so relieved
About what?
Hitomi... one 5a late
bloomer, so I thought
she wouldn't find
a boyfriend
But from what I saw,
he didn't seem like
her boyfriend yet
More like admiration for a
more experienced dancer.
That's true
It would grow into
a deeper relationship
from there.
I wish it would
work out for her
I can find my way to
the station from here
Thank you for today
I'm sorry for asking
such a strange question
Everyone really wants o
see you and Ray dance
up on the stage again.
I told you before that
dance is life, didn't I?
You did.
That's what it is.
Do your best with
ROSE MARY.
I will... Good night
Good night
Thank you for
everything
Not at all
Take care
Good night.
Make sure you 15th won't
catch his cold...
I can't have you
a in timeo
on i ^vorry'
Yuzo
Sit over here
What is it?
I've been in business
since I was 8 ears 19..
It's been 5 ears n
4 started h rie
business, managed employees
and increased
of regular customers
I feel)' e o
veil s nan.
Wh \ .g o
r ing Ao a
That's why I want you to
hurry and get the people
in Tsukiji to trust you, and
become a full-fledged man.
Getting you to become a
respectable man and
have you take over
Ishida Shoten is
the last big job
I have left
Don't forget that
So Ken's feelings are
still a mystery.
All I know is that it isn't
t "St sirrii 1e for Ken
to dance again
We don't have to work
today, so shall we
have a meeting about
our costumes?
Where shall we have it?
Shall we go
to my place?
Can you come, Hitomi?
I'll ask Grandpa first,
but I think it's OK
Let's go then
I'm sorry... I forgot my
towel, so can I meet
you all later?
Be careful
I didn't know you
were still here
I'm sorry... I was just
so fascinated
Excuse me..
What is it?
Are you and Kne going
to enter Dance Beat?
Who told you that?
Well...
That's OK...
The answer right
now is "no"
It's true that I want
Ken to dance
I think it'll be
good for him
Dance is all he has
That's why I got him to
come back from New York,
grid help with the choreography
or the promotion video,
and work with the dancers.
I wanted him to get back
up on the stage again
Unfortunately, it's not going
as well as I thought
I occ
I'm sorry... I'm going to
work on it a little more
I'm sorry for
interrupting.
Ray said she wanted Ken
to dance again, but...
So the problem is
Ken's feelings
Does it mean that he can't
dance without Eiji?
That's how perfect
their unit sas.
Ken hasn't danced on stage
for eight ears..
It shows how big Eiji's
loss is to Ken.
That's true
But don't you want to see
Ken and Ray dance?
As a dancer, I'd like to see
those two dance again.
When Ken and Ray danced
OCKS V.at time, it was
really terrific,
wasn't it?
I want to see it.
I do, too
Wait a minute!
If they're really going
to enter Dance Beat,
Ken and Ray will
be our rivals!
We have o in it
I'm going to do my best
so we j/vin it fo ue
It's your revenge,
isn't it, Hitomi?
That's right. I couldn't
enter last year, so this
will be my revenge
We have no choice
We have to do it
This time, unless we put
5Qt 120 percent, we won't
be able to win
hen ei sput" MX
20 percent.
Let's aim or$J20 W:ent,
and do our best!
We'll do our best.
All Hitomi and the others
could think about right
now was Dance Beat