HITOMI
CHAPTER 7
"Let's Be Friends"
Episode 39
In order to get Yuka to join
their group in the audition,
Hitomi invited her
to Tsukishima.
It's kind of soothing, isn't it?
It has flavor.
It looks like Yuka likes it here.
Your house must be
awesome, Yuka.
It must be a mansion.
You're so lucky...
Your father runs a lot of
different restaurants.
A high-class Japanese
restaurant...
Japanese food...
A high-class shabu
shabu restaurant...
Shabu-shabu...
A high class Italian
restaurant...
Italian!
The KITA Dining Group is
in the gourmet guide, too.
Do you get to eat
all that for free?
Let's not talk
about my family.
I hate it... My parents both act
like they're such big celebrities.
Looks delicious.
It looks delicious!
It's delicious!
Is it?
Now I know what you meant about
the way it feels in your mouth, Moe.
The sliced squid is
delicious, too.
Sliced squid?
This?
I want to try it, too.
It's really good.
Delicious!
I'm glad you like it.
We have a lot of variety
on our menu.
Then the other day, he came up
with a "monja" Arabia...
It was my idea.
My name's Hiroshi.
Bring out the explanation.
We have a fun explanation
about the history of "monja".
Wait a minute!
We wanted to talk today...
You do?
What did you bring
that out here?
You told me to!
Junko!
Get to the point.
Yuka...
She's not listening.
No... she's listening.
I'm sorry about the
other day...
I just lost my temper...
I meant to apologize to you.
I'll apologize, so don't you want to try
out for the audition with the two of us?
Your dancing is awesome, so Junko
and I really want to dance with you.
We need you to
win the audition.
Won't you dance
with us?
I don't know. It's not that I
absolutely don't want to do it, but...
Dancing alone suits
me better.
I'd like to try dancing
in a group, but...
It just doesn't
seem to work out.
After enjoying their "monja",
they went to explore the
town that still had a
nostalgic feel to it.
I'm home! I brought
my friends with me.
We've been waiting for you.
This is Yuka... Junko... and
Moe... This my grandpa.
Pleased to meet you.
Thank you for being
friends with Hitomi.
These are my children...
Akira... Yuria... Shota.
Hello...
They're the children
I told you about.
This is...
Hello...
These are our neighbors...
Yujiro and Ume.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Yuzo.
Sit down.
This is great. I've never
been in a house like this.
It's dirty, isn't it?
You should talk!
Is there a second floor?
There's a really old
laundry area, too.
I'd like to see it.
Do you want to go up?
Is it okay?
Sure!
Go ahead.
I think I will.
She seems to like our
house, doesn't she?
It's unusual to
a young gal.
Gal...?
She's from a rich family.
Her father is the president
of KITA Dining Group.
The one with the high-class
Japanese restaurant and
high class shabu shabu restaurant...?
They also have a high-class
Italian restaurant.
That's not bad.
We're a bonito flake wholesaler.
We make bonito flakes.
This is Yuria's
and my room.
Nice breeze.
I give those kids credit.
They don't live with their
parents, but they're happy
and doing their best.
Right now, this
is their home.
This is nice.
Isn't it?
You're getting in the way.
The Chinese cabbage is ready.
Here you go young lady.
We have our own pot here.
Don't worry...
Young lady... Your father
is really great, isn't he?
I respect a man like that.
Opening so many restaurants.
He's really something.
And every one of those
restaurants come out
in the gourmet magazines.
I think your honorable
father is great.
Let's not talk
about my father.
She's right. She doesn't want
to talk about him, so stop it.
She's being modest.
The young lady's just
being modest.
This is when we need to push.
What do you mean by that?
Never mind. This is
between adults.
Young lady...? In such a
high class restaurant as
that, they must use really
good quality bonito flakes...
Our bonito flakes are really
good quality, too.
Don't you agree?
We have old, traditional
restaurants in Ginza and
Nihonbashi that buy
from us all the time.
Don't you think it's in
bad taste to talk about
business at a time
like this?
He's right. Rubbing your hands
together like that, too.
When it comes to the daughter
of someone that important,
I'm so humbled, I just rub my hands
together without even thinking about it.
Young lady...! Please
don't look at him..
I'd like you to
look at me.
If you could just mention
it your honorable father,
and see if he would like
to sample our product...
I told you to stop...
Excuse me!
I'm leaving!
Yuka... ?
I'm sorry, Hitomi...
I don't feel well.
I'm sorry, everybody.
I'm sorry.
Thank you for the meal.
Yuka! Wait!
Yuka!
Did I say something wrong?
Look at what you did! You
upset the young lady.
Did you hear what you said?
You sounded just like
a samurai humbling himself
before his lord.
You idiot!
What did you mean by
"time to push"?
Never mind. It's for
adults only.
Tell her what it means!
Yuka!
I hate people who call
me "young lady".
People like that aren't
looking at me...
They're seeing my dad.
I think I understand
how you feel, but...
Up until now, there have
been a lot of kids who
tried to make friends with
me, thinking that they
could get something
out of it.
We're not like that.
We want to be with you.
I'm sorry. I'm going home.
Yuka!
Yuka...?
I'm hungry...
Here they come...
Hitomi...
What happened to
the young lady?
She went home.
Did we make her angry...?
Talking about her father
and his business...
That might have had something
to do with it...
I'm sorry.
I know you were trying to
get to know each other...
You're angry, aren't
you, Hitomi?
Not at all. I'm not angry.
I'm not angry at all.
You sound a little sharp.
You're all upset,
aren't you?
Not at all...
No... We're not, so don't
let it bother you.
I see...
Let's go finish
our pot stew...
They're not angry...
I'm glad. Let's eat, too.
The door's locked.
It's Ishida...
The next day...
She's here!
Shall we go?
Yuka!
Were you lying in
wait for me?
We need you to
dance with us.
Without you, we can't
win the audition.
Just try it once... See how the
three of us dance together.
We already have some
of it choreographed.
I've reserved a studio to
practice at from today
until the audition.
I'm going to practice
there by myself.
You two do your best.
Pick me up at four.
Yuka!
She turned us down
flat, didn't she?
What are you going to do?
Shall we do it with just
the two of us then?
After Yuka turned them down,
Junko and Hitomi got down
to practicing for the
audition seriously.
In hip hop dancing, you build
on the basic steps available,
adding steps and movements
that reflect the dancers'
individuality. and enhance
the group's ambience.
When you get a good idea, you
write it down right away.
Solidifying your movements
a little at a time.
It's also important to build
up your muscles, so you can
move just the way you
picture the dance moves.
Once you have the whole
dance choreographed, you
practice it over and over again, so
your body will remember each move.
When dancing in a group, it's
important to have teamwork.
You keep practicing until
you get your timing to
match, and once you have that,
then your dance is complete.
From three days before the
audition, Hitomi left the
meal preparations to Katsutaro
and the children, so she
would have more time
to practice.
What do you think?
Do you think we look good?
We do, but then again
maybe not.
What do you think, Moe?
It's not explosive enough.
You seem to be
holding back.
You two can do better.
What are we supposed to do?
The audition is tomorrow.
Put more of yourself
into your dancing.
We learned in diet class
to listen carefully to
the music, and dance
more like you.
You mean go back
to your roots?
But how are we going
to do that?
Junko... You have to think
"I'm hot! I'm going to
make my major debut, and go
back home in a blaze of glory!"
What about me?
You just think, "I'm huge! I'm throwing
the balance off but I don't care!"
I'm hot!
I'm huge!
Shall we show them
some attitude?
Ok. Let's do it.
Since coming to Tokyo, this
will be her first real
audition, and Hitomi is going
to give it all she's got.
The audition is tomorrow.
To be continued...